{
"rows": [
{
"Question": "Adam Cole beat this man to win his first NXT Title",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "After beating Undertaker, who said \"This is my yard now\"?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Alexa Bliss shot a fireball at what Superstar in January 2021?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2020, what Superstar has won the most DLC Matches?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2020, who had only 1 reign as Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2020, who has competed in the most Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2021, which team has been both NXT and Raw Tag Champions?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2021, who had not won multiple Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "As of December 2020, which of these had Drew McIntyre not won?",
"Answer": "Universal Title"
},
{
"Question": "As of March 2021, who was the last man to hold the WWE Title for more than a year?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "At what 1999 event did Big Show win his first WWE Championship?",
"Answer": "Survivor Series"
},
{
"Question": "At what 2008 event did Kane win the ECW World Title?",
"Answer": "Wrestlemania XXIV"
},
{
"Question": "At what 2018 event did Ronda Rousey win the Raw Women's Title?",
"Answer": "SummerSlam"
},
{
"Question": "At what event did Sycho Sid win his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Survivor Series"
},
{
"Question": "At what event was the first Elimination Chamber match held?",
"Answer": "Survivor Series"
},
{
"Question": "At what Pay-Per-View did The Rock make his debut?",
"Answer": "Survivor Series"
},
{
"Question": "At what WrestleMania did Undertaker's incredible streak begin?",
"Answer": "WrestleMania VII"
},
{
"Question": "At which 1991 Pay-Per-View event did the WWE Title NOT change hands?",
"Answer": "SummerSlam"
},
{
"Question": "By what name did Road Dogg go when he first entered WWE?",
"Answer": "The Roadie"
},
{
"Question": "Diesel first entered WWE as a bodyguard for what Superstar?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Dolph Ziggler debuted in WWE in what faction?",
"Answer": "The Spirit Squad"
},
{
"Question": "Earthquake won the World Tag Team Titles with what partner?",
"Answer": "Typhoon"
},
{
"Question": "Elia announced his 2020 return to Raw by attacking what Superstar?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "From what city was Cactus Jack billed from?",
"Answer": "Truth or Consequences, New Mexico"
},
{
"Question": "From what entry did Shawn Michaels win the 1995 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "#1"
},
{
"Question": "From what French city did Andre the Giant hail?",
"Answer": "Grenoble"
},
{
"Question": "How long did Kane's first WWE Title reign last?",
"Answer": "1 day"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors were in the first Royal Rumble match (1988)?",
"Answer": 20
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors were in the first Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": 20
},
{
"Question": "How many times did Trish Stratus win the Women's Title?",
"Answer": 7
},
{
"Question": "How many times has Triple H been World Champion?",
"Answer": 14
},
{
"Question": "How many times was Razor Ramon Intercontinental Champion?",
"Answer": 4
},
{
"Question": "How many WrestleMania matches has Undertaker won? (as of 2020)",
"Answer": 24
},
{
"Question": "How tall was Andre the Giant?",
"Answer": "7'4\""
},
{
"Question": "In the game, what color is the POWERHOUSE class?",
"Answer": "Red"
},
{
"Question": "In the game, what color is the STRIKER class?",
"Answer": "Black"
},
{
"Question": "In the game, what is NOT an Ability Style?",
"Answer": "Physical"
},
{
"Question": "In the game, Which of these is a TOUR in THE ROAD?",
"Answer": "NXT Tour"
},
{
"Question": "In the game, which Superstar helps Alexa Bliss create more Blue Gems?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "In what branch of the Armed Services did Bobby Lashley serve?",
"Answer": "Army"
},
{
"Question": "In what city did Bruno Sammartino win his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "New York"
},
{
"Question": "In what city did the historic WrestleMania III take place?",
"Answer": "Detroit"
},
{
"Question": "In what city was WrestleMania X held?",
"Answer": "New York"
},
{
"Question": "In what event did Chad Gable compete in the Olympics?",
"Answer": "Greco-Roman Wrestling"
},
{
"Question": "In what event did Mark Henry compete before joining WWE",
"Answer": "Weightlifting"
},
{
"Question": "In what match did Cesaro and Shinsuke Nakamura win the SmackDown Tag Titles in July 2020?",
"Answer": "Tables Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what military branch did \"Road Dogg\" Jesse James serve?",
"Answer": "Marines"
},
{
"Question": "In what sport did Ronda Rousey win an Olympic medal?",
"Answer": "Judo"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of contest did Ultimate Warrior and Rick Rude meet at the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Super Posedown"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Adam Cole win his first NXT North American Title?",
"Answer": "Ladder Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Big E win the Intercontinental Title in December 2020?",
"Answer": "Lumberjack Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Bobby Lashley win his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Lumberjack Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Bray Wyatt beat Kane at SummerSlam 2012?",
"Answer": "Ring of Fire Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Bret Hart defend the WWE Title at SummerSlam 1994?",
"Answer": "Steel Cage Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did JBL compete at WrestleMania XXIV?",
"Answer": "Belfast Brawl"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Kane beat Triple H for the Intercontinental Title at Judgment Day 2001?",
"Answer": "Chain Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of Match did Randy Savage compete at WrestleMania X?",
"Answer": "Falls Count Anywhere"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Roman Reigns defend the Universal Title at the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Last Man Standing Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Shane McMahon beat the Miz at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Falls Count Anywhere Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Sheamus win his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Tables Match"
},
{
"Question": "January 2021's Superstar Spectacle aired to celebrate what country's Republic Day?",
"Answer": "India"
},
{
"Question": "Mickie James first joined WWE as whose biggest fan?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "Mickie James' \"Mick Kick\" was an homage to what Superstar's \"Chick Kick\"?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "Name the SmackDown Women's Champion for most of 2020",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Of these Superstars, who was the first cash in their Money in the Bank in a Hell in a Cell Match?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "On what segment did The Miz interview other Superstars?",
"Answer": "Miz TV"
},
{
"Question": "On what talk show did Brutus Beefcake interview Superstars?",
"Answer": "The Barber Shop"
},
{
"Question": "On what talk show does Kevin Owens interview people?",
"Answer": "The KO Show"
},
{
"Question": "On what team did Undertake compete at Survivor Series 1993?",
"Answer": "The All-Americans"
},
{
"Question": "On which WWE show did Paige act as general manager?",
"Answer": "SmackDown"
},
{
"Question": "On whom did Alexa Bliss cash her Money in the Bank in 2018?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Rey Mysterio won a tag Title in December 2005 with what partner?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Shane McMahon began a rivalry with what Raw Superstar in March 2021?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Six women worked together to eliminate which Superstar from the 2018 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Spell this Superstar's name.",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Spell this Superstar's name.",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Spell this Superstar's name.",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "The \"Two Man Power Trip\" paired Triple H with what man?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "The nickname of this Legend is what?",
"Answer": "The Animal"
},
{
"Question": "The one time two men won the Royal Rumble it was Bret Hart and who?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "This Superstar or Legend is associated with what object?",
"Answer": "Hammer"
},
{
"Question": "What are the initials for the person with this jacket?",
"Answer": "DZ"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2020 Robert Roode won all but which Title",
"Answer": "Universal Title"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2020, what was NOT an in-game character variant for AJ Styles?",
"Answer": "The Face that Runs the Place"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2020, which Title had Shinsuke Nakamura never won?",
"Answer": "Universal Title"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2020, who hasn't the Miz won a Tag Team Title with?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2021, who had entered a record 18 Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Titus O'Neil won a Tag Team Title as part of what pairing?",
"Answer": "Prime Time Players"
},
{
"Question": "Tucker is a former All-American Wrestler at a university from which state?",
"Answer": "Arizona"
},
{
"Question": "What additional Title did then-WWE Champ Seth Rollins win at SummerSlam 2015?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "What branch of the armed forces did Sgt. Slaughter serve in?",
"Answer": "Marines"
},
{
"Question": "What British city is Pete Dunne from?",
"Answer": "Birmingham"
},
{
"Question": "What California city is Jey Uso's hometown?",
"Answer": "San Francisco"
},
{
"Question": "What Canadian city is Bret Hart from?",
"Answer": "Calgary"
},
{
"Question": "What Champion was SmackDown's #1 pick on night 2 of the 2020 Draft?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "What city does MVP call home?",
"Answer": "Miami"
},
{
"Question": "What city hosted consecutive WrestleMania events (IV and V)?",
"Answer": "Atlantic City"
},
{
"Question": "What city hosted the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Houston"
},
{
"Question": "What city hosted WrestleMania I, X, and XX?",
"Answer": "New York"
},
{
"Question": "What city hosted WrestleMania X-Seven and 25?",
"Answer": "Houston"
},
{
"Question": "What city hosted WrestleMania XXX and 34?",
"Answer": "New Orleans"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Irwin R. Schyster from?",
"Answer": "Washington D.C."
},
{
"Question": "What city is Johnny Gargano from?",
"Answer": "Cleveland"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Razor Ramon from?",
"Answer": "Miami"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Sasha Banks from?",
"Answer": "Boston"
},
{
"Question": "What city was not a host city of WrestleMania 2?",
"Answer": "Detroit"
},
{
"Question": "What color was the Ultimate Warrior's Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Yellow"
},
{
"Question": "What country is Jinder Mahal from?",
"Answer": "India"
},
{
"Question": "What country was Earthquake from?",
"Answer": "Canada"
},
{
"Question": "What does JBL claim as his hometown?",
"Answer": "New York"
},
{
"Question": "What does the 'P' in 'MVP' stand for?",
"Answer": "Porter"
},
{
"Question": "What does the Miz now consider his hometown?",
"Answer": "Hollywood"
},
{
"Question": "What does this bag contain?",
"Answer": "A Snake"
},
{
"Question": "What event is considered the start of the Road to WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Royal Rumble"
},
{
"Question": "What faction did Braun Strowman initally join?",
"Answer": "The Wyatt Family"
},
{
"Question": "What faction promotes the \"Power of Positivity\"?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "What faction rode a tank into their SummerSlam 2006 match?",
"Answer": "DX"
},
{
"Question": "What faction wants you to \"Feel the Power\"?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was Christian in when he first debuted in WWE?",
"Answer": "The Brood"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was Stephanie McMahon a co-leader of?",
"Answer": "The Authority"
},
{
"Question": "What former Champion returned to NXT's roster in September 2020?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "What future champion drove Rhythm and Blues to the ring at WrestleMania VI?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "What future champion joined Drew McIntyre in 3MB?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "What group did X-Pac shockingly join early in his WWE career?",
"Answer": "The Million Dollar Corporation"
},
{
"Question": "What Hall of Famer made his WrestleMania debut at WrestleMania IV?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "What Hall of Famer trained Ember Moon?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "What instrument does Xavier Woods play?",
"Answer": "Trombone"
},
{
"Question": "What is a signature move of the owner of this jacket?",
"Answer": "Diamond Cutter"
},
{
"Question": "What is a signature move of the Usos?",
"Answer": "Double Uce"
},
{
"Question": "What is an MVP signature move?",
"Answer": "Play of the Day"
},
{
"Question": "What is Big Show's hometown?",
"Answer": "Tampa"
},
{
"Question": "What is Faarooq's actual name?",
"Answer": "Ron Simmons"
},
{
"Question": "What is King Corbin's hometown?",
"Answer": "Kansas City"
},
{
"Question": "What is Lana's hometown?",
"Answer": "Moscow"
},
{
"Question": "What is NOT an ability for Adam Cole \"The Undisputed Era\"?",
"Answer": "Knee Drop"
},
{
"Question": "What is NOT an ability for Aleister Black \"NXT\" at 1-Star Bronze?",
"Answer": "Superkick"
},
{
"Question": "What is not part of Triple H's name?",
"Answer": "Harold"
},
{
"Question": "What is Randy Orton's middle name?",
"Answer": "Keith"
},
{
"Question": "What is Road Dogg's name?",
"Answer": "Jesse James"
},
{
"Question": "What is the catchphrase of this Superstar or Legend?",
"Answer": "Damn!"
},
{
"Question": "What is the class of the character with this tie?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What is the Godfather's hometown?",
"Answer": "Las Vegas"
},
{
"Question": "What is the Honky Tonk Man's signature move?",
"Answer": "Shake, Rattle, and Roll"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of a Trish Stratus signature move?",
"Answer": "Stratusfaction"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of Erik & Ivar's tag team?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of the Pig in the Firefly Fun House?",
"Answer": "Huskus"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of the WWE clown competitor?",
"Answer": "Doink"
},
{
"Question": "What is the next letter in this logo?",
"Answer": "Y"
},
{
"Question": "What is The Rock's hometown?",
"Answer": "Miami"
},
{
"Question": "What is this?",
"Answer": "Crown"
},
{
"Question": "What item did Brutus Beefcake usually bring to the ring?",
"Answer": "Shears"
},
{
"Question": "What item would The Honky Tonk Man often bring to the ring?",
"Answer": "Guitar"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend defeated Mr. McMahon at WrestleMania XIX?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend did Charlotte Flair beat at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend has flames tattooed all over his bald skull?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend is known as The Nature Boy?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend served as host of 2018's Crown Jewel event?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "What legend was the #30 entrant in the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend weighed nearly 600 pounds?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "What longtime rival inducted Ricky Steamboat into the Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What more conservative persona did the Godfather adopt in 2000?",
"Answer": "The Goodfather"
},
{
"Question": "What move does Brutus Beefcake use to incapacitate opponents?",
"Answer": "Sleeper Hold"
},
{
"Question": "What move does Ember Moon user to finish off opponents?",
"Answer": "Eclipse"
},
{
"Question": "What move does Ronda Rousey use to tap out opponents?",
"Answer": "Armbar"
},
{
"Question": "What name did Kevin Nash originally use in WWE?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "What name did X-Pac use in WCW?",
"Answer": "Syxx"
},
{
"Question": "What new Raw segment did Shane McMahon introduce in 2020?",
"Answer": "Raw Underground"
},
{
"Question": "What new Title was introduced on the March 10, 2021 Episode of NXT?",
"Answer": "NXT Women's Tag Team Titles"
},
{
"Question": "What NWO member did Stone Cold Steve Austin face at WrestleMania X8?",
"Answer": "Scott Hall"
},
{
"Question": "What object is associated with this Superstar or Legend?",
"Answer": "Anvil"
},
{
"Question": "What pair captured the Raw Tag Titles in March 2020?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "What pair won the Interbrand Tag Team Battle Royal at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler and Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "What rival inducted The Iron Sheik into the Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "What signature move did the British Bulldog use?",
"Answer": "Running Powerslam"
},
{
"Question": "What slogan is this \"W\" part of?",
"Answer": "Who's Next?"
},
{
"Question": "What sport did Randy Savage play professionally before wrestling?",
"Answer": "Baseball"
},
{
"Question": "What sport did Titus O'Neil play professional before coming to WWE?",
"Answer": "Football"
},
{
"Question": "What state is Alexa Bliss from?",
"Answer": "Ohio"
},
{
"Question": "What state is Jake Roberts from?",
"Answer": "Georgia"
},
{
"Question": "What state is Otis from?",
"Answer": "Wisconsin"
},
{
"Question": "What state is Road Dogg from?",
"Answer": "Georgia"
},
{
"Question": "What state is Tucker from?",
"Answer": "Oregon"
},
{
"Question": "What stipulation was added to the Reigns/Uso 2020 Hell in a Cell match?",
"Answer": "Loser must say \"I quit\""
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar challenged for both the Raw and SmackDown women's Titles at SummerSlam 2020?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar ended Bayley's first reign as Raw Women's Champion in April 2017?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar ended Drew McIntre's WWE Title reign at Hell in a Cell 2020?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar got married at SummerSlam 1991?",
"Answer": "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar had a documentary crew with him throughout January 2021?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar had the longest Divas Title reign ever?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar has been inducted in the Hall of Fame twice?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "What superstar has competed as The Demon?",
"Answer": "Finn Bálor"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar has Rey Mysterio not won a Tag Title with?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar has starred in a reality show about his life?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar has used the Yes Lock to make opponents submit?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar inducted Big John Studd into the Hall of Fame in 2004?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar injured Aleister Black's eye in the summer of 2020?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is from Death Valley?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is known as the Charismatic Enigma?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is nicknamed \"The Sassy Southern Belle\"?",
"Answer": "Lacey Evans"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar made finger guns and exclaimed \"Bang Bang!\"?",
"Answer": "Cactus Jack"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar nails opponents with the Panama Sunrise?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar spoke of Macho Madness?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar starred in a 2020 family sitcom?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar used to call herself a hugger?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was a rookie on the 1st season of NXT?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was billed at 7'4\" and 520 pounds?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was separated from his tag team as a result of the 2020 Draft?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was separated from the rest of the New Day in the 2020 Draft?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was the first to pin Braun Strowman?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was undefeated for 2+ years in NXT?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar's 70th birthday was ruined by a brutal attack by Batista in February 2019?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team served as the hosts of WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team was Faarooq a member of?",
"Answer": "The APA"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team was the sole survivor of the Tag Elimination Match at Survivor Series 2018?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team won the champion vs champion match at Survivor Series 2021?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team won the Champions Triple Threat match at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "What team had the longest Title reign in WWE History?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "What team in 2010 ended D-Generation X's Tag Team Title reign?",
"Answer": "Miz and Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "What team was the first 5-time SmackDown Tag Champions?",
"Answer": "New Day"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did Diamond Dallas Page not win in WCW?",
"Answer": "Cruiserweight Title"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did the 1-2-3 Kid win in January 1994?",
"Answer": "Tag Team Title"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did X-Pac first win after returning to WWE in 1998?",
"Answer": "European Title"
},
{
"Question": "What trio was Rikishi a member of?",
"Answer": "Too Cool"
},
{
"Question": "What type of animal is a nickname for Stone Cold?",
"Answer": "rattlesnake"
},
{
"Question": "What type of match did \"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt win at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Falls Count Anywhere"
},
{
"Question": "What unique match type did Big Boss Man win at SummerSlam 1991?",
"Answer": "Jailhouse Match"
},
{
"Question": "What was AJ Styles' first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "WWE Championship"
},
{
"Question": "What was Big Show's name in WCW?",
"Answer": "The Giant"
},
{
"Question": "What was Edge's first singles Title in WWE?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was Jake Roberts' signature move?",
"Answer": "DDT"
},
{
"Question": "What was Junkyard Dog's signature move?",
"Answer": "Thump Powerslam"
},
{
"Question": "What was King Corbin's Title on Raw in 2018?",
"Answer": "Constable"
},
{
"Question": "What was Mr. Perfect's signature move?",
"Answer": "Perfect-Plex"
},
{
"Question": "What was Ricky Steamboat's nickname?",
"Answer": "The Dragon"
},
{
"Question": "What was Steve Austin's nickname in WCW?",
"Answer": "Stunning"
},
{
"Question": "What was Sycho Sid's name when he first competed in WWE?",
"Answer": "Sid Justice"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Bret Hart won in WCW?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Christian won in WWE?",
"Answer": "Light Heavyweight Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Dolph Ziggler won in WWE?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Drew McIntyre won in WWE?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Goldberg won in WCW?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title King Corbin won in WWE?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Rey Mysterio won in WWE?",
"Answer": "Cruiserweight Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title that Syxx won in WCW?",
"Answer": "Cruiserweight Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first WWE Title Bobby Lashley won?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first WWE Title Elias won?",
"Answer": "24/7 Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the last Title Christian won in his career?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Andre the Giant's WWE tag-team championship team?",
"Answer": "The Colossal Connection"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Big Show and The Miz's tag team?",
"Answer": "ShoMiz"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Bret Hart's team with Jim Neidhart?",
"Answer": "The Hart Foundation"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Chad Gable's first tag team?",
"Answer": "American Alpha"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Doink the Clown's team at Survivor Series 1994?",
"Answer": "Clowns R' Us"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Earthquake's tag team?",
"Answer": "The Natural Disasters"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of JBL's tag team?",
"Answer": "APA"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Kalisto's tag team in NXT?",
"Answer": "The Lucha Dragons"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Kevin Nash's NWO splinter group?",
"Answer": "The Wolfpac"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Paige's faction?",
"Answer": "Absolution"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Ric Flair's Faction?",
"Answer": "The 4 Horsemen"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Road Dogg's tag team?",
"Answer": "The New Age Outlaws"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of the Big Boss Man's tag team?",
"Answer": "Twin Towers"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of WWE's Voodoo Practitioner from 1992?",
"Answer": "Papa Shango"
},
{
"Question": "What was the prize money for the WrestleMania I Body Slam Challenge?",
"Answer": "$15,000"
},
{
"Question": "What was the tag team Jim Neidhart joined after the Hart Foundation?",
"Answer": "The New Foundation"
},
{
"Question": "What weapon did Bayley often bring to the ring in the fall of 2020?",
"Answer": "A chair"
},
{
"Question": "What weapon did Edge & Christian love using?",
"Answer": "Chairs"
},
{
"Question": "What woman became a 2-time Tag Team Champion at Royal Rumble 2021?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "What woman calls herself The Queen?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What woman entered the men's 2019 Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "What women's Superstar has been known to use the Sister Abigail finishing move?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE event was once called \"The Thanksgiving Night Tradition\"?",
"Answer": "Survivor Series"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Superstar also does stand-up comedy?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Superstar studies psychology?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "What's the famous Stone Cold Steve Austin saying?",
"Answer": "Austin 3:16"
},
{
"Question": "What's the first name of the Superstar once known as Shorty G?",
"Answer": "Chad"
},
{
"Question": "What's the last name of the Superstar with this tattoo?",
"Answer": "Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "What's the name of Alexa Bliss's interview segment?",
"Answer": "A Moment of Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "What's the name of the Buzzard in the Firefly Fun House?",
"Answer": "Mercy"
},
{
"Question": "When he first joined Raw, Big E was an enforcer for what Superstar?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Where did John Cena win his first WWE Championship?",
"Answer": "WrestleMania"
},
{
"Question": "Where did Ronda Rousey win her Olympic medal?",
"Answer": "Beijing"
},
{
"Question": "Where did The British Bulldog win the Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "London"
},
{
"Question": "Where did Undertaker's legendary streak end?",
"Answer": "WrestleMania 30"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Bam Bam Bigelow from?",
"Answer": "New Jersey"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Bayley from?",
"Answer": "California"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Becky Lynch from?",
"Answer": "Ireland"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Beth Phoenix from?",
"Answer": "Buffalo"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Cesaro from?",
"Answer": "Switzerland"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Dolph Ziggler from?",
"Answer": "Florida"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Edge from?",
"Answer": "Toronto"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Paul Orndorff from?",
"Answer": "Florida"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Roman Reigns from?",
"Answer": "Florida"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Shelton Benjamin from?",
"Answer": "The United States"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Stephanie McMahon from?",
"Answer": "Connecticut"
},
{
"Question": "Where is The Iron Sheik from?",
"Answer": "Iran"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Trish Stratus from?",
"Answer": "Canada"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Vader from?",
"Answer": "The Rocky Mountains"
},
{
"Question": "Where was Big John Studd from?",
"Answer": "Los Angeles"
},
{
"Question": "Where was Junkyard Dog from?",
"Answer": "Charlotte"
},
{
"Question": "Where was Nikolai Volkoff from?",
"Answer": "Soviet Union"
},
{
"Question": "Where was Randy Savage from?",
"Answer": "Florida"
},
{
"Question": "Where were the 2020 Money in the Bank matches held?",
"Answer": "WWE Headquarters"
},
{
"Question": "Which ability does Aleister Black \"Root of All Evil\" have even at 1-star Bronze?",
"Answer": "Black Mass"
},
{
"Question": "Which is a Vader signature movev?",
"Answer": "Vaderbomb"
},
{
"Question": "Which is not a nickname of Randy Orton?",
"Answer": "The Prototype"
},
{
"Question": "Which is not a signature move by Paige?",
"Answer": "PaigePlex"
},
{
"Question": "Which Legend did not help Drew McIntyre in his 2020 Ambulance Match against Randy Orton?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Which Legend hadn't been a victim of The Fiend? (As of 2020)",
"Answer": "Ricky Steamboat"
},
{
"Question": "Which man made his WrestleMania debut at WrestleMania XII?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these has Cesaro won as of November 2020?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these is a signature move of Jeff Hardy?",
"Answer": "Poetry in Motion"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these is the only Title King Corbin won as of November 2020?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these men has not been United States Champion 5 times?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars did not win the NXT Title at least twice?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars did not win the NXT Title at least twice?",
"Answer": "All have won at least twice"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars had the longest Intercontinental Title reign?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars had the shortest WWE Title reign?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars won the United States Title first?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Which state is the Miz originally from?",
"Answer": "Ohio"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar competed at both the first Starrcade and WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Greg Valentine"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar did AJ Styles beat at SummerSlam 2016?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar did Kevin Owens beat for the NXT Title?\"",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar did Mr. McMahon once call the Chosen one?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar has been known as the Big Dog?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar has not won multiple Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar has not won multiple Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar has not won the United States Title 5 times? (as of 2020)",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar is a member of the Street Profits?",
"Answer": "Montez Ford"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar is a member of the Street Profits?",
"Answer": "Angelo Dawkins"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar married Brie Bella?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar spent the most time as WCW Champion?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar uses the Shake Rattle and Roll as a signature move?",
"Answer": "The \"Road Dogg\" Jesse James"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was a Tag Team Champion heading into WrestleMania VI?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was nicknamed \"The Animal\"?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was part of Evolution?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was the first to beat Charlotte Flair at a Pay-Per-View?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar won his first WWE Title by cashing in Money in the Bank?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar won his first WWE Title in a Tables Match?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar's father was not a WWE Superstar?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Which term is a nickname for Rona Rousey?",
"Answer": "Rowdy"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did 2020 Royal Rumble winner Charlotte challenge for at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "NXT Women's Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did 2020 Royal Rumble winner Drew McIntyre challenge for at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "WWE Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did Bam Bam Bigelow win?",
"Answer": "ECW Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did Booker T not win in WWE?",
"Answer": "WWE Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did Goldberg not win?",
"Answer": "WWE Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did Greg Valentine win in September 1984?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did Rikishi win?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did Road Dogg win?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did the Big Boss Man once win?",
"Answer": "Hardcore Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did The British Bulldog never win?",
"Answer": "WWE Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title has Dolph Ziggler never won (through 2020)?",
"Answer": "WWE Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title has Sheamus NOT won?",
"Answer": "NXT Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title has The Rock never won?",
"Answer": "ECW Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title has Xavier Woods never won?",
"Answer": "WCW Cruiserweight Championship"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title hasn't Kalisto won?",
"Answer": "Universal Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which was NOT one of the three faces of Foley?",
"Answer": "The Animal"
},
{
"Question": "Which world title did Sgt. Slaughter win?",
"Answer": "WWE Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which WWE Hall of Famer is Natalya's father?",
"Answer": "Jim Neidhart"
},
{
"Question": "Which WWE Title did X-Pac never win?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who adopted the motto \"Show Up and Win\" in 2020?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who advanced to the finals of the 2021 Women's Dusty Classic?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "Who aligned himself with Titus O'Neil in the summer of 2017?",
"Answer": "Akira Tozawa"
},
{
"Question": "Who attacked Roman Reigns after his Universal Title match at Elimination Chamber 2021?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who attempted to cash in a Money in the Bank shot at TLC 2020?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Bret Hart at WrestleMania XII for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Charlotte in a Last Woman Standing match at WWE Evolution 2018?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Chyna in a September 2000 Title match?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Goldberg for the Universal Title at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Pete Dunne for the NXT UK Title in 2019?",
"Answer": "WALTER"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Randy Savage at WrestleMania 3?",
"Answer": "Ricky Steamboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Stone Cold Steve Austin in Austin's last match at WrestleMania XIX?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat the Miz for the WWE Title in 2011?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Undertaker in a Casket Match at the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who became 6-time SmackDown Tag Champs in April 2020?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a 10-time WWE Champion in October 2020?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a 2-time WWE Champion in November 2020?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a 3-time North American Champ at NXT War Games 2020?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Raw Tag Champion at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Tag Team Champion at the 1995 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "1-2-3 Kid"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Tag Team Champion at WrestleMania VIII?",
"Answer": "Earthquake"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Tag Team Champion at WrestleMania VIII?",
"Answer": "Typhoon"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Tag Team Champion at WrestleMania XI?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a WWE Tag Team Champion at SummerSlam 1990?",
"Answer": "Jim Neidhart"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a WWE Tag Team Champion at SummerSlam 1990?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who became an NXT Women's Tag Team Champion on March 10, 2021?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "Who became WWE Champion on January 23, 1984?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who began 2020 as Intercontinental Champion?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who began 2020 as Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "The Fiend"
},
{
"Question": "Who called himself \"The Hippest Cat in the World\"?",
"Answer": "Dude Love"
},
{
"Question": "Who calls herself a \"genetically superior athlete\"?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who captained the team Undertaker joined at Survivor Series 1990?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the ECW Title at WrestleMania XXIV?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Hardcore Title at WrestleMania X-Seven?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania V?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania V?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Raw Tag Team Titles at the 2018 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The Bar"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Raw Women's Title at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the SmackDown Tag Titles in January 2021?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler & Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the WWE Title at Survivor Series 1995?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged AJ Styles for the WWE Title at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Asuka for the Raw Women's Title at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Bret Hart for the WWE Title at Survivor Series 1992?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Bret Hart for the WWE Title at the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Drew McIntyre for the WWE Title at the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Hulk Hogan for the WWE Title at WrestleMania III?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Kofi Kingston for the WWE Title at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Randy Savage for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 1992?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Roman Reigns for the Universal Title at the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Ronda Rousey for the Raw Women's Title at Evolution 2018?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Sasha Banks for the SmackDown Women's Title at Royal Rumble 2021?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Sasha Banks for the SmackDown Women's Title at TLC 2020?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Ultimate Warrior for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 1990?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenges opponents to \"Get These Hands\"?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who claimed that \"Bret screwed Bret\"?",
"Answer": "Mr. McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who claims to be \"all heart, no soul\"?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who comes out ot the song \"Here Comes the Money\"?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in NXT WarGames matches every year from 2017-2020?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Cactus Jack in Hell in a Cell at No Way Out 2000?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Hulk Hogan in the Legend vs. Icon match at WrestleMania X8?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated JBL for the Intercontinental Title in less than 30 seconds at WrestleMania 25?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Randy Savage in a retirement match at WrestleMania VII?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Ric Flair in a \"Loser Leaves WWE\" match on Raw in 1993?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Sgt. Slaughter for the WWE Title at WrestleMania VII?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title against Daniel Bryan at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Universal Title against his own cousin in 2020?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at WrestleMania 32?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who describes himself as Limitless?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who did \"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt beat for the Universal Title in 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Adam Cole beat for his first NXT Title?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Adam Cole defeat in a Backlot Brawl at 2020's NXT Takeover: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Velveteen Dream"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Asuka last eliminate to win the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Baron Corbin beat to become King of the Ring?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Batista beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Batista last eliminate to win the 2005 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Batista last eliminate to win the 2014 Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bayley beat for her first Raw Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bayley beat for her first SmackDown Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Becky Lynch last eliminate to win the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Becky Lynch replace in the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Lana"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Beth Phoenix team with at WrestleMania 35 in a Tag Title match?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Big John Studd last eliminate to win the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Big Show defeat to win his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Big Show face in his WrestleMania debut at WrestleMania XV?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bobby Lashley beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bobby Lashley beat for the United States Title in May 2006?",
"Answer": "JBL"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Braun Strowman replace in the WrestleMania 36 Universal Title match?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Braun Strowman team with at the 1st Mixed Match Challenge?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bray Wyatt beat in the Firefly Funhouse match at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bray Wyatt defeat in a House of Horrors Match at Payback 2017?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bret Hart beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bret Hart beat in the finals of the 1993 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bret Hart defeat to win his last United States Title?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bret Hart team with to win a WCW Tag Team title?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Cesaro win a SmackDown Tag Title with in 2020?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Cesaro win the SmackDown tag Titles with in 2020?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Charlotte Flair beat for her first Divas Title?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Charlotte Flair beat for her first SmackDown Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Charlotte team with to win her first Women's Tag Team Title?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Diesel defeat to win his first Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Dolph Ziggler beat for the Intercontinental Title at SummerSlam 2024?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Drew McIntyre defeat to become NXT Champion?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Drew McIntyre last eliminate to win the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Edge beat at WrestleMania 36 in his return match?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Edge beat in a Hardcore Match at WrestleMania 22?",
"Answer": "Mick Foley"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Edge beat in a Last Man Standing Match at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Elias defeat at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Goldberg beat to win the Universal Title in February 2020?",
"Answer": "The Fiend"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Goldberg dominate in a match at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Hulk Hogan beat to win the WWE Title at WrestleMania VII?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Hulk Hogan defeat to win his 1st WWE Championship?",
"Answer": "Iron Sheik"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Hulk Hogan last eliminate to win the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Hulk Hogan last eliminate to win the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Earthquake"
},
{
"Question": "Who did JBL beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Jeff Hardy beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Jeff Hardy beat to become Intercontinental Champ in April 2001?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Jey Uso shokcingly attack in October 2020 on SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did John Cena beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "JBL"
},
{
"Question": "Who did John Cena beat to win his first WWE Title at WrestleMania 21?",
"Answer": "JBL"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kane beat at Survivor Series 1997, his first WWE match?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kane beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Keith Lee beat for his first NXT Title?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who did King Booker beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kofi Kingston beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mankind beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mark Henry beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mickie James defeat for her first WWE Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mr. McMahon beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mr. McMahon beat to win the ECW World Title?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Natalya face in the first women's match in Saudi Arabia?",
"Answer": "Lacey Evans"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Nia Jax beat for her first Raw Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not challenge Bayley for the Raw Women's Title at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Brie Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not challenge Braun Strowman for the Intercontinental Title at Elimination Chamber 2020?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the first TLC Match?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not fight for the WWE Title in the Main Event of WrestleMania 2000?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not hold the Raw Women's Title in 2020?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not hold the SmackDown Tag Titles in 2020?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not participate in the first match in Survivor Series history?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not participate in the first match in Survivor Series history?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not win his first WWE Title at a WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Otis defeat at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Randy Orton last eliminate to win the 2009 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Randy Orton shockingly RKO in March 2020 before his WrestleMania march with Edge?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Randy Savage beat in the last match of WrestleMania IV?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Razor Ramon defeat in a Crybaby Match at In Your House 6 in February 1996?",
"Answer": "1-2-3 Kid"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Rey Mysterio beat to win the United States Title at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Rick Rude defeat in 1989 to win the Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ronda Rousey beat for her first Raw Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sasha Banks beat for her first Raw Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sasha Banks beat for her first SmackDown Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Seth Rollins last eliminate to win the 2019 men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shane McMahon defeat in a Steel Cage Match at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shane McMahon defeat in this WrestleMania debut at WrestleMania XV?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shane McMahon defeat to win the World Cup at 2018's Crown Jewel?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shawn Michaels beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shawn Michaels last eliminate to win the 1995 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Davey Boy Smith"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shawn Michaels last eliminate to win the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sheamus beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Stone Cold Steve Austin beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Stone Cold Steve Austin last eliminate to win the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Stone Cold Steve Austin last eliminate to win the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sycho Sid defeat for his first WWE Championship?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who did the Big Show defeat to win his first WCW Championship?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did The Fiend beat in a Strap Match at the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did The Rock defeat for his first Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did the Ultimate Warrior beat in a Super Posedown at the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "\"Ravishing\" Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Triple H kick out of Evolution after he won a Title?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Trish Stratus face at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ultimate Warrior beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker beat for the WWE Title at WrestleMania 13?",
"Answer": "Sycho Sid"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker beat in the Boneyard Match at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker beat in the Main Event of 2019's Super ShowDown?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker throw off the Hell in a Cell?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Velveteen Dream beat for the NXT North American Title?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who did X-Pac win Tag Titles with twice?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Yokozuna last eliminate to win the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't Bret Hart face in the 1993 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't compete in a Fatal 4 Way Match for the United States Title at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't Randy Savage face in the WrestleMania IV Tournament?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't win a WWE Title as a result of a tournament?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 11 men and finished as runner up in the 2001 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 13 men in 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 4 men from the 2021 Royal Rumble, tied for the most?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 8 consecutive Superstars in the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated AJ Styles from the 2016 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated the most competitors from the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sid Justice"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated the most people (5) from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended 1983 as the WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Iron Sheik"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended 2020 as Raw Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended 2020 as the SmackDown Tag Team Champions?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended 2020 as the Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended Diesel's lengthy WWE Title reign at Survivor Series 1995?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended Goldberg's undefeated streak?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended King Corbin's first reign as United States Champion?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble as an NXT representative?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered the men's and women's Royal Rumble matches on the same night?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered the ring to the song \"Burn it Down\"?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 35 as the Intercontinental Champion?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 35 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 36 as SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 36 as the Women's Tag Team Champions?",
"Answer": "The Kabuki Warriors"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania IX as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bret \"Hit Man\" Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania VII as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania VIII as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania XII as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bret \"Hit Man\" Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania XV as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced a professional boxer at WrestleMania XXIV?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Big John Studd in a Body Slam Challenge at WrestleMania I?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Bret Hart in an \"I Quit\" match at WrestleMania 13?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Undertaker in a Hell in a Cell Match at WrestleMania 32?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who finished opponents with The Banzai Drop?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with a Leg Drop?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Brogue Kick?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Hammerlock DDT?",
"Answer": "Andrade"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Pedigree?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Purple Rainmaker?",
"Answer": "Velveteen Dream"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Rear View?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Tombstone?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who forfeited the United States Title in December 2019?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who gave up the Raw Women's Title in 2020 due to pregnancy?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who goes by the nickname \"Prince Pretty\"?",
"Answer": "Tyler Breeze"
},
{
"Question": "Who got his head shaved due to a match at WrestleMania 23?",
"Answer": "Mr. McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who had the longest first reign as Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who had the longest Intercontinental Title reign of the 20th century?",
"Answer": "Honky Tonk Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who handed Mr. Perfect his 1st WWE loss at WrestleMania VI?",
"Answer": "Brutus Beefcake"
},
{
"Question": "Who has argued that Wrestlemania is actually KO-Mania?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been called The King of Flight?",
"Answer": "Kalisto"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been called the Ultimate Underdog?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been known as \"The New Face of Fear\"?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been known to kick opponents in the head?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who has called himself \"The Gold Standard\"?",
"Answer": "Shelton Benjamin"
},
{
"Question": "Who has competed in both a men's and women's Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who has competed in both a men's and women's Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who has competed in every Inferno Match to date through 2020?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who has White Noise as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who has won 3 Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who has won the Intercontinental Title 8 times?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't Shane McMahon faced in a WrestleMania match?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't the Miz won a Tag Team Title with?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't the Miz won aTag Team Title with?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't won the King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't won the King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "All have won"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the NXT UK Title for almost 2 years in 2017-2019?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "Who helped Roman Reigns defeat Drew McIntyre at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who helped Undertaker beat Hulk Hogan for the WWE Title at Survivor Series 1991?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who hosts the \"Ding, Dong Hello!\" Talk Show on SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who hosts the weekly WWE podcast \"Feel the Power\"?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Who in 1995 became the first man to win the Royal Rumble from #1?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who in 2006 famously signed \"the largest contract in SmackDown history?\"",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who in 2007/2008 held the United States Title for a then WWE-record 343 days?",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who in March 2021 was added to the Universal Title Match at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted \"Ravishing\" Rick Rude into the WWE Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Ricky Steamboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted Beth Phoenix into the 2017 WWE Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted Bret Hart into the WWE Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted opponents into his \"Hall of Pain\"?",
"Answer": "Mark Henry"
},
{
"Question": "Who insisted on being introduced as \"The Best in the World\" throughout 2018?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who interviews Raw Superstars on her Playground show?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who is billed as the World's Largest Athlete?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who is called \"The Baddest Woman on the Planet\"?",
"Answer": "Ronda Rousey"
},
{
"Question": "Who is fond of saying \"All Aboard\"?",
"Answer": "The Godfather"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as \"Little Miss Bliss\"?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as \"The Celtic Warrior\"?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as \"the dirtiest player in the game\"?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as \"The Phenom\"?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as \"The Showoff\"?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as the BruiserWeight?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as The Ultimate Opportunist?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known by the nickname \"The Queen of Hearts\"?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who is not considered one of the 4 Horsewomen?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who is NOT known for a devastating spear?",
"Answer": "Doink the Clown"
},
{
"Question": "Who is not related to The Rock?",
"Answer": "Ronda Rousey"
},
{
"Question": "Who is the 1st man to win the ECW, WCW, and WWE Titles?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who is Undertaker's brother?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who joined WWE with a motto of \"Ruthless Aggression\"?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who lasted more than 50 minutes in the first Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who lead a team of 3 knights against the Hart Family at Survivor Series 1993?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who leads a Faction known as The Way?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who left SummerSlam 2015 with both the WWE and United States Titles?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who liked to call himself \"The Bad Guy\"?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to call himself \"Phenomenal\"?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to say \"Have a Nice Day\"?",
"Answer": "Mick Foley"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to say Bay Bay?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the WWE title on SmackDown's 2019 20th Anniversary show?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who made a stunning return to WWE at the end of WrestleMania VII?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who made his in-ring return to WWE in the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who made his NXT debut at NXT's Takeover: Brooklyn III by attacking Drew McIntyre?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who made Raw's picks in the 2002 Draft?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who makes opponents submit to the Hurt Lock?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who makes WWE Champions?",
"Answer": "Scopely"
},
{
"Question": "Who nails opponents with a flying elbow off the top rope?",
"Answer": "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who nails opponents with the Twist of Fate?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who never won the WWE Title at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who never won the WWE Title at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who plays a trombone named Francesca?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who purchased the #30 slot for the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who represented SmackDown in the Champion vs Champion match at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who returned to Smackdown in November 2020 by attacking Sasha Banks?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who returned to WWE and won the 2014 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who says \"Who's Next?\"?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who served as host of WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who shockingly betrayed Otis after he won the Money in the Bank?",
"Answer": "Tucker"
},
{
"Question": "Who spookily says \"Let Me In\"?",
"Answer": "The Fiend"
},
{
"Question": "Who started relying on a band of ninjas to help him compete in 2020?",
"Answer": "Akira Tozawa"
},
{
"Question": "Who started showing an odd connection to The Fiend in 2020?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who started using the mantra Untouchable in late 2020?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who stunningly lost the 24/7 Title during the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who submits opponents with the Cloverleaf?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who submits opponents with the Hell's Gate?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania IV?",
"Answer": "Honky Tonk Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania IX?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania X?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the NXT Title at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Raw Tag Team Titles at Elimination Chamber 2020?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Raw Tag Titles at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Raw Women's Title at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Universal Title in a 2-on-1 Handicap Match at Backlash 2020?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the WWE Title at WrestleMania XI?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "Who surprisingly challenged Randy Orton at WWE Fastlane 2021?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Diesel to form Two Dudes with Attitudes",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Lex Luger to form the Allied Powers tag team?",
"Answer": "Davey Boy Smith"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with R-Truth to form the Fabulous Truth in the second Mixed Match Challenge?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Randy Savage at Survivor Series 1992?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Ric Flair at Survivor Series 1992?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Sasha Banks in the first Mixed Match Challenge?",
"Answer": "Finn Bálor"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with The Rock at WrestleMania XX?",
"Answer": "Mick Foley"
},
{
"Question": "Who threatened to \"Stomp a mudhole\" in opponents?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who took Shane McMahon's place in his Fastlane 2021 Match with Braun Strowman?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who unsuccessfully cashed in a Money in the Bank Title shot at WWE TLC 2020?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who unsuccessfully challenged for the WWE Title at Super Show 2020?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who unsuccessfully challenged Roman Reigns for the Universal Title at Elimination Chamber 2021?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who unsuccessfully challenged Triple H for the World Heavyweight Title at Wrestlemania XIX?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who unsuccessfully challenged Yokozuna for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 1993?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who used the Stump Puller as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Doink the Clown"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses her Manhandle Slam as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses Paydirt as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Shelton Benjamin"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses Stone Cold's Stunner as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Big Bang Catastrophe as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Compactor as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Tucker"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Coquina Clutch as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Fairytale Ending as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Killswitch as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Christian"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Last Shot as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Lie Detector as a signature move?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Playmaker as a signature move?",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Spirit Bomb as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the T-Bone Suplex as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Shelton Benjamin"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Three Amigos as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Uranage as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who viciously attacked her former best friend in the summer of 2020?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a Golf Caddy early in his WWE Career?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of the 4 Horsemen?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of the Million Dollar Team at Survivor Series 1994?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a Tag Team Champion heading into WrestleMania 29?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was an early member of D-Generation X?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Asuka's surprise tag-team partner at WWE TLC 2020?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was awarded the WWE Title, lost it, then won it back in one night at No Mercy 2007?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who was better known as The British Bulldog?",
"Answer": "Davey Boy Smith"
},
{
"Question": "Who was briefly an honorary member of the New Day?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who was briefly co-owner of WWE with Mr. McMahon in late 2001?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Davey Boy Smith's brother-in-law?",
"Answer": "Bret \"Hit Man\" Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who was forced to defend the WWE Title twice at Wrestlemania X?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who was guest referee when Daniel Bryan won the WWE Title at SummerSlam 2013?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Hulk Hogan's partner when he won the Tag Titles in 2002?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in Triple H's corner at WrestleMania 2000?",
"Answer": "Stephanie McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who was initially the manager of the Kabuki Warriors?",
"Answer": "Paige"
},
{
"Question": "Who was John Cena's partner when he won his 1st Tag Team Title?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who was known for often uttering the word \"DAMN!\"?",
"Answer": "Faarooq"
},
{
"Question": "Who was last eliminated from the WWE Title Match at WrestleMania 2000?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Mickie James' partner in season 2 of Mixed Match Challenge?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was named SmackDown General Manager in 2016?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was never a member of The Authority?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was never a member of The Authority?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who was never a member of The Authority?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who was nicknamed \"The Excellence of Execution\"?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who was nicknamed The Cerebral Assassin?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who was nicknamed The Irish Lass Kicker?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the 1997 Hart Foundation faction?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the Nation of Domination?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the original Hurt Business?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a Raw Tag Team Champion in 2020?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a Raw Tag Team Champion in 2020?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not an original member of D-Generation X?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the NXT Four Horsewomen?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not involved in the WrestleMania 33 Mixed Tag Match?",
"Answer": "Brie Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on Raw's 2020 Survivor Series team?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who was often called the \"Italian Strongman\"?",
"Answer": "Bruno Sammartino"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Randy Orton's partner in Rated RKO?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Raw's first pick in the 2002 Draft?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who was runner up to Asuka in the first Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who was SmackDown's first pick in the 2002 Draft?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who was SmackDown's first pick in the 2019 Draft?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Special Guest Enforcer for the Universal Title Match at Fastlane 2021?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who was special referee for Hulk Hogan's SummerSlam 1991 match?",
"Answer": "Sid Justice"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the 1st 2-time European Champion?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the 1st winner of the Vincent J. McMahon Legacy of Excellence?",
"Answer": "Stephanie McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the 24/7 Champion entering WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Constable of Raw in 2018?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 10-time WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 2-time WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bruno Sammartino"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 3-time WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 4-time World Heavyweight Champion?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 5-time Raw Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 5-time SmackDown Women's champion?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 7-time World Heavyweight Champion?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first entrant in the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first entry in the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first entry in the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first European Champion in WWE history?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first female Intercontinental Champion?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to be World Heavyweight champ 7 times?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to hold the United States Title 5 times?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first NXT Champion?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first NXT Superstar taken in the 2016 Brand Extension Draft?",
"Answer": "Finn Bálor"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first NXT Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Paige"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first of these SmackDown Superstars to be Universal Champion",
"Answer": "\"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to beat R-Truth for the 24/7 Title?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to cash in Money in the Bank on the same day he won it?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to defend the WWE Title successfully at a WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win 10 Women's Titles?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win the Intercontinental Title at a WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Ricky Steamboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win the WWE Title at a SummerSlam?",
"Answer": "Bret \"Hit Man\" Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win the WWE Title at a WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win the WWE Title in a TLC Match?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win the WWE Title on SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Mr. McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Tag Team to defend their Titles in a Hell in a Cell match?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first to win the SmackDown Tag Titles with 2 different partners?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Triple Crown champion in NXT?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Triple Crown champion in NXT?",
"Answer": "None of these"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Finn Bálor"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman picked in the 2016 Draft?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Woman selected by SmackDown in the 2019 Draft?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to have a Raw Women's Title reign longer than 200 days?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to have a Raw Women's Title reign longer than a year?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to hold the Tag Team Titles with 2 different partners?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Woman to win both the Raw and SmackDown Women's Titles?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to win the Divas, NXT, Raw, and SmackDown Women's Titles?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the guest referee for Bret Hart's WrestleMania X victory?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the last entry in the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the last Light Heavyweight Champion in WWE History?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the last pick of the 2016 Draft?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the longtime host of \"The VIP Lounge?\"",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Raw Women's Champion entering WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the runner up in consecutive Royal Rumble matches (2008-2009)?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the first main event in Survivor Series history?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the men's elimination match at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee when Shane and Vince McMahon fought at WrestleMania X-Seven?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Undertaker's opponent at SummerSlam 1994?",
"Answer": "An imposter Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who was United States Champion first?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who was United States Champion first?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who was unsuccessful cashing in his Money in the Bank shot?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who wasn't WCW Champion at least 5 times?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who went by the nickname \"Big Daddy Cool\"?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "Who went by the nickname Beastslayer?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who went by the nickname Kingslayer?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who were the first WWE Women's Tag Champions?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks and Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who win the United States Title at WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won 2 matches at WrestleMania XXX?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won 2019's Elimination Chamber Match for the WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a January 2018 tournament for the vacant United States Title?",
"Answer": "Bobby Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Ladder Match at SummerSlam 1995?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Ladder Match at WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a match to earn the #30 Entry spot for the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a mixed tag team match at WrestleMania VI?",
"Answer": "Dusty Rhodes"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Nightstick on a Pole Match at Survivor Series 1992?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Tag Team Title in 2002 as a member of the Un-Americans?",
"Answer": "Christian"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a tournament on the July 25, 2011 Raw to become WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Triple Threat Match for the World Heavyweight Title at WrestleMania 22?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an 8-way Elimination match for the United States Title on a July 2004 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an April 1990 tournament to become Intercontinental champion?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who won and lost the 24/7 Title dozens of times in 2020?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who won and lost the WWE Title in 1 day at Money in the Bank 2016?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who won and lost the WWE Title in 1 day at Survivor Series 2015?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his 5th Intercontinental Title in August 2020?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title at Elimination Chamber 2019?",
"Answer": "Finn Bálor"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title at Night of Champions 2015?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania XXVIII?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title in June 2000?",
"Answer": "Rikishi"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title in November 2017?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first United States Title at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first WCW Title in the first World War 3 Match?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first WWE Title at Armageddon 2008?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first WWE Title at Survivor Series 2015?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his only Intercontinental Title in April 1999?",
"Answer": "The Godfather"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his only WWE Title at the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his only WWE Title on December 26, 1983?",
"Answer": "Iron Sheik"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the #30 entrance to the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 1989 Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Big John Studd"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 1991 Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2016 Andre the Giant Memorial Battle Royal?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2017 Men's Money in the Bank match?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2020 Women's Money in the Bank match?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2021 Raw Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Battle Royal at WrestleMania II?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the ECW Title in the Extreme Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Elimination Chamber match?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Hell in a Cell match?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Hollywood Backlot Brawl at Wrestlemania XII?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Inferno match at WWE TLC 2020?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at each of the first 2 SummerSlams?",
"Answer": "The Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at the first SummerSlam?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title in a Ladder match at Clash of Champions 2020?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Jailhouse Match at SummerSlam 1991?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Main Event of WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title at 2020's the Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title at the first NXT Takeover: Wargames in 2017?",
"Answer": "Andrade"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title in Japan in December 2016?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title in Japan in July 2015?",
"Answer": "Finn Bálor"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Women's Title after Asuka vacated in 2017?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Women's Title 3 times in 2019?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Tuwaiq Mountain Trophy Gauntlet Match at Super Show 2020?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title 3 times in 2017?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at the 2016 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Kalisto"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Universal Title at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the vacant NXT Title at 2019's NXT Takeover: New York?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the vacant NXT Title at 2019's NXT Takeover: New York?",
"Answer": "None of these"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WCW Title on the last-ever episode of Nitro, March 26, 2001?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Women's Battle Royal at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Women's Title at the first WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Wendi Richter"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Title in a tribute to Eddie Guerrero at WrestleMania 22?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WrestleMania II Battle Royal featuring football players and WWE Superstars?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at both WrestleMania XIV and XV?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at the 1993 King of the Ring event?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at This Tuesday in Texas?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at WrestleMania VI?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title in a First Blood match?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title in England in November 2017?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who won WrestleMania 35's Andre the GIant Memorial Battle Royal?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who worked as a Commentator for NXT TV in 2020?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who would have been forced to retire if he lost at WrestleMania 29?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who would hit his opponents with the Swanton Bomb?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who, in 2016, was the first Superstar to represent NXT in a Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who, in 2020, was the first woman to defend a Title in Saudi Arabia?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who's first United States Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Andrade"
},
{
"Question": "Who's first United States Title reign was the shortest?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who's first Univeral Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who's had the most WWE Title reigns after John Cena? (As of 2020)",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who's known for the Figure 4 leglock?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who's nickname was \"The Snake\"?",
"Answer": "Jake Roberts"
},
{
"Question": "Who's theme music started with \"You think you know me\"",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Whose 1st Smackdown Women's Title reign was the shortest?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Whose 2020 Universal Title reign only lasted a week?",
"Answer": "The Fiend"
},
{
"Question": "Whose entrance music begins with the sound of glass breaking?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Whose entrance music proclaims that he hears voices in his head?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Whose first NXT Title reign was the shortest?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Whose injury prevented him from fighting for the Intercontinental Title at SummerSlam 1988?",
"Answer": "Brutus \"the Barber\" Beefcake"
},
{
"Question": "Whose match speciality was the Boot Camp match?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "Whose nickname is \"The Nightmare\"?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Whose nickname is \"The World's Strongest Man\"?",
"Answer": "Mark Henry"
},
{
"Question": "Whose nickname was \"Hot Rod\"?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Whose nickname was \"The Hit Man\"?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is known as Sweet Chin Music?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is known as The Write-Off?",
"Answer": "Irwin R. Schyster"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is the Cobra Clutch?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is the InSane Elbow?",
"Answer": "Kairi Sane"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is the Last Dance?",
"Answer": "Fandango"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is the Milllion Dollar Dream?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is the World's Strongest Slam?",
"Answer": "Mark Henry"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move was the Last Dance?",
"Answer": "Fandango"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move was the Mandible Claw?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move was the Rude Awakening?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Whose WrestleMania 29 debut led to a viral dance craze?",
"Answer": "Fandango"
},
{
"Question": "With what legend did Batista win a tag team championship?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "With what legend did Ric Flair win a Tag Team title at Cyber Sunday 2006?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "With what partner did Shane McMahon win Tag Titles with in January 2019?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "With what Superstar did Batista win the WWE Tag Title?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "With what Superstar did Kane once win the WCW Tag Titles?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "With what Superstar did Ken Shamrock win a Tag Team Title?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "With which Superstar did Braun Strowman win a Tag Team Title?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar beat Kevin Owens for the NXT Title?",
"Answer": "Finn Bálor"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mr. McMahon face in an \"I Quit\" match at No Mercy 2003?",
"Answer": "Stephanie McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "What class is Andre the Giant \"Eighth Wonder of the World\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the runner up in the Royal Rumble 4 times between 2014 and 2020?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 5-time WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Andrade beat for the NXT Title?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mr. McMahon last eliminate to win the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Faarooq from?",
"Answer": "Georgia"
},
{
"Question": "At what 1989 event did Rick Rude win the Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Wrestlemania V"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Women's Title at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first active performer inducted in the Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with The Iron Sheik to win the tag Titles at the 1st WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Nikolai Volkoff"
},
{
"Question": "What longtime rival did Stone Cold face 3 times at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sgt. Slaughter beat to win the WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Elias from?",
"Answer": "Pennsylvania"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Hulk Hogan's partner in the Mega Powers?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who goes by the nickname Ravishing?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat \"Rowdy\" Roddy Piper for the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania VIII?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "At what August 2020 event did \"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt win his 2nd WWE Title?",
"Answer": "SummerSlam"
},
{
"Question": "What type of animal is a nickname for The Rock?",
"Answer": "Bull"
},
{
"Question": "Whose first NXT Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who is NOT a user of the Figure 4 Leglock?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who used the Whoopie Cushion as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Doink the Clown"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar claimed to be from Jamaica when he debuted in WWE?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Championship at WrestleMania 36 in 2020?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Shawn Michaels from?",
"Answer": "Texas"
},
{
"Question": "Who raps his own entrance music \"The Time Is Now\"?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to exclaim \"Yowie Wowie!\"?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "What city played host to Wrestlemania 37?",
"Answer": "Tampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sycho Sid beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is known as The Glamazon?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of the Ultimate Warriors team at 1989's Survivor Series?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did Shelton Benjamin win at least 3 times in 2020?",
"Answer": "24/7 titles"
},
{
"Question": "How many reigns did JBL have as Hardcore Champion?",
"Answer": 17
},
{
"Question": "Whose only United States Title reign lasted longer than a year?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as \"Mr. WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who left WrestleMania 36 as NXT Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a tournament for the revived United States Title at Vengeance 2003?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Battle Royal at 2018's Women's Evolution event?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who did JBL defeat to win his first WWE Title in 2004?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Which is not one of the traits John Cena lives by?",
"Answer": "Dishonesty"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Big E beat to win his first NXT Title?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ted DiBiase buy the WWE Title from?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Superstar twice won the WCW Title in 2001?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 33 as Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "What state is Adam Cole from?",
"Answer": "Florida"
},
{
"Question": "Who has called himself the Lone Wolf?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "In the game, What's the nickname for Alexa Bliss's acrobat class character?",
"Answer": "Little Miss Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who fires up the crowd by yelling \"Woooo!\"?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did The Rock defeat for each of his first 3 WWE Titles?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "What are Edge's fans known as?",
"Answer": "Edgeheads"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended Finn Bálor's Intercontinental Title reign at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title on October 12, 1992 in Saskatoon, Canada?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his 2nd United States Title in January 2019, almost 9 years after his first?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who was WWE Champion entering WrestleMania XXX?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Irish Curse Backbreaker as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "What team was the first to win the SmackDown Tag Titles 3 times?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "What faction did Naomi join during the Women's Evolution?",
"Answer": "Team B.A.D"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Christian from?",
"Answer": "Toronto"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did Mr. McMahon win in April 2007?",
"Answer": "ECW Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who is Asuka's partner in the Kabuki Warriors?",
"Answer": "Kairi Sane"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to win the United States Title at a WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Becky Lynch beat for her first Raw Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Ronda Rousey"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 10 men from the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was a member of Heavy Machinery?",
"Answer": "Otis"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was a member of Heavy Machinery?",
"Answer": "Tucker"
},
{
"Question": "What faction did Nikolai Volkoff join?",
"Answer": "The Million Dollar Corporation"
},
{
"Question": "Who made a shocking return at WWE Fastlane 2021?",
"Answer": "\"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Who is nicknamed the Shenom?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar dramatically returned to the 2020 Royal Rumble after an almost 10-year absence?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Jinder Mahal beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar has faced Undertaker 3 times at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Cesaro win tag Titles with 5 times?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who spent much of 2019 challenging rivals to \"knock on his door\"?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar made an inspirational comeback from Leukemia in 2019?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars never won the NXT Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "In the game, what color is the ACROBAT class?",
"Answer": "Blue"
},
{
"Question": "What weapon did Big Boss Man like to bring to the ring?",
"Answer": "Nightstick"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did Lex Luger never win?",
"Answer": "WWE Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known to drop the Ballin' Elbow?",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 7 consecutive men from the 1994 Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "Who was WWE Universal Champion entering WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar started out as a member of the Nexus?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Booker T defeat to win his first WWE World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who was guest referee when Bret Hart won the WWE Title at SummerSlam 1997?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Triple H beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Where was Wendi Richter from?",
"Answer": "Dallas"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "In what WCW event did Hulk Hogan and Ultimate Warrior have their rematch?",
"Answer": "Halloween Havoc"
},
{
"Question": "Who nicknamed the NXT Championship \"Goldie\"?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "How many times has Kane been a Tag Team Champion?",
"Answer": 11
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the NXT North American Title at Wargames 2020?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Goldberg beat for his first WCW Title?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "What faction did Undertaker form?",
"Answer": "The Ministry of Darkness"
},
{
"Question": "The \"Unholy Alliance\" was a pairing of Undertaker and what man?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who served as host of WrestleMania XXVII?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Gimmick Battle Royal at WrestleMania X-Seven?",
"Answer": "Iron Sheik"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as The Pirate Princess?",
"Answer": "Kairi Sane"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to win 2 Money in the Bank Matches?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Alexa Bliss beat for her first SmackDown's Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar ended Drew McIntyre's WWE Title reign at Hell in a Cell 2020?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar has called himself \"The Architect\"?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted Ric Flair into the Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is \"The Monster Among Men\"?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Where was Andre the Giant from?",
"Answer": "France"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first singles Title Braun Strowman won in WWE?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Hulk Hogan to form the Mega-Maniacs?",
"Answer": "Brutus Beefcake"
},
{
"Question": "Who wasn't Universal Champion in 2020?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2020, what Superstar has won the most TLC matches?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Sgt. Slaughter's team at Survivor Series 1990?",
"Answer": "The Mercenaries"
},
{
"Question": "From what state does Bobby Lashley hail?",
"Answer": "Colorado"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been known as the Chief Hurt Officer of the Hurt Business?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "What authority figure did Kevin Owens have a rivalry with?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "What Intercontinental Champ did Triple H beat in a Title unification match at No Mercy 2002?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of the NWO's Pay-Per-View?",
"Answer": "Souled Out"
},
{
"Question": "What class is Aleister Black \"NXT\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an \"I Quit\" Match at WrestleMania XI?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move has the word 'Train' in it?",
"Answer": "The Godfather"
},
{
"Question": "What legend was advising Lacey Evans in January 2021?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did The Rock face at WrestleManias 28 and 29?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Sheamus's hometown?",
"Answer": "Dublin"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars won the Universal Title twice in 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who used \"Pomp and Circumstances\" as his entrance music?",
"Answer": "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who did the Miz beat in July 2012 to win his first Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Christian"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Cup at WWE Crown Jewel 2018?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Women's Money in the Bank match?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Rhea Ripley face at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Superstar married Beth Phoenix?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat The Rock for the WWE Title in an Empty Arena match?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who surprisingly beat X-Pac for the European Championship?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who is nicknamed \"The Devil's Favorite Demon\"?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at WrestleMania 32?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Edge beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Whose entrance music has the phrase \"Self High Five\" in it?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "What male Superstar lost in the finals of the second Mixed Match Challenge?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar did not hold the Intercontinental Title at least 5 times as of November 2020?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was George \"The Animal\" Steele in at the end of his career?",
"Answer": "The Oddities"
},
{
"Question": "Who is the Modern-Day Maharaja?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first title MVP won in his WWE Career?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Women's Title at WrestleMania X-7?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Women's Title at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ric Flair never beat for the WCW Championship?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of Team PCB?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of Team PCB?",
"Answer": "Brie Bella"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was formed in 2008 to aid Edge in his championship goals?",
"Answer": "La Familia"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar refers to himself as \"The All Mighty\"?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team did D-Generation X defeat in the Main Event of 2018's Crown Jewel?",
"Answer": "The Brothers of Destruction"
},
{
"Question": "Which man has never won the Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on Hulk Hogan's team at the first Survivor Series?",
"Answer": "Paul Orndorff"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on Hulk Hogan's team at the first Survivor Series?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on Hulk Hogan's team at the first Survivor Series?",
"Answer": "None of them"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Intercontinental Champion heading into WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "Wade Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "What submission move does the Fiend like using?",
"Answer": "Mandible Claw"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the first Money in the Bank match at WrestleMania 21?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Unforgiven 2007?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "What was Diesel's signature move?",
"Answer": "Jacknife Powerbomb"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the Intercontinental Title the longest in 2020?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Money in the Bank contract at Hell in a Cell 2020?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Becky Lynch for the Raw Women's Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who took on Goldberg at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Gorilla Press as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was called a \"B+ Player\" by the McMahons?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did King Corbin last eliminate to win the Andre the Giant Battle Royal at WrestleMania 32?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Rack Attack?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Akira Tozawa won the 24/7 Title 3 times in 2020 on what show?",
"Answer": "Raw"
},
{
"Question": "Who did DDP beat to first win the WCW Title?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the WWE title on the March 1, 2021 episode of Raw?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar released an Extended Play music album in October 2020?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to be unsuccessful in cashing in a Money in The Bank contract?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Championship at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Mr. McMahon at WrestleMania 22?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to hold the NXT Title more than a year?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Naomi from?",
"Answer": "Orlando"
},
{
"Question": "Who takes out opponents with the RKO?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What was the Sasha Banks/Bayley team first called?",
"Answer": "The Boss 'n' Hug Connection"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Robert Roode from?",
"Answer": "Canada"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not an Intercontinental Champion in 2020?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the Universal Title at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in an official match at Vengeance 2006?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who shared \"Tales of the Dark Father\" on an April 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first United States Title at SummerSlam 2012?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Carmella beat for her first SmackDown Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a 16-man tournament for the WWE Title at WrestleMania IV?",
"Answer": "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Team Champion at the 2019 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2020, what Superstar competed in the most Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Icon vs. Icon match at WrestleMania X8?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title in a Steel Cage at WrestleMania II?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar married Stephanie McMahon?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Lacey Evans"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Women's Tag Titles at Fastlane 2021?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Undertaker in a Buried Alive Match at Survivor Series 2003?",
"Answer": "Mr.McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who is not originally from Canada?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to hold the NXT Title for more than 500 total days?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "At what WWE event did Undertaker debut?",
"Answer": "Survivor Series"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Women'a Battle Royal at SummerSlam 2007?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shinsuke Nakamura last eliminate to win the 2018 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the self-proclaimed captain of Team Raw at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Ricochet to win the 2019 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team classic?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title at 2017's NXT Takeover: WarGames?",
"Answer": "Andrade"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the vacant United States Title on SmackDown in January 2018?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 32 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first United States Title at Capitol Punishment 2011?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in the Women's Elimination Chamber Match at Elimination Chamber 2020?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in the Women's Elimination Chamber Match at Elimination Chamber 2020?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is Drift Away?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who was suspended for her actions on the April 19th, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Edge beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at The Horror Show at Extreme Rules?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Seth Rollins for the Universal Title at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title won in WWE by Daniel Bryan?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who cashed in Money in the Bank and won the WWE Title at Elimination Chamber 2021?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2020, which woman hadn't won the Raw, SmackDown, and Tag Team Titles?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Rey Mysterio last eliminate to win the 2006 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar debuted as a member of the Viking Raiders?",
"Answer": "Ivar"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar debuted as a member of the Viking Raiders?",
"Answer": "Erik"
},
{
"Question": "Which WWE Title did Batista not win?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Alexa Bliss beat at Fastlane 2021?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who left WrestleMania 37 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Natalya beat for her first SmackDown Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "What sport did Goldberg play professionally before joining WCW?",
"Answer": "Football"
},
{
"Question": "Who's first Raw Women's Title reign was the shortest?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "At what event did the Gobbledy Gooker debut?",
"Answer": "Survivor Series"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Women's Title at No Mercy 2007?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was Edge a member of when he joined WWE?",
"Answer": "The Brood"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Daniel Bryan at Hell in a Cell 2019?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "What is George Steele's nickname?",
"Answer": "The Animal"
},
{
"Question": "Who hosts the Firefly Funhouse?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Kane recently became a mayor of Knox County in what state?",
"Answer": "Tennessee"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Adam Cole in a winner take all match for 2 NXT Titles?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Aleister Black from?",
"Answer": "Amsterdam"
},
{
"Question": "In what state is Triple H based?",
"Answer": "Connecticut"
},
{
"Question": "Who set a record by lasting more than 56 minutes in the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who has held the WWE Title 13 times?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Roman Reigns face at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a surprise entrant in the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Andre the Giant at WrestleMania V by DQ?",
"Answer": "Jake Roberts"
},
{
"Question": "Who claims to be the \"most must see\" champ in history?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Intercontinental Title at Fastlane 2021?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "In the game, what color is the SHOWBOAT class?",
"Answer": "Yellow"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a Hell in a Cell match to Undertaker at WrestleMania XV?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Seth Rollins for the Universal Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced a sumo wrestler at WrestleMania XXI?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Naomi beat for her first SmackDown Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who has Dolph Ziggler won the Raw and SmackDown Tag Titles with?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is known as The King of Kings?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the United States Title at SummerSlam 2020?",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who did The Rock last eliminate to win the 2000 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged JBL for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 2004?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who did fans select to face World Heavyweight Champ Triple H at the first Taboo Tuesday?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a match WrestleMania 23?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashey"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Hulk Hogan at the first SummerSlam?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "What is a signature move of the Viking Raiders?",
"Answer": "The Viking Experience"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Hulk Hogan beat for his first WCW Title?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Seth Rollins defeat in an Eye for an Eye Match in July 2020?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the World Heavyweight Title at Survivor Series 2006?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Randy Orton for the Intercontinental Title at Vengeance 2004?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the WWE Women's Tag Titles with two different partners in 2020?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who hosted his own award show on a December 2020 episode of SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who nails opponents with the Spirit Bomb?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Braun Strowman in the second Mixed Match Challenge?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended 2020 as NXT Champion?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Goldberg's hometown?",
"Answer": "Atlanta"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Hip Attack as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Hall of Famer is the Usos father?",
"Answer": "Rikishi"
},
{
"Question": "Who takes out opponents with his Superman punch?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker last eliminate to win the 2007 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who's first WWE Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 24/7 Title at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Akira Tozawa"
},
{
"Question": "What city hosted WrestleMania XXIV and 33?",
"Answer": "Orlando"
},
{
"Question": "Who hosted the 2020 WWE Hall of Fame ceremony?",
"Answer": "Jerry \"The King\" Lawler"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at WrestleMania X-Seven?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "What city is R-Truth's hometown?",
"Answer": "Charlotte"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Wade Barrett beat for his first Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Tag Team Titles at SummerSlam 2020?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Bray Wyatt for the WWE Title at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Light Heavyweight Title in October 1998?",
"Answer": "Christian"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the SmackDown Women's Title the longest in 2020?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "At WrestleMania, a battle royal winner gets a trophy modeled after what legend?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the WWE Title the longest in 2020?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "What is The Rock's actual name?",
"Answer": "Dwayne Johnson"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the WWE Title at WrestleMania VIII?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't Stone Cold Steve Austin win a Tag Title with?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Women's Title at WrestleMania XIX?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated AJ Styles for the WWE Championship at the 2017 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was Road Dogg a member of?",
"Answer": "D-Generation X"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with Chaos Theory?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Whose spot did Becky Lynch take to enter the 2019 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Lana"
},
{
"Question": "What is Adam Cole's NXT faction?",
"Answer": "The Undisputed Era"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Asuka beat for the NXT Women's Title in 2016?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Which is not a nickname of Undertaker?",
"Answer": "The Grim Reaper"
},
{
"Question": "Who would check opponents into The SmackDown Hotel?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Randy Orton in an Ambulance Match in September 2020?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker beat in a Casket Match at WrestleMania 22?",
"Answer": "Mark Henry"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Booker T beat in the King of the Ring final at Judgment Day 2006?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Tag Team Titles at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who recruited SmackDown Superstars to join his Alpha Academy in November 2020?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "What does nWo stand for?",
"Answer": "New World Order"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first WWE Title at the 2004 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "JBL"
},
{
"Question": "What team was not in the SmackDown Tag Team Elimination Match at Elimination Chamber 2020?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the Bad Guys team at Survivor Series 1994?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the Bad Guys team at Survivor Series 1994?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 29 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kevin Nash beat for his first WCW Title?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Hulk Hogan at SummerSlam 2005?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "The Bella Twins grew up in what state?",
"Answer": "Arizona"
},
{
"Question": "What move does Natalya use to submit opponents?",
"Answer": "Sharpshooter"
},
{
"Question": "What is Goldberg's first name?",
"Answer": "Bill"
},
{
"Question": "What move does Batista use to finish off opponents?",
"Answer": "Batista Bomb"
},
{
"Question": "Who won two Royal Rumble matches 9 years apart?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did \"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt defend the Universal Title at the 2021 Royal Rumbe?",
"Answer": "Strap Match"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Xavier Woods from?",
"Answer": "Atlanta"
},
{
"Question": "Who became WWE Champion on the March 1, 2021 episode of Raw?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not involved in the Main Event of WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Alexa Bliss beat for her first Raw Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Bray Wyatt in the Wyatt Swamp Fight at The Horror Show at Extreme Rules?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2020 Men's Money in the Bank Match?",
"Answer": "Otis"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Legend defended the Tag Team Titles at WrestleMania VI?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Ember Moon from?",
"Answer": "Texas"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of Team Flair at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "What state is Jeff Hardy from?",
"Answer": "North Carolina"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 8-time WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What was the tag team Greg \"The Hammer\" Valentine formed with Honky Tonk Man?",
"Answer": "Rhythm and Blues"
},
{
"Question": "Who wasn't Intercontinental Champion at least 5 times?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Edge last eliminate to win the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Universal Title at Payback 2020?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not inducted into the Hall of Fame as part of the nWo?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Tag Titles at 2020's Horror Show at Extreme Rules?",
"Answer": "Cesaro & Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Bobby Lashley at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended Bayley's lengthy SmackDown women's Title reign at Hell in a Cell 2020?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who was never a member of the NWO?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was never a member of the NWO?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 6-time WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Where do the Usos like to send their opponents?",
"Answer": "The Uso Penitentiary"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Bret Hart in a Kiss My Foot Match at the 1995 King of the Ring?",
"Answer": "Jerry Lawler"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Jeff Hardy beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Roman Reigns joined WWE as a member of what group?",
"Answer": "The Shield"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the special referee for Andre the Giant's match at WrestleMania V?",
"Answer": "Big John Studd"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Bayley for the SmackDown Women's Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered the WWE Hall of Fame in 2021?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered the WWE Hall of Fame in 2021?",
"Answer": "Davey Boy Smith"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Bobby Lashley at Backlash 2007?",
"Answer": "Mr.McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Title at 2021's Takleover: Stand and Deliver?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "On whom did Edge cash his first Money in the Bank in 2006?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar is Jimmy Uso's cousin?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Daniel Bryan's 'Pro' coach on the 1st season of NXT?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Elimination Chamber Match at SummerSlam 2003?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to win the Raw Women's Title 5 Times?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Armageddon 2007?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Whose stunning return saved Hulk Hogan at the end of WrestleMania VIII?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Shane McMahon in a Falls Count Anywhere Match at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Women's Title after Asuka vacated it?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "Which woman did not win one of the first 3 Women's Royal Rumbles?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Through December 2020, which Superstar had won a King of the Ring, Royal Rumble, and Money in the Bank?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Drew McIntyre beat in a No Holds Barred Match at Fastlane 2021?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Bray Wyatt in the WrestleMania Firefly Fun House match?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania XXX as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What pair captured the Raw Tag Titles in October 2019?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend was also a High School teacher while wrestling?",
"Answer": "George Steele"
},
{
"Question": "Who left WrestleMania 37 as Raw Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title changed hands at WWE TLC 2020?",
"Answer": "Raw Tag Titles"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the WWE Title at Elimination Chamber 2019?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Stone Cold Steve Austin from?",
"Answer": "Texas"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Vengeance 2006?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Which was NOT a group led by Triple H?",
"Answer": "The Nexus"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2020, Andrade had won which Title?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "Which is a signature Jerry Lawler move?",
"Answer": "Piledriver"
},
{
"Question": "Which group was X-Pac not a member of?",
"Answer": "The Nexus"
},
{
"Question": "Finish the phrase: \"If you smell what The Rock is...\"",
"Answer": "cooking"
},
{
"Question": "Where was Diamond Dallas Page from?",
"Answer": "New Jersey"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated AJ Styles at Elimination Chamber 2020?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Money in the Bank 2020?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 36 as NXT Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend became GM of Raw in May 2010?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who left WrestleMania 37 as Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended 2020 as Intercontinental Champion?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Shane McMahon at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first season of NXT in 2010?",
"Answer": "Wade Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Cesaro and Sheamus' tag team?",
"Answer": "The Bar"
},
{
"Question": "Who takes out opponents with the \"Woman's Right\"?",
"Answer": "Lacey Evans"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at Super ShowDown 2021?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar hits the West Coast Pop as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Champ at Super ShowDown 2021?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his 1st United States Title at Hell in a Cell 2017?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "With what dance pair did Naomi debut in WWE?",
"Answer": "The Funkadactyls"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Universal Title at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "As of April 2021, who is not a 2-time SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Women's Tag Titles at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Women's Tag Titles at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Tamina"
},
{
"Question": "Who is the first person to win the NXT, WWE, and Universal Titles?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "How many Tag Titles has Edge won though 2020?",
"Answer": 14
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win 2 Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as \"The Beast of Belfast\"?",
"Answer": "Killian Dain"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Becky Lynch pin to win the Winner Take All Main Event Match of WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Ronda Rousey"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Asuka last eliminate to win the 2018 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Seth Rollins from?",
"Answer": "Iowa"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Women's Title at the first WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Wendy Richter"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended Ultimate Warrior's Intercontinental Title reign?",
"Answer": "No One"
},
{
"Question": "Who represented Raw in the Champion vs Champion match at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "With what man did Bam Bam Bigelow twice win WCW Tag Titles?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title is not part of the original \"Triple Crown\"?",
"Answer": "Cruiserweight Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Raw's first pick in the 2016 Draft?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar hasn't had at least 5 WWE Title reigns?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who has won 2 King of the Ring tournaments?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses a Top Rope Splash as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "What popular pairing was Randy Savage a part of?",
"Answer": "The Mega Powers"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win the United States Title in both WWE and WCW?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2021 Andre the Giant Battle Royal?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 36 as Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Kofi Kingston for the WWE Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended 2019 as the Raw Tag Team Champions?",
"Answer": "Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of Alexa Bliss's signature move?",
"Answer": "Twisted Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Dolph Ziggler win the Raw Tag Titles with in 2018?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who doesn't use a chokeslam as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did Big E first win after joining Raw in 2012?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who was nicknamed \"The World's Most Dangerous Man\"?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who refers to himself as \"The People's Champ\"?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bayley beat for the NXT Women's Title in 2015?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Whose spot did Nia Jax steal to enter the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who introduced the spinner Title when he was WWE Champ?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Edge last eliminate to win the 2010 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first United States Title at Extreme Rules 2018?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Women's Title at Worlds Collide 2020?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Women's Championship at WrestleMania XIX?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "Who forced Kane to unmask by beating him in a 2003 match?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Bray Wyatt's faction?",
"Answer": "The Wyatt Family"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Yokozuna beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bret Hart beat to first win the WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Whose motto is \"Shock the System\"?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was nicknamed \"The Hounds of Justice\"?",
"Answer": "The Shield"
},
{
"Question": "Who shockingly returned to WWE and joined D-Generation X the night after WrestleMania XIV?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Tommaso Ciampa's former tag-team partner in DIY?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the \"Champion of Champions\" Match at Cyber Sunday 2006?",
"Answer": "King Booker"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Drew McIntyre for the WWE Title the Raw after WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "On what night did SmackDown debut on FOX?",
"Answer": "Friday"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Brutus Beefcake from?",
"Answer": "San Francisco"
},
{
"Question": "Who won Tag Titles with Edge 7 times?",
"Answer": "Christian"
},
{
"Question": "Who returned to WWE after years to face Triple H at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who was never a member of Evolution?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who was never a member of Evolution?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title at Night of Champions 2008?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Super ShowDown 2021?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Where did the WWE Thunderdome debut?",
"Answer": "Orlando"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who was named Raw General Manager in 2016?",
"Answer": "Mick Foley"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been called the Italian Strongman?",
"Answer": "Bruno Sammartino"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar hails from Venice Beach, California?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Kevin Nash from?",
"Answer": "Detroit"
},
{
"Question": "Who did John Cena last eliminate to win the 2008 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was billed a 7'4\" and 520 pounds?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Kane in an Inferno Match at Armageddon 2006?",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "How many men did Shawn Michaels eliminate in winning the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 8
},
{
"Question": "What class is AJ Styles \"The Posessed One\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the Raw Tag Titles at Elimination Chamber 2020?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Big E beat to win the NXT Title?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in Evolution with Ric Flair?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who has Kane not won a Tag Team Title with?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who comes to the ring to the song \"Glorious\"?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Randy Savage's 1989 Survivor Series Team?",
"Answer": "The King's Court"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Samoa Joe from?",
"Answer": "California"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the Raw Women's Title the longest in 2020?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as the Swiss Superman?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who would often brag about his \"Latino Heat\"?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Montez Ford from?",
"Answer": "Chicago"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted Shawn Michaels into the Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WCW Title in the first-ever World War 3 Match?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses \"End of Days\" as a signature move?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar did not win a Title cashing in their first Money in the Bank?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of Team Hogan at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Goldberg beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who used the Gorilla Press Slam as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who did King Corbin unsuccessfully cash in his Money in the Bank shot against?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "What Texas city is Eddie Guerrero from?",
"Answer": "El Paso"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win the Royal Rumble from the #30 spot?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar won the United States Title first?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "What does Sasha Banks' Team B.A.D. stand for?",
"Answer": "Beautiful and Dangerous"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Rey Mysterio to win the WWE Tag Titles at No Way Out 2005?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who wasn't in the #1 Contender Match on the Raw after WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "The Big Boss Man won a Tag Team Title with which Superstar?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Where was Mr. Perfect from?",
"Answer": "Minnesota"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to compete in a men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Intercontinental Champion heading into WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "What is the Biggest Party of the Summer?",
"Answer": "SummerSlam"
},
{
"Question": "Who refused to tag with Sami Zayn for a match against the Street Profits on the March 5, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was Big Boss Man a member of?",
"Answer": "The Corporation"
},
{
"Question": "Who used the Bull Hammer as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Wade Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Aleister Black shockingly betray in the summer of 2020?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Tommaso Ciampa and Johnny Gargano's team?",
"Answer": "#DIY"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Buried Alive match?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar entered the 1998 Royal Rumble three different times?",
"Answer": "Mick Foley"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2021, who hasn't eliminated 10 Superstars in a single Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Women's Title at WrestleMania 32?",
"Answer": "Charlotte"
},
{
"Question": "What future Superstar attended WrestleMania 6?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Which woman was a 2-time Tag Team Champion first?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ricochet beat for the NXT North American Title?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who used to say \"Everybody's got a price!\"?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Tommaso Ciampa from?",
"Answer": "Milwaukee"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Andre the Giant's Tag Team Title-winning duo?",
"Answer": "The Colossal Connection"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not become a 2-time WWE Hall of Famer in 2019?",
"Answer": "Brutus \"The Barber\" Beefcake"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Tag Team Champion at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "What Hall of Famer made his WrestleMania debut at WrestleMania V?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "How long was Undertaker's streak before he lost at WrestleMania XXX?",
"Answer": "21-0"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Robert Roode win the Raw Tag Team Titles with in 2019?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Randy Savage for the WWE Title at WrestleMania V?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an Arizona Hog Pen Match at In Your House 5?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "From what country is Wade Barrett?",
"Answer": "England"
},
{
"Question": "Who was never in the NWO?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who describes herself as \"Fearless\"?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of Kofi Kingston, Big E, and Xavier Woods' faction?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is the Million Dollar Dream?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title in the Deadly Games tournament?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who won \"The Greatest Wrestling Match Ever\" at Backlash 2020?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Braun Strowman for the Universal Title at SummerSlam 2020?",
"Answer": "\"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended 2020 as the United States Champion?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated the most people (6) from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Ric Flair's hometown?",
"Answer": "Charlotte"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Gargano and Ciampa's NXT Tag Team?",
"Answer": "DIY"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2020, who has not won a Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to be NXT Champion for more than a year?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an Ambulance Match against Shane McMahon at Survivor Series 2003?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who did The Miz beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "In the game which of these is NOT a tour in THE ROAD?",
"Answer": "Wrestlemania Tour"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Nikki Bella beat for her first Divas Title?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these is an Aleister Black signature move?",
"Answer": "Black Mass"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't lost multiple matches to Undertaker at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team claimed they had \"Body By Steak\"?",
"Answer": "Heavy Machinery"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the founder of NXT?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Bray Wyatt beat Kane at SummerSlam 2013?",
"Answer": "Ring of Fire Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Figure 8 as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Batista beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kane beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2020, which Title hasn't the Miz won?",
"Answer": "Universal Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Kofi Kingston for the WWE Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who was an Intercontinental Champion in WWE first?",
"Answer": "Greg Valentine"
},
{
"Question": "Who was The Rock's partner in The Rock 'n' Sock Connection?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Title at NXT Takeover 31?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Nia Jax put what unfortunate Superstar through the announcer's desk multiple times in 2020?",
"Answer": "Lana"
},
{
"Question": "Who took out opponents with the Anvilizer?",
"Answer": "Jim Neidhart"
},
{
"Question": "What was Scott Hall's name in WWE?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Universal Title in a Handicap Match at Backlash 2020?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who's theme music started \"You think you know me\"",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who takes out opponents with the Clothesline From Hell?",
"Answer": "JBL"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the SmackDown Women's Title at Hell in a Cell 2019?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "As of April 2021, who had not cashed in a Money in the Bank contract?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "As of April 2021, who had not cashed in a Money in the Bank contract?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title was created first?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who calls himself \"The Blackheart\"?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Concrete Crypt Match at the 2004 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mark Henry beat to win his first ECW World Title?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who like to brag \"You can't see me!\"?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who calls himself \"The Monday Night Messiah\"?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar did not hold the European Title multiple times?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "At what Pay-Per-View event did AJ Styles make his WWE debut?",
"Answer": "Royal Rumble"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first women's Superstar to win a singles and tag team TLC Match?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "In what match did Alexa Bliss win her first Title?",
"Answer": "Tables Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Women's Tag Team Title at Hell in a Cell 2019?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as the Princess of Staten Island?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Undertaker in a Hell in a Cell Match at Armageddon 2005?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who would have quit WWE if he didn't beat Shane McMahon at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at Money in the Bank 2020?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT North American Title at 2021's NXT TakeOver: Portland?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was never a member of DX?",
"Answer": "Bret \"Hitman\" Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses Natural Selection as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What brand ran an In Your House event in 2020?",
"Answer": "NXT"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ric Flair beat in an \"I Quit\" Match at SummerSlam 2006?",
"Answer": "Mick Foley"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended Randy Orton's first World Title reign at Unforgiven 2004?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "By November 2020, which Title had Daniel Bryan NOT won?",
"Answer": "Universal Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted Wendi Richter into the Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Which Championship did Christian never win?",
"Answer": "WWE Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who nails opponents with the Big Ending?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who nails opponents with the Dark Ritual?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to nail opponents with the 1916?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Roman Reigns beat Undertaker at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "No Holds Barred"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Andrade defeat in his NXT Takeover debut?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the men's 2020 Money in the Bank Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "Otis"
},
{
"Question": "Who was never a member of the 4 Horsemen?",
"Answer": "Vader"
},
{
"Question": "What kind of move is the Bayley-to-Belly?",
"Answer": "Suplex"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar provided color commentary on Raw's 1st season?",
"Answer": "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who calls himself \"The Hollywood A-Lister\"?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Jim Neidhart's brother-in-law?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars had the longest WWE Title reign?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not Intercontinental Champion in 2020?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "What was Roddy Piper's hometown?",
"Answer": "Glasgow"
},
{
"Question": "On what team did Yokozuna compete at Survivor Series 1993?",
"Answer": "The Foreign Fanatics"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Payback 2020?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of the special event held after Survivor Series 1991?",
"Answer": "This Tuesday in Texas"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2015 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Wade Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "Whose 1st SmackDown Women's Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who would have been forced to retire if he lost at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Which is a signature move of Asuka?",
"Answer": "Asuka Lock"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at WrestleMania XI?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "Who is the Legit Boss?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a mixed-martial arts fighter before coming to WWE?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who wore a mask when he debuted with WWE?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Raw Women's Title at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who served as co-host of WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Titus O'Neal"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Randy Orton defeat at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "\"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "In the game, what color is the TECHNICIAN class?",
"Answer": "Green"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated the most people (7) from the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "What's Ted DiBiase's nickname?",
"Answer": "The Million Dollar Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who is nicknamed The Mastodon?",
"Answer": "Vader"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2021, who had been runner up in 4 Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "With what partner did Charlotte Flair win Team Team Titles with in 2020?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted Stone Cold Steve Austin into the WWE Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Mr.McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who was awarded the SmackDown Tag Team Titles due to the 2020 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar did R-Truth win a Tag Team Title with?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Tag Title as a member of the Hurt Business in 2021?",
"Answer": "Shelton Benjamin"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor in the main event of the first Survivor Series (1987)?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who first cashed in a Money in the Bank Title shot at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't Batista won a Tag Team Title with?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Seth Rollins at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "At what 1991 event did Bret \"Hit Man\" Hart win his 1st Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "SummerSlam"
},
{
"Question": "Who hits opponents with her Chick Kick?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team paired with Braun Strowman at Hell in a Cell 2019?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Chad Gable from?",
"Answer": "Minnesota"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend did Randy Orton challenge at SummerSlam 2006?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who is not a member of the New Day?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Randy Orton face in a Texas Bullrope Match at the 2007 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Dusty Rhodes"
},
{
"Question": "From what state does Mickie James hail?",
"Answer": "Virginia"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Belfast Brawl at WrestleMania XXIV?",
"Answer": "JBL"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of WALTER's NXT UK faction?",
"Answer": "Imperium"
},
{
"Question": "Who has called herself a \"Role Model\" to the WWE Universe?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was known as \"Mister Wonderful\"?",
"Answer": "Paul Orndorff"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to win the Raw, SmackDown, and Tag Team Titles?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who told his opponents they'd be \"serving hard time\"?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was Drew McIntyre a member of with Jinder Mahal?",
"Answer": "3MB"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Raw's first pick in the 2019 Draft?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of the faction Randy Orton led?",
"Answer": "Legacy"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar challenged for the Women's Tag Titles at Elimination Chamber 2021?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who pretended to be Nia Jax's best friend in early 2018?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Velveteen Dream from?",
"Answer": "Washington D.C"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to give his opponents a Last Ride?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "What is Kalisto's home town?",
"Answer": "Mexico City"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker beat at WrestleMania VIII?",
"Answer": "Jake Roberts"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an Elimination Chamber match to earn a Universal Title Match at Elimination Chamber 2021?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at WrestleMania 30?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "What city has never hosted WrestleMania? (as of 2020)",
"Answer": "London"
},
{
"Question": "Who, in October 2020, became a 10-time WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Whose nickname in WWE was The Narcissist?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who got his head shaved at WrestleMania 23?",
"Answer": "Mr.McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "What city was originally supposed to host WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Tampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended Asuka's lengthy undefeated streak?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What European city is the British Bulldog from?",
"Answer": "Manchester"
},
{
"Question": "What is DIamond Dallas Page's signature move?",
"Answer": "Diamond Cutter"
},
{
"Question": "Who had a customized WWE Title with a smoking skull on it?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who has not won a Royal Rumble? (as of 2020)",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who comes out to the song \"No Chance in Hell\"?",
"Answer": "Mr.McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars was the first to be a 2-time Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Hulk Hogan defeat to win his first WCW Championship?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who's NXT Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Bobby Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who's NXT Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who made his WWE Pay-Per-View debut at Survivor Series 1990?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a \"Title vs. Career\" Match for the World Heavyweight Title at Unforgiven 2003?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who was was WWE Champion for more than 7 years?",
"Answer": "Bruno Sammartino"
},
{
"Question": "What group was linked to the infamous 1996 Curtain Call?",
"Answer": "The Kliq"
},
{
"Question": "What team has Kalisto been associated with?",
"Answer": "Lucha House Party"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Beauty Shot as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Tyler Breeze"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the women's 2020 Money in the Bank Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Titus O'Neil's faction?",
"Answer": "Titus Worldwide"
},
{
"Question": "Who was part of the infamous Montreal Screwjob?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who accompanied Bobby Lashley to the Ring at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Lana"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Seth Rollins in a No Disqualification Match at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "In what season of the NXT show did Titus O'Neil first compete?",
"Answer": "2nd"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Randy Orton from?",
"Answer": "St.Louis"
},
{
"Question": "What woman entered the 2010 men's Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ric Flair last eliminate to win the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sid Justice"
},
{
"Question": "Which annual event has been going on the longest?",
"Answer": "Wrestlemania"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Wade Barrett won in WWE?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Randy Orton last eliminate to win the 2017 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors did Yokozuna eliminate from the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 7
},
{
"Question": "Who was known as \"The Rated R Superstar\"?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Which is not a Johnny Gargano nickname?",
"Answer": "Mr. Wrestlemania"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these factions was Natalya in?",
"Answer": "The Hart Dynasty"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Shawn Michaels in a Ladder Match at WrestleMania X?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Complete the saying \"No one is ready for...\"?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Bruno Sammartino from?",
"Answer": "Italy"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend headlined WrestleMania XI against a football legend?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "What female Hall of Famer provides commentary on NXT TV?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured his 1st Heavyweight Title at WrestleMania 21?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to cash in Money in the Bank twice?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Dual-Brand Battle Royal at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Roman Reigns for the Universal Title at TLC 2019?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to yell \"BANG!\" when hitting his signature move?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "In what California city does Nikki Bella live?",
"Answer": "San Diego"
},
{
"Question": "Who was known for his \"pink-and-black attack\"?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Championship at NXT: Takerover XXV?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to win the WWE Title outside of North America?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "In what city is the WWE Performance Center?",
"Answer": "Orlando"
},
{
"Question": "Where is the Ultimate Warrior from?",
"Answer": "Parts Unknown"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title at Armageddon 2003?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Canadian city is Natalya from?",
"Answer": "Calgary"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title hasn't Christian won in WWE?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the Women's Elimination Match at Survivor Series 2018?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker beat in a Casket Match at Survivor Series 1993?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "What are John Cena's followers known as?",
"Answer": "CeNation"
},
{
"Question": "Sami Zayn beat whom for his 1st Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was Irwin R. Schyster a member of?",
"Answer": "The Million Dollar Corporation"
},
{
"Question": "On what team did Undertaker compete at Survivor Series 1993?",
"Answer": "The All-Americans"
},
{
"Question": "What parody of the New World Order did Eddie Guerrero lead?",
"Answer": "The Latino World Order"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Undertaker in a Casket Match at WrestleMania 22?",
"Answer": "Mark Henry"
},
{
"Question": "Who has The Whisper in the Wind as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the vacant United States title at Vengeance 2003?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "What was George \"The Animal\" Steele's signature move?",
"Answer": "Flying Hammerlock"
},
{
"Question": "Who was nicknamed \"The American Dream\"?",
"Answer": "Dusty Rhodes"
},
{
"Question": "What group did Shelton Benjamin join in 2020?",
"Answer": "The Hurt Business"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend did Triple H lose to in his WrestleMania debut?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Undisputed Title at WrestleMania X8?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who comes out to the song \"Here Comes the Money\"?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Whose knockout punch was named the WMD?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who managed the fake Undertaker at SummerSlam 1994?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Hulk Hogan beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Iron Sheik"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Jake Robert's pet python?",
"Answer": "Damien"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these is a signature move of The Rock?",
"Answer": "Rock Bottom"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Mark Henry from?",
"Answer": "Texas"
},
{
"Question": "Who would anger the fans by singing the Soviet national anthem?",
"Answer": "Nikolai Volkoff"
},
{
"Question": "What team won the first TLC match?",
"Answer": "Edge & Christian"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Daniel Bryan in Team Hell No?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars made their WrestleMania debut at WrestleMania 29?",
"Answer": "Fandango"
},
{
"Question": "Who has eliminated the most men from Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first WWE Hall of Famer?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is the Sharpshooter?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "With who did Tyler Breeze win the NXT Tag Titles in 2020?",
"Answer": "Fandango"
},
{
"Question": "Who sings his own entrance music, \"Sexy Boy\"?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar has been called \"Five Feet of Fury\"?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "What faction competed in the main event of Vengeance 2006?",
"Answer": "D-Generation X"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bray Wyatt face at his WrestleMania debut, WrestleMania XXX?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team proclaims \"We Want the Smoke\"?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who was awarded the Raw Tag Team Titles due to the 2020 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Ricochet for the United States Title?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Dolph Ziggler beat for the Intercontinental Title at SummerSlam 2014?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did JBL not win?",
"Answer": "Universal Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Hulk Hogan at the No Holds Barred Pay-Per-View event?",
"Answer": "Brutus Beefcake"
},
{
"Question": "Who in the Fall of 2004 beat Booker T in a best-of-5 series for the United States Title?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the Men's Triple Threat Elimination Match at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the 9th Wonder of the World?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "Which WWE show has been on the longest?",
"Answer": "Raw"
},
{
"Question": "Who did John Cena beat for the WWE Title at WrestleMania 29?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Triple H for the World Heavyweight Title at WrestleMania XIX?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "On what show did Jerry Lawler begin commentating back in 1995?",
"Answer": "Raw"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend was in Ricky Steamboat's corner in WrestleMania III?",
"Answer": "George \"The Animal\" Steele"
},
{
"Question": "Who did the Rock beat for the WCW Title at SummerSlam 2001?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of The League of Nations?",
"Answer": "Wade Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of The League of Nations?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title has Batista not won?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who had the longest single reign as Divas Champion?",
"Answer": "Brie Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ric Flair have to beat at the 2007 Royal Rumble to keep his career?",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "At what 2008 event did Kane win the ECW World Title?",
"Answer": "Wrestlemania XXIV"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Kofi Kingston from?",
"Answer": "Ghana"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the United States Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Tag Titles in an Elimination Chamber Match in 2020?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Asuka beat for her first SmackDown Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did The Miz win in 2020?",
"Answer": "Smackdown Tag Titles"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of Chad Gable and Otis's tag team?",
"Answer": "Alpha Academy"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars has beaten Undertaker at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT UK Title at 2021's Takleover: Stand and Deliver?",
"Answer": "Walter"
},
{
"Question": "Which group was Wade Barrett not a member of?",
"Answer": "Legacy"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on the team that faced Andre the Giant's team at the first Survivor Series?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Lana form an alliance with in 2020 on Raw?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "On what WWE TV show did Kofi Kingston start?",
"Answer": "ECW"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Davey Boy Smith from?",
"Answer": "Great Britain"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Ladder Match for the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Daniel Bryan beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors are in most Royal Rumble matches?",
"Answer": 30
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ron Simmons beat to win his first WCW Title?",
"Answer": "Vader"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Women's Tag Team Title at Hell in a Cell 2019?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Tag Titles at TLC 2019?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Who recieved the 2020 Warrior Award for the WWE Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "Titus O'Neal"
},
{
"Question": "whose catchphrase is \"Feel the Glow\"?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who takes out opponents with the X Factor?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "In what year did Chad Gable compete in the Olympics?",
"Answer": 2012
},
{
"Question": "What was the faction that invaded Raw and SmackDown in 2020?",
"Answer": "Retribution"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Diesel for the WWE Title at the first-ever In Your House?",
"Answer": "Sycho Sid"
},
{
"Question": "Who's first Universal Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who wasn't SmackDown Women's Champ at some point during Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was never in the NWO?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did JBL win his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Texas Bullrope Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who left Survivor Series 2020 as 24/7 Champion?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Mr. McMahon at WrestleMania XIX?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to earn a WrestleMania Title match by winning the Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar competed in the first match in SummerSlam history?",
"Answer": "Davey Boy Smith"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first competitor to win the WWE Title 10 times?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Faction was Bam Bam Bigelow a member of?",
"Answer": "The Million Dollar Corporation"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Zig Zag as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who calls his followers \"Peeps\"?",
"Answer": "Christian"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kevin Owens attack during his Raw debut?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was nicknamed \"The Legend Killer\"?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "On what show has Samoa Joe regularly provided commentary?",
"Answer": "Raw"
},
{
"Question": "What is a signature move of Razor Ramon?",
"Answer": "Razor's Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the NXT Title the longest in 2020?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team made a surprise return to the Raw after WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who refers to himself as a Prince?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mr. McMahon beat to win the WWE Title in September 1999?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Seth Rollins for the Universal Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Big John Studd face at the first WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Hulk Hogan in the Main Event of SummerSlam 1989?",
"Answer": "Brutus Beefcake"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title at Taboo Tuesday 2004?",
"Answer": "Shelton Benjamin"
},
{
"Question": "By the end of 2020, which title hadn't Rey Mysterio won?",
"Answer": "Universal Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the United States Title by winning a best-of-five series in October 2004?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who threw away a decades-long friendship with Drew McIntyre in early 2021?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "At what WWE event did Undertaker win his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Survivor Series"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sycho Sid"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the Women's Elimination Match at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Lana"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the World Heavyweight Title at the 2006 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar hosts a popular video game YouTube show?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "How many languages does Cesaro speak?",
"Answer": 5
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kane defeat to win the WWE Championship?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Money in the Bank match?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Angelo Dawkins from?",
"Answer": "Cincinnati"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did \"The Fiend' Bray Wyatt win the Universal Title at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Falls Count Anywhere Match"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first WWE PPV event to be held in England?",
"Answer": "SummerSlam"
},
{
"Question": "In which armed forces branch did Lacey Evans serve?",
"Answer": "Marines"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Killian Dane from?",
"Answer": "Northern Ireland"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Roman Reigns beat in a Falls Count Anywhere Match at the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Matching ___ or more gems gives an extra turn.",
"Answer": 5
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Universal Title at Super Showdown 2020?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Kevin Nash and Scott Hall's WCW tag team?",
"Answer": "The Outsiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who defied the odds to win the 2006 Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who was kicked out of the Million Dollar Corporation because of his WrestleMania XI loss?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "With who did Ted DiBiase win the tag Titles?",
"Answer": "Irwin R Schyster"
},
{
"Question": "In what year did Monday Night Raw debut?",
"Answer": 1993
},
{
"Question": "Who nails opponents with the Claymore Kick?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 13 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Sycho Sid"
},
{
"Question": "Who had Stone Cold Steve Austin just beat when he said his famous \"Austin 3:16\" quote?",
"Answer": "Jake Roberts"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the original leader of the Nexus?",
"Answer": "Wade Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "What sport did John Cena play in college?",
"Answer": "Football"
},
{
"Question": "Who won Backlash 2020's \"Greatest Match Ever\"?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an Ambulance Match at Clash of Champions 2020?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who calls himself \"The Sexy Scotsman\"?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did Diamond Dallas Page win in WWE?",
"Answer": "European Title"
},
{
"Question": "What bird nickname did JBL use when he first joined WWE?",
"Answer": "Hawk"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title the night after WrestleMania 29?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Universal Title Match at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Which move is a Sasha Banks specialty?",
"Answer": "Bank Statement"
},
{
"Question": "With whom did Asuka win the first Mixed Match Challenge in 2018?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who lifted both Big Show and Edge for a slam At WrestleMania XXV?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Midnight Hour as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "What former ally did Batista brutally betray in late 2009?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a tournament for the vacant Intercontinental Title in June 2020?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "With what partner did Sheamus win his first Tag Team Title?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to finish off opponents with the Jackhammer?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "What does Elias think WWE stands for?",
"Answer": "Walk with Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Which is a Vader signature move?",
"Answer": "Vaderbomb"
},
{
"Question": "What is NOT a type of event in WWE Champions?",
"Answer": "King of the Hill"
},
{
"Question": "Where was WrestleMania XX held?",
"Answer": "New York"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't challenge Bayley for the SmackDown Women's Title at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who was WWE Champion for all of 1987?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is known for his Strong Style?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a sole survivor in a 1989 Survivor Series match?",
"Answer": "Greg Valentine"
},
{
"Question": "Who's first SmackDown Women's Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Adam Cole in an Extreme Rules Match at 2018's NXT Takeover: Philadelphia?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "Where did the first WrestleMania take place?",
"Answer": "New York"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the WWE Title on October 2019's SmackDown 20th Anniversary show?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "In the game, what color is the TRICKSTER class?",
"Answer": "Purple"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended The Universal Title at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who shockingly won the 1999 Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Mr.McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Becky Lynch for the Raw Women's Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is \"Greetings from Asbury Park\"?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "What sport did Keith Lee play the most in college?",
"Answer": "Football"
},
{
"Question": "Who claimed to be \"the best there is, the best there was, the best there ever will be\"?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced his brother in an Extreme Rules Match at WrestleMania XXV?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "What class is Adam Cole \"The Undisputed Era\"",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "On whom did Daniel Bryan cash his Money in the Bank in 2011?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Drew McIntyre last eliminate to win the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who reminds people he was world champ \"5 Times! 5 Times!\"?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Stone Cold Steve Austin at WrestleMania XIX?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Where is WALTER from?",
"Answer": "Austria"
},
{
"Question": "Who was WWE Champion heading into WrestleMania VI?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to compete in a King of the Ring?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "On whom did Sheamus cash his Money in the Bank in 2015?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 8 men en route to winning the 1995 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Seth Rollins joined WWE as part of what faction?",
"Answer": "The Shield"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been known as \"The Eater of Worlds\"?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "After WrestleMania, what is WWE's longest-running PPV event?",
"Answer": "Survivor Series"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend was a co-host of WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "What WCW faction was DDP and Bam Bam Bigelow in?",
"Answer": "The Jersey Triad"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2021, which of these teams has been NXT, Raw, and SmackDown tag champions?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who angered Mr. McMahon by buying WCW in 2001?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "What move did Paul Orndorff use to finish off opponents?",
"Answer": "Piledriver"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in both DX and the NWO?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who forfeited the WCW Television Title by throwing it in a trash can?",
"Answer": "Scott Hall"
},
{
"Question": "Who was an Evolution teammate of Randy Orton?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was an Evolution teammate of Randy Orton?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who used Triple H's Pedigree as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who was WWE's first World Heavyweight Champion?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kofi Kingston beat for the WWE Championship?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Finn Bálor to win the first Dusty Rhodes Tag Team classic?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who viciously attacked Hulk Hogan, putting him out of action for several months in 1990?",
"Answer": "Earthquake"
},
{
"Question": "What breakfast item did the New Day used to throw in the crowd?",
"Answer": "Pancakes"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not an original member of the NWO?",
"Answer": "Ricky Steamboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania XIV as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Shinsuke Nakamura from?",
"Answer": "Japan"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the WWE Title to Daniel Bryan at SummerSlam 2013?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a tag team champion in WWE first?",
"Answer": "Iron Sheik"
},
{
"Question": "Name AJ Styles' powerful signature move?",
"Answer": "Styles Clash"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Helluva Kick?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who did \"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt beat for the Universal Title in 2020?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been called \"The Underdog from the Underground\"?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Keith Lee from?",
"Answer": "Texas"
},
{
"Question": "Who claimed to be from \"The Land of the Rising Sun\"?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ricochet beat for the United States Title?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who proclaimed that \"he's cool, he's cocky, he's bad\"?",
"Answer": "The Honky Tonk Man"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of the Miz's 2017 Faction?",
"Answer": "The Miztourage"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses The Dominator as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Drew McIntyre in an Extreme Rules Match for the WWE Title in July 2020?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Champions vs. Champions tag match at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mr. T box at WrestleMania 2?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shawn Michaels beat for his 1st World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What was JBL's first singles Title in his WWE career?",
"Answer": "European Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who used the Wasteland as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Wade Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Firefly Funhouse Match at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "\"The Fiend\" Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of the bulldog Davey Boy Smith brought to the ring?",
"Answer": "Matilda"
},
{
"Question": "What state is the Miz originally from?",
"Answer": "Ohio"
},
{
"Question": "What move does Rhea Ripley use to finish her foes?",
"Answer": "Riptide"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the Universal Title the longest in 2020?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "In what city did Hulk Hogan and The Rock have their epic WrestleMania match?",
"Answer": "Toronto"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Bayley for the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the #30 entrance to the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who won her first WWE title at WrestleMania 22?",
"Answer": "Mickie James"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with Trouble in Paradise?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who began 2020 as United States Champion?",
"Answer": "Andrade"
},
{
"Question": "Which wasn't a name X-Pac used early in his career?",
"Answer": "The Gourmet Kid"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the Kliq?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who makes opponents tap out with the Dis-arm-her?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as the Ravishing Russian?",
"Answer": "Lana"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't Big Show won a Tag Team Title with?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What is Randy Savage's nickname",
"Answer": "Macho Man"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did The Miz first win in WWE?",
"Answer": "WWE Tag Team Title"
},
{
"Question": "What is Jerry Lawler's nickname?",
"Answer": "The King"
},
{
"Question": "Who shows his strength by swinging his opponents in the ring?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who in 2019, became the first African-born WWE Champ in history?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Akira Tozawa from?",
"Answer": "Japan"
},
{
"Question": "What's the name of Brie Bella's twin sister?",
"Answer": "Nikki"
},
{
"Question": "What is a name of Tyler Breeze and Frandango's tag team?",
"Answer": "The Fashion Police"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Bayley for the SmackDown Women's Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first WWE Worlds Collide tournament?",
"Answer": "Velveteen Dream"
},
{
"Question": "Who did AJ Styles beat in November 2017 to become WWE Champ a second time?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title twice in 2020?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Women's WrestleMania Battle Royal?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is married to Naomi?",
"Answer": "Jimmy Uso"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Ted DiBiase and Andre the Giant's tag team?",
"Answer": "The Megabucks"
},
{
"Question": "Where was George \"The Animal\" Steele was from?",
"Answer": "Detroit"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Mankind beat to win the WWE Title the 1st time?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "What team won the first tag-team Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Lacey Evans from?",
"Answer": "South Carolina"
},
{
"Question": "Which championship did Eddie Guerrero never win?",
"Answer": "Hardcore Title"
},
{
"Question": "Whose feet did Jerry Lawler have to kiss after an intense match?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Asuka and Kairi Sane's team?",
"Answer": "Kabuki Warriors"
},
{
"Question": "By what score did Shawn Michaels win the Iron Man WWE Title Match at WrestleMania XII?",
"Answer": "1-0"
},
{
"Question": "Who did AJ Styles defeat at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What woman was part of the pairing known as Glamarella?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar did Keith Lee confront in his 2020 Raw debut?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Women to hold the Tag Titles with 2 different partners?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who is \"The Most Electrifying Man in Sports Entertainment\"?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with John Cena in a Mixed Tag Match at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a WWE Women's Tag Champion in 2020?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Roman Reigns in a Tables, Ladders and Chairs Match at TLC 2019?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Finn Bálor from?",
"Answer": "Ireland"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses a Running Knee as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar won his first WWE Title at No Way Out 2004?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Roddy Piper's interview show?",
"Answer": "Piper's Pit"
},
{
"Question": "As of 2020, who hadn't Charlotte Flair teamed with in a Mixed Match Challenge?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "What was Jim Neidhart's nickname?",
"Answer": "The Anvil"
},
{
"Question": "Who was featured in a 5-Part WWE Documentary called The Last Ride?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Ted DiBiase at the first-ever SummerSlam?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sasha Banks beat to win the NXT Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who assisted Roman Reigns during his Universal Title defense at WWE TLC 2020?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to beat opponents with the Phenomenal Forearm?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't been the NXT Champion?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was Killian Dane a member of?",
"Answer": "SAnitY"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Honky Tonk Man beat for the Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Ricky Steamboat"
},
{
"Question": "What area code is associated with Rey Mysterio?",
"Answer": 619
},
{
"Question": "What WWE show did Shane McMahon take over in 2016?",
"Answer": "Smackdown"
},
{
"Question": "What move does Ember Moon use to finish off opponents?",
"Answer": "Eclipse"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania X as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar promotes the Power of Positivity?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Randy Orton at Payback 2020?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who attacks opponents with the Pop-up Powerbomb?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the WCW Television Title a record 6 times?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar became a 5-time Intercontinental Champion first?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What type of animal mask did Braun Strowman wear in the Wyatt Family?",
"Answer": "Black Sheep"
},
{
"Question": "Which term is a nickname for Ronda Rousey?",
"Answer": "Rowdy"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the second ever WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bruno Sammartino"
},
{
"Question": "Who won WWE's first-ever Inferno Match?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who famously said \"to be the man, you gotta beat the man\"?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was known for taking ringside selfies during his matches?",
"Answer": "Tyler Breeze"
},
{
"Question": "Which man has won the Royal Rumble match twice?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in two Championship Matches at Clash of Champions 2020?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the Triple Threat TLC match for the WWE Title at WWE TLC 2020?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Sgt. Slaughter from?",
"Answer": "South Carolina"
},
{
"Question": "Who is not a character in the Firefly Fun House?",
"Answer": "Stinky Squirrel"
},
{
"Question": "Who was forced to defend the WWE Title in the 2016 Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who had a customized WWE Title with a Brahma Bull on it?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who has won Tag Team Titles with 6 different partners?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at WrestleMania XIV?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the vacant NXT Tag Titles at NXT: Takeover XXV?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Women's Title at the first NXT Takeover in 2014?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the longest-reigning European Champion in WWE History?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend was undefeated in WWE for nearly 15 years?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Women's Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Universal Title twice in 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who submits opponents with the Calf Crusher",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first competitor to win the WWE Title 7 times?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title in February 1988 at WWE: The Main Event?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar did The Rock win a Tag Team Title with?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Ted DiBiase's Megabucks partner in the first SummerSlam?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "How quickly did Sheamus beat Daniel Bryan at WrestleMania 28?",
"Answer": "18 seconds"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Supermodel Kick as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Tyler Breeze"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Bobby Lashley in a Last Man Standing Match at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat The Rock at Backlash 2003?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who would often proclaim \"the champ is here\"?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who served as Ric Flair's Executive Consultant when he joined WWE in 1991?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the SmackDown Tag Titles at Elimination Chamber 2019?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Elias announced his 2020 return to Raw by attacking what Superstar?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who has Undertaker not faced at WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who's NXT Title reign was the shortest?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "What move does John Cena use to finish his foes?",
"Answer": "Attitude Adjustment"
},
{
"Question": "Who calls himself the Tribal Chief of his family?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title has Randy Orton never held? (As of 2020)",
"Answer": "24/7 Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who debuted in WWE as Triple H's bodyguard?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Torture Rack as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar calls herself \"The Man\"?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who hosts \"The Dirt Sheet\"?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "In 1991, who did Bret \"Hit Man\" Hart beat to win his 1st Intercontinental Title?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Tag Titles at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Who won, and then lost, the WWE Title at WrestleMania IX?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Andrade for the NXT Title?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who, in December 2020, became the first 3-time NXT North American Champion?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who is the Chief Brand Officer of WWE?",
"Answer": "Stephanie McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who takes out opponents with the Glam Slam?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar is Roman Reigns' cousin?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Doink's diminutive partner?",
"Answer": "Dink"
},
{
"Question": "Whose motto was \"Don't Trust Anybody\"?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "What double chair hit did Edge & Christian make famous?",
"Answer": "Con-Chair-To"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar held the WWE Title the longest?",
"Answer": "Iron Sheik"
},
{
"Question": "Who would often cry out \"Viva La Raza\"?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the Artist Collective?",
"Answer": "Aleister Black"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the Artist Collective?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar had a movie made about her early life in 2019?",
"Answer": "Paige"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of Match did Braun Strowman and the Fiend compete at Extreme Rules 2020?",
"Answer": "Wyatt Swamp Fight"
},
{
"Question": "Who was called \"The Eighth Wonder of the World\"?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who never held the SmackDown Tag Titles in ?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend is known as The Heartbreak Kid?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "What does R-Truth call his imaginary supporter?",
"Answer": "Little Jimmy"
},
{
"Question": "How many times was Road Dogg a WWE Tag Team Champion?",
"Answer": 6
},
{
"Question": "Who ended Nikki Bella's lengthy reign as Divas Champion?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "On whom did Edge cash his second Money in the Bank in 2007?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "What is Rey Mysterio's home town?",
"Answer": "San Diego"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Seth Rollins won in WWE?",
"Answer": "Tag Team Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the first Survivor Series main event?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who's first NXT Title reign was the longest?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "What was X-Pac's name when he first joined WWE?",
"Answer": "1-2-3 Kid"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Big E from?",
"Answer": "Tampa"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is the leader of the Undisputed Era?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE show did Stephanie McMahon take over in 2016?",
"Answer": "Raw"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to nail opponents with the People's Elbow?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who has competed in the most NXT Takeover events? (Through 2020)",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who attacked Hulk Hogan at the end of WrestleMania VIII?",
"Answer": "Papa Shango"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "ho was the first Superstar to win the WWE Title on Raw?",
"Answer": "Sycho Sid"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sheamus beat for his first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Alexa Bliss used her Money in the Bank contract on what champ?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "What color does DX often wear to the ring?",
"Answer": "Green"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first two-time WWE Hall of Famer?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What cheating technique did the Bellas use to win matches?",
"Answer": "Twin Magic"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Becky Lynch defend the Raw Women's Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Submission Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the WWE Title at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Big E beat to win the Intercontinental Title in December 2020?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Whose signature move is Salida del Sol?",
"Answer": "Kalisto"
},
{
"Question": "What was Brutus Beefcake's nickname?",
"Answer": "The Barber"
},
{
"Question": "Who was once nicknamed \"The Scottish Psychopath\"?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Women's Elimination Chamber match?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Coup de Grace?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Matching ___ gems clears out the row.",
"Answer": 4
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "When did Undertaker begin his incredible streak?",
"Answer": "Wrestlemania 7"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania35?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Titus O'Neil from?",
"Answer": "Florida"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Chyna won in WWE?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Title at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "Who held the Raw Tag Team Titles the longest in 2020?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who calls himself \"The Great One\"?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the final WWE Divas Champion?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is known for the \"Yes! Yes! Yes!\" chant?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who has Batista not won a Tag Title with?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "What was Akira Tozawa's first WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Cruiserweight Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who originally brought Undertaker to WWE?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Booker T's WCW tag team?",
"Answer": "Harlem Heat"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was shockingly bit by a cobra at SummerSlam 1991?",
"Answer": "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Which WCW faction did Lex Luger end up joining?",
"Answer": "NWO Wolfpac"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not NXT Champion in 2020?",
"Answer": "Velveteen Dream"
},
{
"Question": "What signature move did Greg \"The Hammer\" Valentine use to submit opponents?",
"Answer": "Figure 4 Leg Lock"
},
{
"Question": "Who called himself \"The Planet's Champ\"?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Drew McIntyre from?",
"Answer": "Scotland"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first-ever Hell in a Cell \"I Quit\" Match in 2020?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title thanks to a crooked twin referee?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Title Samoa Joe won in WWE after leaving NXT?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who ended AJ Styles' WWE Title reign in November 2018?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Andrade from?",
"Answer": "Mexico"
},
{
"Question": "Who unified the WWE and World Heavyweight Titles?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did The Honky Tonk Man hold for over a year?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did AJ Styles win in June 2020?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "On whom did Randy Orton cash his Money in the Bank in 2013?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Where did Finn Bálor first win the NXT Championship?",
"Answer": "Tokyo"
},
{
"Question": "On whom did Carmella cash her Money in the Bank in 2018?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who unsuccessfully challenged Kofi Kingston for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the Intercontinental Title to Triple H in a Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "In what city did Chad Gable compete in the Olympics?",
"Answer": "London"
},
{
"Question": "Who did R-Truth team with to win WWE's Mixed Match Challenge Season 2?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Rhea Ripley from?",
"Answer": "Australia"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first WWE Title at Backlash 2016?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "What is \"The House that AJ Styles built\"?",
"Answer": "Smackdown"
},
{
"Question": "NXT has hosted an annual tag team competition to honor what Legend?",
"Answer": "Dusty Rhodes"
},
{
"Question": "Who's son joined him on the SmackDown roster in 2020?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shane McMahon defeat in his WrestleMania debut at WrestleMania XV?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Andre the Giant Memorial Battle Royal?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "What instrument does Elias play?",
"Answer": "Guitar"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the inaugural NXT North American Champion?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Kinshasa?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who hosts a WWE Podcast called Uncool?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Jey Uso shockingly attack in October 2020 on SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered WrestleMania 33 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar claims he is \"immune to fear\"?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did Bret Hart surprisingly win in May 2010?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "Complete Carmella's catchphrase: \"Mella is ...\"",
"Answer": "money"
},
{
"Question": "Who has defended the NXT Women's Title in an Iron Man match in 2015?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted his father and grandfather into the Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Which is a signature move of X-Pac?",
"Answer": "Bronco Buster"
},
{
"Question": "Who did John Cena beat for the WWE Title at WrestleMania XXVI?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "What WCW Title did Scott Hall never win?",
"Answer": "WCW Title"
},
{
"Question": "Whose mottos include \"Wreck Everyone and Leave\"?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Asuka win her first SmackDown Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Tables, Ladders, and Chair Match"
},
{
"Question": "What was a Roddy Piper signature move?",
"Answer": "Sleeper Hold"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar beat Finn Bálor for the NXT Title?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ronda Rousey beat to win the Raw Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with The Stomp?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first ever Boiler Room Brawl?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Where is AJ Styles from?",
"Answer": "Georgia"
},
{
"Question": "Where is The Honky Tonk Man from?",
"Answer": "Memphis"
},
{
"Question": "Who did the Fiend beat at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to win the WWE Title on Raw?",
"Answer": "Sycho Sid"
},
{
"Question": "What Title did Akira Tozawa win several times in 2020?",
"Answer": "24/7 Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who was nicknamed \"The Living Legend\"?",
"Answer": "Bruno Sammartino"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to finish off opponents with Sister Abigail?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Kane is the Big Red what?",
"Answer": "Machine"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Ricochet for the NXT North American Title?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend was known as the Beast from the East?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to win the NXT Title twice?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kevin Owens defeat at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Batista from?",
"Answer": "Washington D.C"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Ted DiBiase's championship tag team?",
"Answer": "Money Inc."
},
{
"Question": "What was the final score in the 2-out-of-3 Falls Match between Ric Flair and Mick Foley at Vengeance 2006?",
"Answer": "2-0 Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Asuka from?",
"Answer": "Japan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Director of Operations for the Authority?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "What is the class of the character with this tie?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Intercontinental Title in an Iron Man Match at Extreme Rules 2018?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who finishes off opponents with the Khallas?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Chad Gable win the Raw Tag Titles with in 2018?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Which was not a signature move of Jim Neidhart?",
"Answer": "Hurricanrana"
},
{
"Question": "Who bragged that he would \"lie, cheat, and steal\"?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Jerry Lawler from?",
"Answer": "Memphis"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sasha Banks beat at SummerSlam 2016 to win the Raw Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Raw Tag Team Titles with Drew McIntyre in 2018?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Which is not a signature move of Eddie Guerrero?",
"Answer": "F-5"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shinsuke Nakamura beat for the NXT Title twice?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Lacey Evans in a 2019 Extreme Rules match for multiple Title matches?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at WrestleMania XX?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who has won the most Elimination Chamber matches?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the tag Titles at WrestleMania 34 with a fan as partner?",
"Answer": "Braun Strowman"
},
{
"Question": "Who nailed unlucky competitors with the Stinkface?",
"Answer": "Rikishi"
},
{
"Question": "What's the MINIMUM number of gems needed to match?",
"Answer": 3
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title for a second time in 2020?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title in October 2020 in a Hell in a Cell Match?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Where did Randy Orton win his first World Title?",
"Answer": "SummerSlam 2004"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Charlotte Flair from?",
"Answer": "North Carolina"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend was from Cobb County, Georgia?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "What was Ted DiBiase's faction named?",
"Answer": "The Million Dollar Corporation"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars was both WWE and WCW Champion?",
"Answer": "\"Macho Man\" Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the \"Skull Crushing Finale\" as a signature move?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team often wore unicorn horns to the ring?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "What is Faarooq's signature move?",
"Answer": "Dominator"
},
{
"Question": "Who was nicknamed The Total Package?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Nikolai Volkoff's tag team?",
"Answer": "The Bolsheviks"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Jim Neidhart from?",
"Answer": "Nevada"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first WWE Title in 2017's Elimination Chamber match?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first 24/7 Champion?",
"Answer": "Titus O'Neal"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of the New Day's cereal?",
"Answer": "Booty-O's"
},
{
"Question": "Whose nickname did Ronda Rousey use?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did Mark Henry not win?",
"Answer": "Cruiserweight Title"
},
{
"Question": "Where is John Cena from?",
"Answer": "Massachusetts"
},
{
"Question": "Which faction was Randy Orton not a member of?",
"Answer": "The Hart Dynasty"
},
{
"Question": "Who asks the WWE Universe to bask in his glory?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title in the 1992 Royal Rumble match?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who helped Stephanie McMahon beat Brie Bella at SummerSlam '14?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar is \"The Empress of Tomorrow\"?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is proudly a vegan?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these is a 3rd Generation Superstar?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Greg Valentine from?",
"Answer": "Seattle"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Kevin Owens from?",
"Answer": "Canada"
},
{
"Question": "On whom did Bayley cash her Money in the Bank in 2019?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Cesaro \"The Professional\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is X-Pac \"DX\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Team Champion at SummerSlam 2017?",
"Answer": "Jimmy Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Team Champion at SummerSlam 2017?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "How many times were the Wild Samoans WWE World Tag Team Champions?",
"Answer": 3
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Hell in a Cell 2013?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Chairs Match at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2018?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is The Boogeyman \"Comin' to Getcha\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Women's Battle Royal at SummerSlam 2009?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for Jerry Lawler's match at WrestleMania XXVII?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE World Heavyweight Title in a Ladder Match at Money in the Bank 2015?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Fatal 4-Way 2010?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title in a Ladder Match at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2016?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Becky Lynch \"Irish Lass Kicker\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Triple H \"The Skull King\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Randy Savage \"Master of Macho Madness\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Fastlane 2018?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Damian Priest \"Archer of Infamy\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Tag Titles in a Lumberjack Match at Extreme Rules 2011?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Eddie Guerrero \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Johnny Gargano \"Johnny Wrestling\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Roman Reigns for the Universal Title at WrestleMania Backlash 2021?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Tables Match at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2018?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Stephanie McMahon \"Best for Business\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Undertaker compete at 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Casket Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the Women's Elimination Match at Survivor Series 2017?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Showstopper\"",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bray Wyatt \"Eater of Worlds\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bret Hart \"The Hitman\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Edge face in a TLC Match at One Night Stand 2008?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Randy Orton \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Backlash 2008?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Rikishi \"Too Cool\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at Backlash 2018?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Rocky Maivia \"Blue Chipper\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What type of match did John Cena win at Extreme Rules 2009?",
"Answer": "Submission Match"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Andre the Giant \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Ladder Match for the NXT North American Title at 2018's NXT TakeOver: New Orleans?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Night of Champions 2008?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "ho teamed with Batista to challenge for the Unified Tag Titles at Hell in a Cell 2009?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Mankind \"The Deranged\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Erik \"The Viking Raiders\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend did fans select to challenge for the Intercontinental Title at Cyber Sunday 2008?",
"Answer": "Honky Tonk Man"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was the first to win a Women's Hell in a Cell match?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the first-ever Women's Money in the Bank Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "What Canadian city is Rocky Johnson's home town?",
"Answer": "Toronto"
},
{
"Question": "Who became NXT Champion at 2017's NXT TakeOver: San Antonio?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Women's Title at Hell in a Cell 2018?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Triple H \"Evil Skull King\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is MVP \"The Hurt Business\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the WWE World Heavyweight Title Elimination Chamber Match at Elimination Chamber 2014?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Chad Gable \"American Alpha\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"Mr. Pay Per View\"",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who risked his career to challenge The Miz for the Intercontinental Title at No Mercy 2016?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the Raw Women's Title at SummerSlam 2017?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who left WrestleMania Backlash 2021 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Otis \"Heavy Machinery\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Randy Orton \"The Legend Killer\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Immortal\"",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Booker T \"Harlem Heat\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title in a Six-Pack Elimination Match at Night of Champions 2010?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Alexa Bliss defend the Raw Women's Title at Extreme Rules 2017?",
"Answer": "Kendo-Stick-On-A-Pole Match"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Batista \"The Animal\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2018?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Charlotte Flair defend the SmackDown Women's Title at Clash of Champions 2017?",
"Answer": "Lumberjack Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the WWE Title at Elimination Chamber 2017?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Daniel Bryan from?",
"Answer": "Washington"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The One and Only\"",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Gold Standard\"",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Seth Rollins \"The Undisputed Fiend\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Roman Reigns compete at 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Steel Cage Match"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is John Cena \"Veteran Salute\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Fatal 4-Way 2010?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a Zombie Lumberjack Match at WrestleMania Backlash 2021?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Undertaker \"Glowing Phantom Phenom\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Shawn Michaels \"D-Generation X\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in first first WWE match in 12 years in the Main Event of Survivor Series 2016?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is IRS?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at Extreme Rules 2018?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title in an Iron Man Match at Extreme Rules 2018?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Backlash 2009?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ken Shamrock \"The World's Most Dangerous Man\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bruno Sammartino \"The Italian Strongman\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is The Godfather \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Chyna \"9th Wonder of the World\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Chyna \"DX Army\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Trish Stratus \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is The Rock \"The People's Champ\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kane \"Icons of Wrestlemania\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Women's Title at SummerSlam 2016?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who unsuccessfully challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at WrestleMania Backlash 2021?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is The Rock \"The People's Chomp\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kofi Kingston \"Power of Positivity\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title at December 2014's NXT Takeover: R Evolution?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Extreme Rules 2018?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who became an NXT Tag Team Champion at 2018's NXT TakeOver: New Orleans?",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title in an Elimination Chamber Match at Elimination Chamber 2018?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kevin Owens \"KO\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Mr. Perfect \"The Perfect One\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who interfered in the Triple Threat TLC Match for the SmackDown Women's Title at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2018?",
"Answer": "Ronda Rousey"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at 2018's Evolution?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who, in February 2021, became WWE's first-ever two-time Grand Slam winner?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Stone Cold Steve Austin \"The Texas Revenant\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Extreme Rules 2011?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title in a TLC Match at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2016?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for the Triple H/Undertaker match at WrestleMania XXVII?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is John Cena \"Chain Gang\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What reunited tag team challenged for the SmackDown Tag Titles at Extreme Rules 2018?",
"Answer": "Team Hell No"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Divas Title at SummerSlam 2014?",
"Answer": "Paige"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not part of the Total Divas Team at Survivor Series 2013?",
"Answer": "Paige"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Doink the Clown \"The Prankster\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Survivor Series 2008?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Women's Title at 2017's NXT TakeOver: WarGames?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Lex Luger \"American Original\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Sasha Banks \"Legit Dead Boss\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What disgusting snack did the Boogeyman enjoy eating before matches?",
"Answer": "worms"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title at February 2015's NXT TakeOver: Rival?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Drew McIntyre \"The Sinister Scotsman\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Shinsuke Nakamura \"Strong Style Has Arrived\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who diid Kevin Owens beat in a Hell in a Cell match at Hell in a Cell 2017?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ultimate Warrior \"Warrior\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team won a #1 Contender Battle Royal on the June 7, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with The Miz to face John Cena & The Rock at Survivor Series 2011?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Trish Stratus \"Tribute to the Troops\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Dude Love \"Hippest Cat in the Land\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam 2017?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the World Heavyweight Title at Survivor Series 2009?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Undertaker \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Rocky Johnson \"Soul Man\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Beth Phoenix's tag team at SummerSlam 2008?",
"Answer": "Glamarella"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Title at 2018's NXT TakeOver: Brooklyn 4?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Montez Ford \"The Street Profits\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Brie Bella \"Brie Mode\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend competed in a Handicap Match at WrestleMania 25?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend competed in a Handicap Match at WrestleMania 25?",
"Answer": "Ricky Steamboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an Unsanctioned Match at Unforgiven 2008?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Batista beat at SummerSlam 2008?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Undertaker for the World Heavyweight Title at the 2010 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States Title in a Russian Chain Match at Extreme Rules 2015?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at SummerSlam 2011?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Women's Tag Team Champion on a May 2021 episode of SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who did John Cena beat in a Chairs Match at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2010?",
"Answer": "Wade Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't Dolph Ziggler face in the World Cup Tournament at 2018's Crown Jewel?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bobby Lashley \"The Almighty\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Possessed One\"",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Syxx \"NWO\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Randy Savage \"NWO Madness\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Night of Champions 2015?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Luke \"The Bushwhackers\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Charlotte Flair \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Triple H \"The Game\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE World Heavyweight Title at Money in the Bank 2014?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on Mick Foley's team at Survivor Series 2012?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Shawn Michaels \"The Heartbreak Kid\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who returned to WWE after a multi-year absense and won the 2014 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't challenge for the WWE Title at Fastlane 2018?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Mr. T \"T\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Nikki Bella \"Fearless\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Triple H \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "By what score did John Cena win the Iron Man Match at Bragging Rights 2009?",
"Answer": "6 to 5"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Bray Wyatt in a House of Horrors Match at Payback 2017?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kane 'Director of Operations\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Big John Studd \"True Giant\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Papa Shango \"The Voodoo King\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his Money in the Bank Ladder Match at Money in the Bank 2012?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his Money in the Bank Ladder Match at Money in the Bank 2012?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an \"I Quit\" Match at Backlash 2009?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Raw Women's Title at SummerSlam 2017?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor when Team Cena met Team Authority at Survivor Series 2014?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Dolph Ziggler to challenge for the WWE Tag Titles at WrestleMania 29?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Typhoon \"The Natural Disasters\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Road Dogg \"DX Army\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated the most competitors, 6, from the 2010 Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Undertaker at WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ted Dibiase \"NWO\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Steve Austin \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar claimed he was \"coming to getcha\"?",
"Answer": "The Boogeyman"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Tag Titles at Night of Champions 2012?",
"Answer": "Kane & Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at SummerSlam 2012?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Lacey Evans \"The Sassy Southern Belle\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Bragging Rights 2009?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not involved in the WWE Title Match at WrestleMania XXIV?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar drew some of his power from a mythical urn?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Universal Title at SummerSlam 2018?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Undertaker in the first Hell in a Cell Match held at a WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Raw Tag Team Champion at SummerSlam 2017?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Jinder Mahal in a Punjabi Prison Match at Battleground 2017?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title at Backlash 2018?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Champion vs. United States Champion Match at Survivor Series 2018?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat John Cena for the WWE Title at Elimination Chamber 2010?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Women's Title at May 2014's NXT Arrival?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Justin \"Hawk\" Bradshaw?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Alexa Bliss \"Play or Pain\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Roman Reigns face in his first-ever Hell in a Cell Match?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not the the WWE Title Match at Fatal 4-Way 2010?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these competitors won their first two Hell in a Cell Matches?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the Team Orton vs. Team Kingston Match at Survivor Series 2009?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not participate in the Triple Threat Match for the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam 2018?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat John Cena in a singles match at Money in the Bank 2016?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Underdog from the Underground\"",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Seth Rollins \"The Architect\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Becky Lynch \"The Man\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"Latino Heat\"",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Triple Threat Match at Fastlane 2016 to earn a World Title shot at WrestleMania 32?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these women did not compete in the inaugural Mae Young Classic?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Name the creepy doll that's been associated with Alexa Bliss.",
"Answer": "Lily"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Unified Tag Team Champion at 2009's The Bash?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Money in the Bank Ladder Match at Money in the Bank 2015?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Triple H defend the WWE Title at Judgment Day 2008?",
"Answer": "Steel Cage Match"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ivar \"Viking Raiders\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bret Hart \"NWO 2000\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Destroyer\"",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Carmella \"The Princess of Staten Island\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Roman Reigns for the WWE World Heavyweight Title in an Extreme Rules Match at Extreme Rules 2016?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Breaking Point 2009?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Undertaker \"Dead Man Walking\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Roman Reigns \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Night of Champions 2014?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the World Heavyweight Title at No Way Out 2008?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who wasn't on the team defending the WWE Title at Backlash 2009?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Battleground 2014?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Nia Jax \"Irresistible Force\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is \"Ravishing\" Rick Rude?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not involved in the Mixed Tag Team Match at Hell in a Cell 2018?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is The Rock \"The Most Electrifying Man in Sports Entertainment\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Drew McIntyre \"Scottish Warrior\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ric Flair \"The Nature Boy\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who left Judgment Day 2008 as World Heavyweight Champion?",
"Answer": "None of them"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Nikolai Volkoff \"The Russian\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Rick Rude \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bianca Belair \"The EST\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Shane McMahon \"Shane O Mac\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Becky Lynch defend the SmackDown Women's Title at 2018's WWE Evolution?",
"Answer": "Last Woman Standing Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title in an Elimination Chamber match at Elimination Chamber 2010?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Afa \"The Wild Samoans\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Seth Rollins defend the Intercontinental Title at 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Ladder Match"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"Hard Times\"",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Titus O'Neill \"Prime Time Players\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What longtime rival did The Miz beat at SummerSlam 2018?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Shawn Michaels \"DX Army\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Nation Leader\"",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Night of Champions 2013?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did John Cena and Kane compete at Elimination Chamber 2012?",
"Answer": "Ambulance Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who is fond of growling \"You're Fired!\" at WWE Superstars?",
"Answer": "Mr.McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who was forced to join the Nexus when he lost a match at Hell in a Cell 2010?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who, in late 2013, briefly joined The Wyatt Family, to the shock of the WWE Universe?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Fatal 4-Way TLC Match for the World Heavyweight Title at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2010?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not fight for the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at the 2009 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with John Cena to face the Shield at Elimination Chamber 2013?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Randy Orton to win the SmackDown Tag Titles at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2016?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Lumberjack Match at SummerSlam 2014?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Championship at the 2017 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Bray Wyatt in a No Holds Barred Match at Backlash 2016?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Roman Reigns \"The Shield\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Jeff Hardy \"The Decomposing Enigma\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Through June 2021, who had not been both Raw and SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a tag team champion at Extreme Rules 2013?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a tag team champion at Extreme Rules 2013?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Roman Reigns \"This is My Graveyard\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Champion vs. Intercontinental Champion Match at Survivor Series 2017?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Jim \"The Anvil\" Neidhart?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to defend the WWE Title in a Hell in a Cell Match?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Hell in a Cell 2017?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Triple Threat TLC Match for the SmackDown Women's Title at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2018?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Sasha Banks \"The Boss\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kevin Owens \"Bite Owens Bite\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Roman Reigns \"The Juggernaut\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Randy Savage \"Macho Man\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is George \"The Animal\" Steele?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is King Barrett \"King of Bad News\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who helped successfully defend the Unifed Tag Titles at WrestleMania XXVI?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kane \"The Devil's Favorite Demon\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Which is a signature move of Bianca Belair?",
"Answer": "K.O.D"
},
{
"Question": "Who were the only tag team that survived the 2016 Survivor Series Tag Team Elimination Match?",
"Answer": "Sheamus & Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Hell in a Cell 2021?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Charlotte Flair \"Unnatural Selection\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2009?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Big Dead Machine\"",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania 29?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Earthquake \"The Natural Disasters\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't compete for the Raw Women's Title at Money in the Bank 2018?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Fatal 5-Way Match at Battleground 2017 to become #1 Contender for the SmackDown Women's Title?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Sgt. Slaughter \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Undertaker \"The Last Outlaw\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Goldberg \"Who's Next\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Tag Team Champion at 2016's NXT Takeover: Dallas?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team used to delight fans by licking each other's heads?",
"Answer": "The Bushwhackers"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at SummerSlam 2018?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who replaced Roman Reigns in the Shield's Match at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2017?",
"Answer": "Kurt Angle"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the WWE vs. Nexus 7-on-7 Elimination Match at SummerSlam 2010?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Tables Match for the United States Championship at Extreme Rules 2011?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Women's Title at Elimination Chamber 2017?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at Hell in a Cell 2021?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Night of Champions 2015?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did John Cena defeat at 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors did Bianca Belair eliminate from the 2020 Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": 8
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Raw Tag Team Champion at Roadblock: End of the Line 2016?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Raw Tag Team Champion at Roadblock: End of the Line 2016?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "What former Andre the Giant Battle Royale winner was the runner up in the WrestleMania 34 edition?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is John Cena \"Ruthless Aggression\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Vader \"The Mastodon\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title in a Three Stages of Hell Match at Payback 2013?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the World Heavyweight Title in a TLC Match at SummerSlam 2009?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who survived the Men's Elimination Match at Survivor Series 2017?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Junkyard Dog \"JYD\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title at Hell in a Cell 2021?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Diesel \"Big Daddy Cool\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Team Champ at WrestleMania Backlash 2021?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who is the High Chief Peter Maivia's famous grandson?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Roman Reigns in a Hell in a Cell Match on the June 18, 2021 Friday Night SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost his authoritative power on Raw when he lost a match at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2018?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first team to win both the Raw and SmackDown Tag Team Championships?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Brutus \"The Barber\" Beefcake?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar lasted a paltry 4 seconds 1991's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Bushwhacker Luke"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Rey Mysterio \"Master of the 619\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Lacey Evans \"The Women's Right\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Seth Rollins \"The Undisputed Future\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "From what country are The Bushwhackers?",
"Answer": "New Zealand"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with John Cena at Super Show-Down 2018?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first tag team to win a championship in a Hell in a Cell Match?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Who became an NXT Tag Team Champion at 2016's NXT TakeOver: Toronto?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who became an NXT Tag Team Champion at 2016's NXT TakeOver: Toronto?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at WrestleMania 25?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who accompanied Dolph Ziggler to the ring for his SummerSlam 2018 Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on Team Raw at Bragging Rights 2009?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't challenge for the NXT Title at June 2021's In Your House event?",
"Answer": "Killian Dane"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who claims to be the \"EST\" of WWE?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Undertaker \"American Badass\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Mr. Perfect \"NWO\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not involved in the WWE Title Match at Survivor Series 2009?",
"Answer": "Shelton Benjamin"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ricky Steamboat \"Black Belt\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What multi-time WWE Champion did Roman Reigns defeat at No Mercy 2017?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What member of the Shield was eliminated during their Elimination Match vs. Evolution at Payback 2014?",
"Answer": "None of them"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Divas Championship at Hell in a Cell 2011?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who did John Cena beat in an \"I Quit\" Match at Breaking Point 2009?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Asuka \"The Empress of Yesterday\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Steel Cage Match at Extreme Rules 2018?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title in a Ladder Match at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2014?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "What team was not part of the Triple Threat Match for the SmackDown Tag Titles at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2018?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Tag Titles with Batista in August 2008?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Shelton Benjamin \"The Hurt Business\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"Beast from the East\"",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title in a Triple Threat Ladder Match at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2010?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Through June 2021, who had been both Raw and SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Elias \"Walk with Elias\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at Hell in a Cell 2021?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT UK Title at 2017's NXT Takeover: Chicago?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title Money in the Bank Match at Money in the Bank 2013?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Asuka \"The Empress of Tomorrow\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who lasted more than 1 hour, 10 minutes in 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Wendi Richter \"Rock n' Wrestling\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Fatal 4-Way Match for the WWE Title at Backlash 2008?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for the WWE Title Match at SummerSlam 2013?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the SmackDown Tag Team Titles at Battleground 2017?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Davey Boy Smith \"British Bulldog\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend won a Kiss My Foot Match at Extreme Rules 2011?",
"Answer": "Jerry Lawler"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam 2017?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the six-man Hell in a Cell Match at Armageddon 2000?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Triple H face in his first-ever Hell in a Cell Match?",
"Answer": "Cactus Jack"
},
{
"Question": "Who left Money in the Bank 2010 as World Heavyweight Champion?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Stamina Monster\"",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title in a Fatal 4-Way Match at Night of Champions 2012?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at the 2013 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Shawn Michaels \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What legend challenged The Miz for the WWE Title at Elimination Chamber 2011?",
"Answer": "Jerry Lawler"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Batista \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an Elimination Chamber Match to earn a WWE Title shot at WrestleMania XXVII?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is The Godfather \"All Aboard\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Randy Orton beat in a Falls Count Anywhere Match at Extreme Rules 2012?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kofi Kingston \"Against All Odds\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Women's Title at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2016?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Viper\"",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Eddie Guerrero \"Viva La Raza\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Mr. McMahon by submission at WrestleMania XXVI?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who participated in the ECW Championship Scramble at Unforgiven 2008?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat a member of the Wyatt Family in less than 10 seconds at WrestleMania 32?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the World Hevyweight Title at No Way Out 2008?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Booker T \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Roddy Piper \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "From what state does Bianca Belair hail?",
"Answer": "Tennessee"
},
{
"Question": "Who was forced to leave WWE by losing his match at One Night Stand 2008?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Dusty Rhodes \"The American Dream\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 2018?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kevin Nash \"Big Sexy\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat John Cena in a Ladder Match at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2012?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kevin Nash \"Big Kev\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Money in the Bank Match at Money in the Bank 2011?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Raven Haired Renegade\"",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ted Dibiase \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Hell in a Cell 2009?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Seth Rollins face Triple H at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Unsanctioned Match"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The New Face of Fear\"",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Honky Tonk Man \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team were the sole survivors of the 10-on-10 match at Survivor Series 2018?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Natalya \"Queen of Harts\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ricochet \"NXT\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't compete in the Women's Money in the Bank Ladder Match at Money in the Bank 2018?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't compete in the Women's Money in the Bank Ladder Match at Money in the Bank 2018?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title Money in the Bank Match at Money in the Bank 2010?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Diamond Dallas Page \"Master of the Diamond Cutter\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Night of Champions 2009?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Becky Lynch \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at SummerSlam 2014?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ricky Steamboat \"The Dragon\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't compete in the Men's Money in the Bank Ladder Match at Money in the Bank 2018?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't compete in the Men's Money in the Bank Ladder Match at Money in the Bank 2018?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a sole survivor of a 5-on-5 Elimination Match at Survivor Series 2013?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "In what sport was Bianca Belair an All-American in college?",
"Answer": "Track and Field"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at SummerSlam 2018?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bray Wyatt The Fiend \"Let Me In\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Killian Dain \"Beast of Belfast\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Triple H \"The Authority\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is John Cena \"Evil Robot of the Skull King\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Women's Title at SummerSlam 2008?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Women's Title at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Undertaker in a Hell in a Cell at SummerSlam 2008?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "What pair tried to win their jobs on SmackDown back in a match at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens & Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did AJ Styles defend the WWE Title at Money in the Bank 2018?",
"Answer": "Last Man Standing Match"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Nikki Bella \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Mixed Tag Team Match at Extreme Rules 2017?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Rhea Ripley \"The Nightmare\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Triple H \"King of Kings\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Clash of Champions 2017?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not challenge Alexa Bliss for the Raw Women's Title at No Mercy 2017?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Women's Champion vs. Champion Match at Survivor Series 2017?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Paige \"Scream for Me\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on Team SmackDown at Bragging Rights 2010?",
"Answer": "Ric Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on Team SmackDown at Bragging Rights 2010?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced John Cena in a New York City Parking Lot Brawl at the 2008 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "JBL"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is John Cena \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname:\"The Ultimate Opportunist\"",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Women's Title at February 2014's NXT Arrival?",
"Answer": "Paige"
},
{
"Question": "Which one of these is a member of the Wild Samoans?",
"Answer": "Afa"
},
{
"Question": "Which one of these is a member of the Wild Samoans?",
"Answer": "Sika"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of Team B.A.D.?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for the Randy Orton/Wade Barrett WWE Title Match at Survivor Series 2010?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Extreme Rules 2017?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Randy Savage \"Madness\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Battleground 2017?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Jimmy. Uso \"The Usos\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Wendi Richter \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"5-Time World Champion\"",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Undertaker \"The Phenom\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Roddy Piper \"Rowdy\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Steve Austin \"Austin 3:16\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Pete Dunne and The Viking Raiders in the 2018 NXT War Games Match?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kane \"Big Red Machine\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "Who represented SmackDown in the WWE Champ vs. Universal Champ match at Survivor Series 2018?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Roman Reigns \"Head of the Table\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a WWE Tag Team Champion at Night of Champions 2010?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who was forced to retire after losing his match at WrestleMania XXVI?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Where is Paige from?",
"Answer": "England"
},
{
"Question": "Who challeged for the SmackDown Women's Title at Hell in a Cell 2021?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is AJ Styles \"The Untouchable One\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Jake Roberts \"The Snake\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Greg \"The Hammer\" Valentine?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Justin Bradshaw \"Acolytes Protection Agency\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who became NXT Women's Champion at 2016's NXT Takeover: Dallas?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at 2009's The Bash?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Backlash 2018?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Bobby Lashley in a Hell in a Cell Match on the June 21, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Beth Phoenix \"Glamazon\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What faction did Braun Strowman initially join?",
"Answer": "The Wyatt Family"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Jey Uso \"The Usos\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the World Heavyweight Title Championship Scramble at Unforgiven 2008?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Raw Tag Titles at Extreme Rules 2017?",
"Answer": "Sheamus & Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Cyber Sunday 2008?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bret Hart \"Excellence of Execution\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Scott Hall \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Steve Austin \"Texas Rattlesnake\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Naomi \"Feel the Glow\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Triple H \"DX\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"2nd Nature\"",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Clash of Champions 2016?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Kofi Kingston \"The New Day\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Booker T won King of the Ring when it was exclusive to what show?",
"Answer": "Smackdown"
},
{
"Question": "Who left WrestleMania Backlash 2021 as Raw Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Trish Stratus \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Night of Champions 2011?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What future tag-team partner did Daniel Bryan beat at SummerSlam 2012?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who became WWE Champion at Backlash 2016?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Tommaso Ciampa \"Blackheart\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2018?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Roman Reigns for the WWE World Heavyweight Title at Money in the Bank 2016?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Baron Corbin \"The Lone Wolf\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Extreme Rules 2014?",
"Answer": "Bad News Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "Who left Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2011 as World Heavyweight Champion?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the last woman eliminated from the Raw Women's Title Elimination Match at WrestleMania 33?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Asuka \"No One is Ready\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Razor Ramon \"The Bad Guy\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Through June 2021, Seth Rollins had won WWE Tag Team Titles with how many different partners?",
"Answer": 5
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam 2018?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is The Rock \"The Great One\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ember Moon \"The Shenom\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not fight for the United States Title at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title in a Six-Pack Challenge at Fastlane 2018?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "In what city was WrestleMania XXIV held?",
"Answer": "Orlando"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the WWE Title Match at WrestleMania Backlash 2021?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title in a Last Man Standing Match at One Night Stand 2008?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Undertaker at WrestleMania 34?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Andre the Giant \"Irresistible Force\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bray Wyatt beat in the Firefly Funhouse match at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "As of June 2021, who hadn't Sasha Banks faced in a Hell in a Cell Match?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title at 2017's NXT TakeOver: Brooklyn III?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Angelo Dawkins \"The Street Profits\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at the 2008 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Shelton Benjamin"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title in an Intergender Tag Match at SummerSlam 2008?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ric Flair \"Co-Owner\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team challenged for the SmackDown Tag Titles twice on the June 4, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ted Dibiase \"Million Dollar Man\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the NXT Title at 2016's NXT Takeover: Brooklyn II?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "What type of match did Roman Reigns compete in at Great Balls of Fire 2017?",
"Answer": "Ambulance Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Armageddon 2008?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Rocky Johnson's Championship-winning tag team in WWE?",
"Answer": "Soul Patrol"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Women's Title at Extreme Rules 2010?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Drew McIntyre beat on the May 31, 2021 Raw to become #1 Contender for the WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Hacksaw Jim Duggan?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Sika \"Wild Samoans\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Brie Bella \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Glorious One\"",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The Hardcore Legend\"",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What team won the SmackDown Tag Team Titles on the SmackDown after SummerSlam 2018?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Pete Dunne \"The Bruiserweight\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Jerry \"The King\" Lawler?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in 2 Elimination Chamber Matches at No Way Out 2009?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2010?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the vacant WWE Title at Hell in a Cell 2013?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Undertaker \"The Deadman\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not face Undertaker in a Hell in a Cell Match?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Ric Flair \"Slick Ric\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is R Truth \"The Truth\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Backlash 2009?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 5 competitors from the 2013 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a tag team champion at Survivor Series 2014?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Women's Title at the 2009 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Sheamus \"The Celtic Warrior\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Divas Title at Survivor Series 2014?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "At college in which state was Bianca Belair an all-conference performer?",
"Answer": "Tennessee"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the WWE Title Elimination Chamber Match at Elimination Chamber 2012?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at WrestleMania 29?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bushwhacker Butch?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the World Heavyweight Title Elimination Chamber Match at Elimination Chamber 2011?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "What team won the Unified Tag Titles at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2009?",
"Answer": "D-Generation X"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a tag team champion at Fastlane 2015?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Honky Tonk Man \"Shake Rattle & Roll\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is WALTER \"Ring General\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Nikki Bella \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who became at Raw Tag Team Champion at 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bray Wyatt"
},
{
"Question": "At Elimination Chamber 2018, who won an Elimination Chamber Match to become #1 Contender for the Universal Title?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Dolph Ziggler \"DZ\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Champion did Triple H challenge in a 3 Stages of Hell Match at 2009's The Bash?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at No Way Out 2009?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who became Tag Team Champions at Extreme Rules 2015?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at Survivor Series 2008?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was one half of the World's Strongest Tag Team?",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who is Sasha Banks' favorite WWE Legend?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Alexa Bliss \"Little Miss Bliss\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Bayley \"The Huggable One\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Diamond Dallas Page \"DDP\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an \"I Quit\" Match at One Night Stand 2008?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who is Rocky Johnson's famous son?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend used the Stump Puller as a signature move?",
"Answer": "High Chief Peter Maivia"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at No Way Out 2009?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Dolph Ziggler \"The Showoff\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 7 competitors from the 2011 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at WrestleMania XXVI?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Jinder Mahal beat to win the WWE Title?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Naomi \"Always Shine\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who lasted less than 30 seconds in the 2009 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Stretcher Match at One Night Stand 2008?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Money in the Bank Ladder Match at Money in the Bank 2013?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Batista to challenge for the Unified Tag Titles at Hell in a Cell 2009?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Tag Titles in an Iron Man Match at Great Balls of Fire 2017?",
"Answer": "Sheamus & Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kane beat in a Buried Alive Match at Bragging Rights 2010?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who did the Usos beat for the SmackDown Tag Team Titles in March 2017?",
"Answer": "American Alpha"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Tommaso Ciampa defend the NXT Title at 2018's NXT TakeOver: Brooklyn 4?",
"Answer": "Last Man Standing Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Shane McMahon in a No Holds Barred Match at No Way Out 2009?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Trish Stratus \"Stratusfaction\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at WrestleMania XXIV?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Night of Champions 2010?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Backlash 2017?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Edge \"The Brood\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Tables, Ladders & Chairs 2009?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Adam Cole \"The Undisputed Era\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Triple H beat in a Sledgehammer Ladder Match at Tables, Ladders and Chairs 2011?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the World Heavyweight Title at One Night Stand 2008?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2015 Survivor Series tournament for the vacant WWE World Heavyweight Title?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Scott Hall \"Outsider\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his freedom from JBL's employ at No Way Out 2009?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at Extreme Rules 2009?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "What was the tag team Greg \"The Hammer\" Valentine formed with Brutus Beefcake?",
"Answer": "The Dream Team"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Goldberg beat for the Universal Title at Fastlane 2017?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Jinder Mahal for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 2017?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "ho won the World Heavyweight Title in a Ladder Match at Extreme Rules 2009?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with R-Truth to defend the WWE Tag Titles at SummerSlam 2012?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team won the Champions vs. Champions match at Survivor Series 2017?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the 2016 Money in the Bank Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title in a Ladder Match at WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "Bad News Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Hulk Hogan \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not involved in the Raw Women's Title Match at WrestleMania Backlash 2021?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Raw Women's Title at Payback 2017?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to call himself \"Awesome\"?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not challenge for the Intercontinental Title at 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Over The Limit 2010?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who inducted High Chief Peter Maivia into the WWE Hall of Fame?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Faarooq \"Acolytes Protection Agency\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is 123 Kid \"The Underdog Hero\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is \"High Chief\" Peter Maivia?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 2013?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "What active World Champion retired days after WrestleMania XXVII?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is \"Mr. Wonderful\" Paul Orndorff?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Seth Rollins \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Booker T at WrestleMania 22?",
"Answer": "The Boogeyman"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title in a Ladder Match at Extreme Rules 2009?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "What title did Roman Reigns challenge for at 2018's Greatest Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Universal Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on Team Raw at Bragging Rights 2010?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Sycho Sid \"Master and Ruler of the World\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "From what island did High Chief Peter Maivia hail?",
"Answer": "Samoa"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Randy Orton \"Apex Predator\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "What was Greg Valentine's nickname?",
"Answer": "The Hammer"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the WrestleMania 25 Money in the Bank Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Women's Title at June 2021's In Your House?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Women's Title at February 2015's NXT TakeOver: Rival?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "What type of match did John Cena compete in at Battleground 2017?",
"Answer": "Flag Match"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did John Cena defend the WWE Title at Extreme Rules 2010?",
"Answer": "Last Man Standing Match"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The New Face of America\"",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Roman Reigns \"NXT\"?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Kevin Owens for the Universal Title at Hell in a Cell 2016?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Heavyweight Title at WrestleMania XXVII?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Jey Uso \"I'mma Get 'Em\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for the WWE Title Match at Hell in a Cell 2013?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced The Undertaker at Super Show-Down 2018?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Mankind \"Mr. Socko\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Yokozuna \"Banzai\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated John Cena at Hell in a Cell 2010?",
"Answer": "Wade Barrett"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the WWE Title Elimination Chamber Match at 2017's Elimination Chamber show?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who was forced to leave SmackDown after losing to Roman Reigns in late April 2021?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Divas Championship at Survivor Series 2010?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not challenge The Miz for the Intercontinental Title at Extreme Rules 2016?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Keith Lee beat for the NXT Championship",
"Answer": "Adam Cole"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at Hell in a Cell 2021?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Match the character Class to this nickname: \"The A-Lister\"",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is \"Rowdy\" Ronda Rousey?",
"Answer": "Striker"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Money in the Bank Match at WrestleMania XXVI?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is AJ Styles \"The Phenomenal One\"?",
"Answer": "Acrobat"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the WWE Divas Championship at Extreme Rules 2012?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Sting \"Hall of Fame\"?",
"Answer": "Showboat"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Randy Savage \"Icons of WrestleMania\"?",
"Answer": "Technician"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Iron Sheik \"Foreign Legion\"?",
"Answer": "Powerhouse"
},
{
"Question": "What group did Faarooq lead?",
"Answer": "Nation of Domination"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Fatal 5-Way Extreme Rules Match to become #1 Contender for the Universal Title at Extreme Rules 2017?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "At what event did John Cena capture his record-tying 16th World Championship?",
"Answer": "Royal Rumble"
},
{
"Question": "What Class is Hunter Hearst Helmsley \"Connecticut Blueblood\"?",
"Answer": "Trickster"
},
{
"Question": "What was the relationship between Bushwhacker Luke and Butch?",
"Answer": "cousins"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed for the ECW Title at Night of Champions 2008?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for the Universal Title Match at Hell in a Cell 2018?",
"Answer": "Mick Foley"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Raw Women's Title at Money in the Bank 2021?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What team defended the SmackDown Tag Titles at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Who refused to face Bianca Belair on the September 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was Kane in at SummerSlam 2013?",
"Answer": "Ring of Fire Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Drew McIntyre on the August 23, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Randy Orton from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the United States Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Tag Titles at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated AJ Styles from the 2021 Raw Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Last Man Standing Match by forfeit at Starrcade 2019?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Bloodline/New Day 6-Man Tag Match on the September 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Tag Team Title at Cyber Sunday 2006?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the Intercontinental Title on the August 13, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend challenged for the WCW Tag Team Titles at the 1997 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who paired with Kevin Nash to form the Insiders Tag Team?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Goldberg at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Tag Titles at 2019's NXT TakeOver: Toronto?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a NXT Tag Team Champion at 2020's NXT TakeOver: Portland?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Tables Match at Tables, Ladders, and Chairs 2019?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "What recently returned Superstar challenged Roman Reigns at the beginning of the July 23rd SmackDown?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Rhea Ripley from the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat WWE Women's Tag Team Champion Natalya on the September 13, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Brie Bella from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States Title on the July 12, 2021 episode of Raw?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Baron Corbin in a \"Battle for the Crown\" Match on a June 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Which NXT Competitor entered the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Cruiserweight Championship at 1997's Superbrawl VII?",
"Answer": "Syxx"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Kirifuda Clutch as a Signature Move?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Women's Title at 2020's NXT TakeOver: Portland?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Universal Title at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States TItle at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Whate was the last name of the guest on the KO Show on the September 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was the Women's Tag Titles first awarded in 2019?",
"Answer": "Elimination Chamber Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered SummerSlam 2021 as SmackDown Tag Champions?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Beth Phoenix from the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended both a singles and tag team title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered SummerSlam 2021 as the Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar defended the Women's Tag Titles at Tables, Ladders, and Chairs 2019?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who left SummerSlam 2021 as SmackDown Tag Champions?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Who represented the champs in the SmackDown Tag Title Match at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not part of the team that faced The Shield at Fastlane 2019?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Naomi from the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Carmella from the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jinder Mahal from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Women's Tag Team Champion at Hell in a Cell 2019?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title at 2019's Smackville?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was the WWE Title contested at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Steel Cage Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a guest referee for the WWE Title match at SummerSlam 2013?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Hulk Hogan in a Steel Cage Match at Uncensored 1998?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "From what state does Shayna Baszler hail?",
"Answer": "South Dakota"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the 10-Man Tag Match on the September 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WCW Title at Slamboree 1999?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Roman Reigns from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Rhea Ripley beat on the August 2, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who helped Sasha Banks attack Bianca Belair on the August 13, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jey Uso from the Men's Raw vs. SmackDown Match at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bayley from the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "What former champion challenged for the NXT Tile at NXT TakeOver 36?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for a multi-Title Championship at 1996's World War 3?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Dolph Ziggler from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 1998 World War 3 Battle Royal?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT North American Title at 2019's NXT TakeOver: Toronto?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was never a member of WCW's The Millionaires Club?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kofi Kingston from the 2021 Raw Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who signed a contract for a SmackDown Women's Title Match on the September 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the 10-Man Tag Match on the September 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kofi Kingston have to face in a Handicap Match at Fastlane 2019?",
"Answer": "The Bar"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the Women's Team Raw at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Strap Match at Halloween Havoc 1999?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WCW Tag Team Title at Road Wild 1999?",
"Answer": "Harlem Heat"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced John Morrison and The Miz at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Carmella from the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who told the WWE Universe on the August 27, 2021 SmackDown that he's now \"Happy\" after winning big in Vegas?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at the 2000 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who confronted Roman Reigns at the end of Money in the Bank 2021?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "From what city does Stacy Keibler hail?",
"Answer": "Baltimore"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Hulk Hogan at Starrcade 1996?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Title at 2019's NXT TakeOver: Toronto?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Title at 2019's NXT TakeOver: Toronto?",
"Answer": "None of these"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in WCW as GI Bro?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at 2001's WCW Greed?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Hardcore Match at Slamboree 1999?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "Who represented Raw in the Triple Threat Cruiserweight Title Match at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "Akira Tozawa"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered SummerSlam 2021 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jinder Mahal from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who opened the August 20, 2021 SmackDown with a fiery speech?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who became the #1 Contender for the WCW Title at Spring Stampede 1997?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WCW Title at Mayhem 1999?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Becky Lynch at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Baron Corbin on the August 13, 2021 SmackDown, meaning Corbin can no longer beg for money?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who left 2019's NXT Takeover: New York as NXT Champion?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "What nickname did John Morrison give himself in 2021?",
"Answer": "Johnny Drip-Drip"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Fatal 4-Way Elimination Match on the August 27,2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Universal Title at 2019's Super ShowDown?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at the 2019 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Seth Rollins on the September 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Edge on the September 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Title at 2019's NXT Takeover: XXV?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "What year was the New World Order Formed",
"Answer": 1996
},
{
"Question": "Who did Hulk Hogan beat in the infamous \"Fingerpoke of Doom\" Match?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Shane McMahon at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was the Universal Title defended at the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Strap Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Street Profits/Alpha Academy match on the August 13, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Angelo Dawkins"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of Match did The New Day compete at Tables, Ladders, and Chairs 2019?",
"Answer": "Ladder Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title on the July 16th episode of SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "What type of match was the Universal Title contested at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Falls Count Anywhere"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Intercontinental Title Match at Elimination Chamber 2020?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar opened the August 13, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is called The Monday Night Delight?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who signed a contract on the August 13, 2021 SmackDown to challenge for the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who did The Miz viciously attack on the August 23, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost in a Last Man Standing Match at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who has hosted the Raw TV Show \"Moist TV\"?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who claimed on the August 20, 2021 SmackDown that he would leave WWE if he didn't win his SummerSlam Match?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WCW Title at 1999's Uncensored?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Natalya from the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the Women's Wargames Match at 2019's NXT TakeOver: WarGames?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Becky Lynch have to beat at Fastlane 2019 to get back into the WrestleMania 35 Main Event?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is called The Guru of Greatness?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at 2019's Super ShowDown?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Becky Lynch in a Hell in a Cell Match at Hell in a Cell 2019?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Seth Rollins blame for Edge's injury on the September 17, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "The WWE Universe"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Damian Priest defeat on the August 16, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of WCW's Filthy Animals Group?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of WCW's Filthy Animals Group?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Elias from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not challenge for the WWE Title in the 2019 Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who saved Cesaro on the September 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced United States Champion Sheamus on the August 9, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kevin Owens from the 2021 SmackDown Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Team Champion at Money in the Bank 2021?",
"Answer": "Jimmy Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Team Champion at Money in the Bank 2021?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at Starrcade 1999?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "What city does John Morrison call home?",
"Answer": "Los Angeles"
},
{
"Question": "Who became the first-ever 3-time NXT Champion in August 2021?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Seth Rollins from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Lacey Evans"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar has been a regular co-host of The Dirt Sheet Show?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors were in the 1997 World War 3 Battle Royal?",
"Answer": 60
},
{
"Question": "Who left the 2019 Royal Rumble as SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at Halloween Havoc 1996?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who left SummerSlam 2021 as the Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on a team that challenged for the SmackDown Tag Titles at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who cashed in their Money in the Bank contract on the September 13, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Triple Threat Match for the WWE Title at 2019's Smackville?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who started their Sports Entertainment career in WCW?",
"Answer": "Stacy Keibler"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for the Universal Title Match at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Lacey Evans"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Tag Team Turmoil Match on the September 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley & MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who did The Demon confront on the September 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Handicap Match on the August 16, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man eliminated from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Street Profits vs. Ziggler and Roode match on the August 6, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "What was not a stipulation in the WCW Title Match at 1999's Uncensored?",
"Answer": "Baseball Bat on a Pole"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Titus O'Neil from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the only competitor to appear in the first 2 Men's Money in the Bank Matches?",
"Answer": "Shelton Benjamin"
},
{
"Question": "Who assisted Finn Bálor on the August 27, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Raw Tag Team Champion at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Raw Tag Team Champion at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Symphony of Destruction Match on the July 19th Raw?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ricochet from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at the 2019 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Tag Titles at Tables, Ladders, and Chairs 2019?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Tag Team Titles at 2019's NXT Takeover: New York?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who is not an original member of The Bloodline?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Street Profits vs. Ziggler and Roode match on the August 6, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Montez Ford"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WCW Title at Starrcade 1997?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not participate in the 2019 NXT Halftime Heat Match?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2021, what woman had the Money in the Bank cashed in on her 3 times?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a winner take all match for 2 NXT Titles in 2020?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Triple Threat Match for the WWE Title at the 2018 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a WCW Tag Team Champion at Mayhem 2000?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who betrayed the Four Horsemen in the WarGames Match at Fall Brawl 1997?",
"Answer": "Curt Hennig"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Charlotte Flair from the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Finn Bálor on the September 17, 2021 SmackDown to face The Usos?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "How did Edge win his SummerSlam 2021 Match?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did the Street Profits win the NXT Tag Titles?",
"Answer": "Ladder Match"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of the Doll Charlotte Flair was given on the September 17, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Charly"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big E from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to lose a Title due to a Money in the Bank contract cash-in?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Bobby Lashley compete at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Last Man Standing Match"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar did not eliminate multiple competitors from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who put his WWE career on the line in a match at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Television Championship at the 1998 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT North American Title at NXT TakeOver: XXX?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WCW Title at Bash at the Beach 2000?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kairi Sane from the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WCW United States Title at Starrcade 1996?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Triple Threat Ladder Match for the SmackDown Tag Titles at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in Drew McIntyre's corner when he fought Roman Reigns at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "What type of match was not one of the falls in the 2-out-of-3 Falls Match for the NXT Title at 2019's NXT TakeOver: Toronto?",
"Answer": "Ladder Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the Raw Women's Championship on the July 19th Raw?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who called himself \"The Visionary of Drip\" on SmackDown in 2021?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who became NXT Women's Champion at 2018's NXT TakeOver: New Orleans?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Triple H and Batista compete in at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "No Holds Barred"
},
{
"Question": "What was John Morrison's first singles title in WWE?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first competitor to appear in 5 Money in the Bank Matches?",
"Answer": "Shelton Benjamin"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced the NXT Champion on the August 9, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to Cash in her Money in the Bank contract the same day she won it?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was never King of the Ring?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WCW Title at Starrcade 1999?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Kevin Owens to face The New Day at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Title on the July 13, 2021 episode of NXT?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Women's Title at 2019's NXT Takeover: New York?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Universal Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Dolph Ziggler from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Bobby Lashley by disqualification on the August 23, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kofi Kingston from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ricochet from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Edge defeat at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Sami Zayn from the 2021 SmackDown Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who stole Miz and Morrison's Drip-Stick 2000 at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who is nicknamed \"The Excellence of Execution\"?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the NXT Title on September 14, 2021?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at the 2019 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Drew McIntyre defeat at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who interrupted the Roman Reigns Family Celebration on the August 27, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Universal Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Edge from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Roman Reigns at Tables, Ladders, and Chairs 2019?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the vacant ECW Title at 2007's Vengeance: Night of Champions?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Lacey Evans"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Undertaker beat for the WWE Title at Survivor Series 1991?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered SummerSlam 2021 as SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Becky Lynch at Tables, Ladders, and Chairs 2019?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Sami Zayn from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "How many teams did the New Day defeat in the Tag Team Turmoil Match on the September 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": 5
},
{
"Question": "Who calls himself \"America's Moist Wanted\"?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who became WCW Champion at Hog Wild 1996?",
"Answer": "Hollywood Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Drew McIntyre name his sword after?",
"Answer": "mother"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Hall of Famer was ringside for a 2021's NXT TakeOver 36 Match?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shane McMahon defeat at 2019's Super ShowDown?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WCW Title at 1999's Spring Stampede?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "Who came out and attacked Drew McIntyre during the 2021 Men's Money in the Bank Match?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bianca Belair from the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Bloodline/New Day 6-Man Tag Match on the September 20,2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated King Corbin from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Women's Title at 2018's NXT TakeOver: Chicago II?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Stun Gun Match at Souled Out 1999?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Seth Rollins from the Men's Raw vs. SmackDown Match at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who left SummerSlam 2021 as SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated the NXT Champion on the August 2, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who was supposed to face Baron Corbin on the September 17, 2021 SmackDown, but did not after Corbin attacked him?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Booker T beat in the finals of the 2006 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Cruiserweight Title at Elimination Chamber 2019?",
"Answer": "Akira Tozawa"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at Road Wild 1997?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WCW Title at 1999's SuperBrawl IX?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "What was John Morrison's first Championship in WWE?",
"Answer": "WWE Tag Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Roman Reigns in a Falls Count Anywhere Match at the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bret Hart beat by submission at Uncensored 1998?",
"Answer": "Curt Hennig"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 5 competitors from the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "In what city was SummerSlam 2021 held?",
"Answer": "Las Vegas"
},
{
"Question": "Who was half of a team that won the WWE Tag Titles at Night of Champions 2012?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at Fall Brawl 2000?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who has Batista won a Tag Title with?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who won two matches at WCW Mayhem 1999?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at Slamboree 2000?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Roman Reigns from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost an \"I Quit\" Match at SummerSlam 2006?",
"Answer": "Mick Foley"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Champion at Super ShowDown 2020?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title on the September 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WCW Title at Halloween Havoc 1996?",
"Answer": "Hollywood Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "What longtime WWE title was contested at 2021's NXT TakeOver 36?",
"Answer": "The Million Dollar Championship"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a WCW Tag Team Champion at 1999's SuperBrawl IX?",
"Answer": "Curt Hennig"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jeff Hardy from the 2021 Raw Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Carmella from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Nikki Bella"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Johnny Gargano at Worlds Collide 2020?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who surprised his opponent by using a Glam Slam at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Shinsuke Nakamura from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "What Hall of Famer was a Special Guest Referee at Starrcade 1997?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Samoa Joe from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match??",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ember Moon from the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Hulk Hogan compete at Halloween Havoc 1997?",
"Answer": "Steel Cage Match"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors did Shayna Baszler eliminate from the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 8
},
{
"Question": "Who unsuccessfully challenged for the United States Title at Halloween Havoc 2000?",
"Answer": "Jim Duggan"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was the Universal Title defended at the 2021 Royal Rumbe?",
"Answer": "Strap Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who served as an Executive Consultant when he joined WWE in 1991?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Fastlane 2019?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an \"I Quit\" Match at WCW Mayhem 1999?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Baron Corbin on the August 6, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Dolph Ziggler from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Money in the Bank 2021?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Beth Phoenix from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Television Championship at 1998's SuperBrawl VIII?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not make the semifinals of the 2015 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Trish Stratus from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of Team Baszler at 2019's NXT TakeOver: WarGames?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who returned to face Bobby Lashley on the the July 19th Raw?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Which Legend never won the King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Nia Jax from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of Drew McIntyre's sword?",
"Answer": "Angela"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "Lacey Evans"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated John Morrison from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who left the September 13, 2021 Raw as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "What Hall of Famer accompanied the nWo WarGames team at Fall Brawl 1996?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not face Edge & The Mysterios in 6-Man Tag action on the July 16th SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the 2019 Men's Money in the Bank Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Cruiserweight Championship at Fall Brawl 1997?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who has Batista won a Tag Team Title with?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on a team in the Triple Threat Match for the SmackDown Tag Titles at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with a basketball All Star to face Hulk Hogan at Bash at the Beach 1998?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "Who helped Roman Reigns ambush Finn Bálor on the August 6, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Who opened the July 16th, 2021 episode of SmackDown, welcoming back the WWE Universe?",
"Answer": "Mr. McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WCW Title at Spring Stampede 1998?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was originally a professional football league cheerleader?",
"Answer": "Stacy Keibler"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Goldberg spear on the August 2, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "MVP"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title in a Handicap Match at Elimination Chamber 2019?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Hardcore Match to become WCW Commissioner at Souled Out 2000?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete for a Title at SummerSlam 2013?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WCW Title at Road Wild 1999?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar is called The Prince of Parkour?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at 2001's WCW Greed?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "ho did Sheamus beat in the finals of the 2010 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ember Moon from the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "What new champion opened the August 27, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Kevin Nash compete at Starrcade 1999?",
"Answer": "Powerbomb Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at Money in the Bank 2021?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Randy Orton from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "What Legend welcomed Bianca Belair home on the September 17, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World Television Title at 1999's WCW Uncensored?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in two matched on the August 20, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who left 2019's NXT Takeover: New York as NXT UK Champion?",
"Answer": "WALTER"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Pete Dunne from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Seth Rollins from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "competed in his first WWE match in 12 years in the Main Event of Survivor Series 2016?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Natalya from the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "o eliminated Nia Jax from the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Raw Tag Team Champion at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who became WCW Tag Team Champions at Halloween Havoc 1996?",
"Answer": "The Outsiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at the 2019 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "What former Women's Champion injured her knee in early July 2021, putting her out of action for several months?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Lacey Evans at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended both the United States and Television Titles at Mayhem 1999?",
"Answer": "Scott Hall"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Hulk Hogan at Halloween Havoc 1998?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Cruiserweight Championship at Halloween Havoc 1997?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated King Corbin from the 2021 SmackDown Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar returned to their hometown on the September 17, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Finn Bálor defeat at 2020's NXT TakeOver: Portland?",
"Answer": "Johnny Gargano"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Finn Bálor defeat at 2020's NXT TakeOver: Portland?",
"Answer": "None of these"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Sami Zayn from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "What wasn't a team in the Triangle Elimination Match at Uncensored 1997?",
"Answer": "Team Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on the same team at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kevin Owens from the Men's Raw vs. SmackDown Match at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on the winning team for the 2019 Dusty Rhodes Tag Team classic?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "At what 2021 event did The Miz cash in his Money in the Bank Contract?",
"Answer": "Elimination Chamber"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of Match did Roman Reigns compete at Tables, Ladder, and Chairs 2019?",
"Answer": "Tables, Ladders, and Chairs Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors did Drew McIntyre eliminate from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": 6
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who goes by the nickname \"The Submission Magician\"?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Title at Starrcade 1997?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Rhea Ripley from the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to cash in his Money in the Bank contract the same day he won it?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who was last eliminated in the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sid Justice"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Ember Moon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Shayna Baszler from the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sheamus beat in the finals of the 2010 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who had not won a Royal Rumble as of 2021?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Alexa Bliss from the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses The Reckoning as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title on the July 16th episode of SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "How did the Universal Title Match at Hell in a Cell 2019 end?",
"Answer": "referee stoppage"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States Title at Halloween Havoc 1997?",
"Answer": "Curt Hennig"
},
{
"Question": "Who stole Big E's Money in the Bank contract on the August 13, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Otis defeat on the August 20, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Montez Ford"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title at Fastlane 2019?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the United States Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Which NXT UK Competitor entered the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Undertaker at 2019's Super ShowDown?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the Men's Wargames Match at 2019's NXT TakeOver: WarGames?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Randy Orton from the 2021 Raw Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Baron Corbin from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who accompanied Curt Hennig for his match at Fall Brawl 1998?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Lacey Evans from the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar had a documentary crew with them throughout January 2021?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the United States Champion vs. Intercontinental Champion Match at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in Hair Match in summer 1998?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Hulk Hogan at the 1998 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who was taken away in an ambulance after his match on the September 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "ho competed in a Handicap Match on the August 2, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first entrant in the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Handicap Elimination Match at Halloween Havoc 2000?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at a music festival on the July 23rd, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Natalya from the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at Money in the Bank 2021?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced United States Champion Damian Priest on the September 17, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Cesaro from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Seth Rollins from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the Women's Team SmackDown at Survivor Series 2020?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee in the WCW Title Match at 1999's Spring Stampede?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Charlotte Flair on the August 16, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who was expected to challenge for the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated John Cena from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who gave Baron Corbin some needed money on the July 23rd SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the World War 3 Battle Royal in 1997?",
"Answer": "Scott Hall"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kane from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Nikki Bella from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated King Corbin at Hell in a Cell 2019?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on a team that competed for the Women's Tag Titles at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the runner-up of the 2020 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 3 competitors from the Gauntlet Match at Super ShowDown 2020?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the SmackDown Women's Title on the SmackDown after Hell in a Cell 2019?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "From what city does Damian Priest hail?",
"Answer": "New York"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Finn Bálor beat on the August 6, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WCW Title at Fall Brawl 2000?",
"Answer": "Booker T"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Fatal 4-Way Match for the United States Title at Fastlane 2019?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Alexa Bliss from the 2021 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "What SmackDown Superstar came to the August 9, 2021 Raw to challenge Drew McIntyre?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who goes by the nickname \"The Queen of Spades\"?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on a team that challenged for the Women's Tag Titles at Starrcade 2019?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Tag Titles at 2019's NXT Takeover: New York?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Hall of Famer provided commentary for 2021's NXT TakeOver 36?",
"Answer": "Beth Phoenix"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Rey Mysterio from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who speared the WWE Champion to end the August 16, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Gauntlet Match at Super ShowDown 2020?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Tag Titles at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at Road Wild 1999?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Handicap Match on the August 2, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at 1997's Superbrawl VII?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first entrant in the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Lacey Evans"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Tag Titles at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Otis"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar uses Starship Pain as a signature move?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to lose a Title due to a Money in the Bank contract cash-in?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WCW Title at Halloween Havoc 1998?",
"Answer": "Diamond Dallas Page"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated the Miz on the August 23, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Which was not a team that fought in the WarGames Match at Fall Brawl 1998?",
"Answer": "Team Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WCW Title at Slamboree 1999?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bayley from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who left SummerSlam 2021 as United States Champion?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first Money in the Bank Match not held at a WrestleMania?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "What is the name of Stone Cold Steve Austin's interview program on the WWE Network?",
"Answer": "Broken Skull Sessions"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title on the September 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first woman to be a two-time NXT Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who is known as the Powerhouse of Positivity?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Through September 2021, who's the only Superstar to win 2 King of the Ring Tournaments?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in his first WWE match in 12 years in the Main Event of Survivor Series 2016?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Elias from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT UK Championship at 2021's NXT TakeOver 36?",
"Answer": "WALTER"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Rhea Ripley on the July 12, 2021 episode of Raw?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Title at 2020's NXT TakeOver: Portland?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Women's Tag Titles at Fastlane 2019?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Women's Tag Titles at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was the Raw Women's Title contested at SummerSlam 2019?",
"Answer": "Submission Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost in the Firefly Funhouse match at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Sheamus from the 2021 Raw Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Lacey Evans from the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Natalya from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Trish Stratus"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of the nWo 2000 Faction?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated multiple competitors from the 2021 Raw Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title in a Handicap Match at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Whose nickname is the Archer of Infamy?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who gave Charlotte Flair a gift on the September 17, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with the Viking Raiders in 6-Man Tag Action on the September 17, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Which is a signature move of Stacy Keibler?",
"Answer": "Roundhouse Kick"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a 4-Way Match among Money in the Bank competitors on the July 16, 2021 episode of SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated AJ Styles from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Roman Reigns at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the WCW Title at Bash of the Beach 1999?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2021, what woman has waited the longest to cash in her Money in the Bank contract?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended 2 Titles at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jeff Hardy from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Otis from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Bayley"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Cruiserweight Title at 1999's Spring Stampede?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the 2019 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for the NXT Title Match on the July 13, 2021 episode of NXT?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Where were fans first introduced to John Morrison",
"Answer": "Tough Enough"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Randy Orton to a match on the August 9, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a \"Loser Leaves WCW\" Match at 2001's SuperBrawl Revenge?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who left SummerSlam 2021 as Raw Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who interrupted Elias' WrestleMania 35 concert?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "What recently returned Superstar challenged Roman Reigns at the end of the July 23rd SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the United States Title at 1999's SuperBrawl IX?",
"Answer": "Scott Hall"
},
{
"Question": "Who left SummerSlam 2021 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Boxing Match at Bash at the Beach 1999?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on the nWo WarGames team at Fall Brawl 1996?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Roddy Piper beat at Halloween Havoc 1997?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged Bobby Lashley after his July 19th match on Raw?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the United States Title at the 2019 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who likes to brag \"You can't see me!\"?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who asked Baron Corbin to come to the August 9, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who was gifted a personalized scooter on the August 23, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Goldberg beat in a No Holds Barred Match at Starrcade 2000?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Rey Mysterio on the August 20, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Xavier Woods from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2021 Men's Money in the Bank Match?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who signed a contract on the August 13, 2021 SmackDown to defend the SmackDown Women's Title at SummerSlam?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in Team Hell No?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in Team Hell No?",
"Answer": "Daniel Bryan"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Roddy Piper at the 1998 Great American Bash?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Randy Orton from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been a frequent user of the Figure 4 Leglock?",
"Answer": "Greg \"The Hammer\" Valentine"
},
{
"Question": "Who has been a frequent user of the Figure 4 Leglock?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Xavier Woods from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Miz from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar made it to the finals of a 2017 multi-night Women's Tournament?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Women's Champion Triple Threat Match at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in a Universal Title Match at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the North American Title at 2020's NXT TakeOver: Portland?",
"Answer": "Keith Lee"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ember Moon from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Asuka"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Women's Tag Team Champion on the September 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Intercontinental Title at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Damian Priest from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Finn Bálor from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Miz from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT Women's Title at 2020's NXT TakeOver: Portland?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was the WCW Title defended at Fall Brawl 2000?",
"Answer": "Caged Heat Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on Team Hogan at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in Shinsuke Nakamura's corner for his match at Clash of Champions 2019?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who was subjected to a \"Broodbath\" on the August 20, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost in a House of Horrors Match at Payback 2017?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Angelo Dawkins beat at a music festival on the July 23rd, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the last entrant in the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Who attacked WWE Champion Bobby Lashley at the end of the September 6th, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who became the #1 Contender for the United States TItle on the September 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated multiple competitors from the 2021 SmackDown Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man to both win and lose Titles in Money in the Bank contract matches?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Chad Gable on the August 27, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Nia Jax replace in the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big E from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who became WCW Champion at Starrcade 1998?",
"Answer": "Kevin Nash"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Nia Jax from the 2019 Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Cesaro from the the 2021 SmackDown Elimination Chamber Match?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "What SmackDown Superstar calls himself The Master Strategist?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Champions Triple Threat Tag Match at Survivor Series 2019?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Team Champion at Elimination Chamber 2019?",
"Answer": "Jimmy Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a SmackDown Tag Team Champion at Elimination Chamber 2019?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar uses The Moonlight Drive as a signature move?",
"Answer": "John Morrison"
},
{
"Question": "Who returned to attack Sami Zayn on the July 16, 2021 episode of SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Money in the Bank 2019?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who was part of the winning team in the first TLC match?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who began the September 13, 2021 Raw as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WCW Title at Road Wild 1997?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Whose return from a multi-week absence kicked off the August 9, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Street Profits/Alpha Academy match on the August 13, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "What team reunited at Worlds Collide 2020?",
"Answer": "DIY"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not make the semifinals of the 2019 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Raw Women's Champion Charlotte Flair on the September 17, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was the Universal Title contested at Crown Jewel 2019?",
"Answer": "Falls Count Anywhere Match"
},
{
"Question": "What piece of Jinder Mahal's property did Drew McIntyre defeat on the July 12, 2021 episode of Raw?",
"Answer": "Motorcycle"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first competitor eliminated from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Naomi from the 2018 Women's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Nia Jax"
},
{
"Question": "Through 2021, what man has waited the longest to cash in his Money in the Bank contract?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Bobby Lashley on the August 23, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Whose challenge did Roman Reigns accept at the end of the July 23rd SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in a House of Horrors Match at Payback 2017?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in the first TLC match?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a \"Loser Leaves WWE\" match on Raw in 1993?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Steel Cage Match at Super ShowDown 2020?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered SummerSlam 2021 as United States Champion?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Ricochet beat for the United States Title at Stomping Grounds 2019?",
"Answer": "Samoa Joe"
},
{
"Question": "Who upset WWE Champion Bobby Lashley on the July 12, 2021 episode of Raw?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who calls themselves \"The Blackheart\"?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the 24/7 Title on the September 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Akira Tozawa"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Elias from the 2021 Men's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "How quickly did Sheamus win at WrestleMania 28?",
"Answer": "18 seconds"
},
{
"Question": "Who also uses Stone Cold's Stunner as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bobby Lashley from the 2019 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Bret Hart beat to retain the WWE Title at the 1992 Survivor Series?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "What weapon did Edge love using as a tag team specialist?",
"Answer": "Chairs"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Rey Mysterio from the 2018 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in a Casket Match at WrestleMania 22?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "What double chair hit did Edge's tag team make famous?",
"Answer": "Con-Chair-To"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a King of the Ring Quarterfinal Match on the October 11, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a King of the Ring Quarterfinal Match on the October 11, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Which entrant of the 1991 Royal Rumble Match never showed up for his spot?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Chad Gable on the November 1, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for Lex Luger's WWE Title Match at WrestleMania X?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Honky Tonk Man from the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Lex Luger from the 1995 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on a team to challenge the Women's Tag Team Champions on the November 1, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bret Hart from the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on a team that challenged for the Raw Tag Titles at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Bianca Belair on the October 11, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Earthquake from the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Bianca Belair eliminate from her 2021 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": 3
},
{
"Question": "Who won a King of the Ring Quarterfinal Match on the October 11, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a King of the Ring Quarterfinal Match on the October 11, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost his spot on the SmackDown Men's Survivor Series team due to losing on the November 12, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a King of the Ring Semifinal Match on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who earned a spot on Raw's Men's Survivor Series Team by winning a match on the November 8, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Fatal 4-Way Match for a spot on Team SmackDown on the November 19, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Paul Orndorff from his 1987 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "How was The 1-2-3 Kid eliminated from the 1994 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Honky Tonk Man from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Jim Neidhart"
},
{
"Question": "Who became King of the Ring at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a Raw member after the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar eliminated from the 2021 Men's Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Roddy Piper from the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sid Justice"
},
{
"Question": "On what team did the Bushwhackers compete at the 1990 Survivor Series?",
"Answer": "The Alliance"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Earthquake from the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first first-round pick by SmackDown in the SmackDown portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who entered Crown Jewel 2021 as SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who stole Undertaker's urn at the 1995 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Irwin R. Schyster"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2019 Men's Money in the Bank Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Mr. Perfect from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Which title was not defended at SummerSlam 1994?",
"Answer": "WWE Tag Team Titles"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Happy Corbin from his 2021 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who formed a team with three of his brothers for a 1993 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Street Profits/Alpha Academy Match on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Sgt. Slaughter from the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sid Justice"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of Jerry Lawler's Royal Family team at Survivor Series 1994?",
"Answer": "Wheezy"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jake Roberts from the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not drafted to Raw in the SmackDown portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Ricochet for the United States Title at Extreme Rules 2019?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Shinsuke Nakamura from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Roman Reigns in the Main Event of the November 12, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "King Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the second first-round pick by Raw in the Raw portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "The Hurt Business"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar interrupted the world premiere of \"Happy Talk\" on the September 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bushwhacker Butch from the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who attacked Big E during his match on the November 1, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bushwhacker Butch from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Bret Hart eliminate from the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 4
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Diesel eliminate from his Survivor Series 1994 Match?",
"Answer": 3
},
{
"Question": "Who faced the Intercontinental Champion on the October 22, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Happy Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kofi Kingston from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Hulk Hogan from the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Sid Justice"
},
{
"Question": "Who was eliminated from the 1995 King of the Ring Tournament when he wrestled to a draw during the Quarterfinals?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who placed the crown on the new King of the Ring on the October 22, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "How was Undertaker eliminated from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in a Fatal 5-Way Match for a Raw Women's Title opportunity on the November 8, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "ho won the WWE Champion vs Universal Champion Match at Survivor Series 2021?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar crashed \"Happy Talk\" on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first first-round pick by Raw in the Raw portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Brock Lesnar for the WWE Title at No Way Out 2004?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Ted DiBiase eliminate in the 1990 Survivor Series event?",
"Answer": 3
},
{
"Question": "Who did not accompany Bam Bam Bigelow to the ring for his WrestleMania XI Match?",
"Answer": "Iron Sheik"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Big E/McIntyre vs. Roode & Ziggler Match on the October 4, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first entrant in the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Doink the Clown from the 1993 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Razor Ramon from his 1995 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with The New Day on the October 1, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Rick Rude from his 1988 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Jake Roberts"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Universal Title at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Irwin R. Schyster from the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "What Champion was a supplemental pick by Raw on Night 1 of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "24/7 Champion"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title twice on the September 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "What Submission Move does Brock Lesnar employ?",
"Answer": "Kimura Lock"
},
{
"Question": "Who helped King Woods attack The Bloodline on the November 19, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with a WWE Official in an October 15, 2021 SmackDown Match?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of The Teamsters squad at Survivor Series 1994?",
"Answer": "Roddy Piper"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bam Bam Bigelow from the 1994 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jake Roberts from the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Andre the Giant"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor when the All-Americans met the Foreign Fanatics at Survivor Series 1993?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't Bam Bam Bigelow face in the 1993 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar calls herself \"The Blueprint\" of the WWE Women's Division?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "What team was not in the 8-Man Tag Match on the October 1, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "By what name does the tag team of Robert Roode and Dolph Ziggler go by?",
"Answer": "Dirty Dawgs"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Cesaro from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Rhea Ripley defeat on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Bobby Lashley to face the New Day at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "How was Typhoon eliminated from his 1991 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "pinfall"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the last Superstar eliminated from the 25-Man Battle Royal at Survivor Series 2021?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Charlotte Flair on the October 11, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who was suspended for his actions on the October 22 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Casket Match at the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Shelton Benjamin from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "How did Rey Mysterio lose his match on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ted DiBiase from the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated MVP from the 2020 Royal Rumble??",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors did \"Hacksaw\" Jim Duggan eliminate from the first Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 3
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar eliminated from the 2021 Women's Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the second first-round pick by SmackDown in the Raw portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the 25-Man Battle Royal at Survivor Series 2021?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Shayna Baszler defeat on the October 29, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bushwhacker Luke from the 1995 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Dusty Rhodes from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Bam Bam Bigelow in a Tag Team Match at SummerSlam 1994?",
"Answer": "Irwin R. Schyster"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Champion vs. United States Champion Match at Survivor Series 2021?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Dusty Rhodes from the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Earthquake"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title on the November 1, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Women's Title at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to eliminate 10 or more competitors in a single Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ted DiBiase from the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "In what round of the 1994 King of the Ring tournament was Razor Ramon eliminated?",
"Answer": "Finals"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Roddy Piper face at the 1994 King of the Ring event?",
"Answer": "Jerry Lawler"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors did Brock Lesnar eliminate from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 13
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Bobby Lashley in the Main Event of the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced WWE Champion Big E in a match on the November 1, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Whose victory on the November 5, 2021 SmackDown was overruled by WWE Management?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Undertaker eliminate from his 1995 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": 3
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ted DiBiase from the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "On what captain's Survivor Series team did Undertaker make his 1990 WWE debut?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big Boss Man from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Earthquake"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jake Roberts from the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a Queen's Crown Semifinal Match on the October 18, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Elias from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Randy Savage from the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who seconded Jeff Hardy for his match on the November 19, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on a tag team for the 1987 10-on-10 Survivor Series Tag Team Match?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who left Extreme Rules 2021 as Universal Champion?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "ho defended the SmackDown Tag Team Titles on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Shawn Michaels eliminate from his 1991 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": 1
},
{
"Question": "From what city does Brock Lesnar hail?",
"Answer": "Minneapolis"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Big E to face Dolph Ziggler and Robert Roode on the October 4, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Undertaker in a Casket Match at SummerSlam 1995?",
"Answer": "Kama"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Randy Savage from his 1993 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Irwin R. Schyster"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Razor Ramon to challenge for the WWE Tag Titles at 1995's In Your House 4?",
"Answer": "The 1-2-3 Kid"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the SmackDown Tag Team Title Match at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "Montez Ford"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first second-round pick by SmackDown in the SmackDown portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who was a member of The Underdogs team at Survivor Series 1995?",
"Answer": "The 1-2-3 Kid"
},
{
"Question": "Who left Extreme Rules 2021 as SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2003 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Which member of the New Day was not selected by SmackDown in the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the United States Title on the October 4, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the SmackDown Women's Title Match at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match were the SmackDown Tag Team Titles defended on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Ontario Street Fight"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ted DiBiase from the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Big John Studd"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jerry Lawler from his 1995 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who attacked Bobby Lashley on the October 4, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who proclaimed himself a \"Locker Room Leader\" on the November 12, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Raw vs. SmackDown Champion vs. Champion Match at Survivor Series 2021?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Brock Lesnar face at WrestleMania XX?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title in a 60-Minute Iron Man Match on a September 2003 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who attacked Seth Rollins on the October 8, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Triple H from his 1995 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Which Superstar was not disqualified from his 1991 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Honky Tonk Man from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Brutus Beefcake"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the second first-round pick by Raw in the SmackDown portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a King of the Ring Semifinal Match on the October 18, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Which title was not on the line in the Main Event of 1995's In Your House 3?",
"Answer": "WWE Cruiserweight Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who substituted for R-Truth in a match on the October 18, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who signed a contract to face Roman Reigns at Crown Jewel on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Irwin R. Schyster from his 1993 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Shawn Michaels from the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ted DiBiase from his 1988 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "What was the last name of the guest on the KO Show on the September 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Seth Rollins defeat in the Main Event of the November 8, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who confronted Universal Champion Roman Reigns during the opening of the October 1, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Triple Threat Match to win a Tag Team Title Opportunity on the October 25, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "The Dirty Dawgs"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the F-5 as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who left the September 27, 2021 Raw as United States Champion?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Greg Valentine from his 1988 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who did King Woods defeat on the November 5, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Jimmy Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who destroyed King Woods' crown on the November 19, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Mr. Perfect from the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The British Bulldog from the 1995 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Doink the Clown from the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "Who answered Drew McIntyre's open challenge on the November 5, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Mr. Perfect from the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost in the King of the Ring Finals at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Colonel Mustafa from his 1991 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged the 24/7 Champion on the September 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did The 1-2-3 Kid eliminate in his 1995 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": 2
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with the Raw Tag Team Champs in a match on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a King of the Ring Quarterfinal Match on the October 8, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a King of the Ring Quarterfinal Match on the October 8, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Kevin Owens defeat on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jake Roberts from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Randy Savage from the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Yokozuna"
},
{
"Question": "Who seconded Diesel for his Intercontinental Title Match at SummerSlam 1994?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a No Disqualification Match on the November 1, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the New Day vs. Usos Match on the October 29. 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Jimmy Uso"
},
{
"Question": "How did the Usos defeat Drew McIntyre and Big E on the October 11, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Robert Roode from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "How did Razor Ramon win his match at WrestleMania XI?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Fatal 4-Way Match for a spot on Team SmackDown on the November 19, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "What champion was selected by SmackDown in the second round of the Raw portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Intercontinental Champion"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States Title on the September 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Intercontinental Title at the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Irwin R. Schyster"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Happy Corbin defeat on the October 22, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Big E/McIntyre vs. Roode & Ziggler Match on the October 18, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jake Roberts from his 1988 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Hell in a Cell Match at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "How was Roddy Piper eliminated from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jim Neidhart from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a Survivor of his 1988 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the 8-Man Tag Match on the October 1, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who attacked Charlotte Flair at the end of the October 22, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "What title was defended based on a \"Spin the Wheel, Make the Deal\" Stipulation on the Halloween Havoc 2021 episode of NXT?",
"Answer": "NXT Women's Title"
},
{
"Question": "How did Seth Rollins win his Main-Event Match on the November 8, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Nikolai Volkoff from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Brock Lesnar defeat to win his first WWE Title?'",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did 1-2-3 Kid eliminate from his 1993 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": 1
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Greg Valentine from the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who was called \"The Next Big Thing\" when he joined the WWE?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team were guests on the November 5, 2021 episode of \"Happy Talk\" on SmackDown?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the 2021 Women's Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a King of the Ring Semifinal Match on the October 18, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on the team that Jinder Mahal faced in Six-Man Tag Action on the September 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Jeff Hardy"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Raw Women's Champion Charlotte Flair in a match on the October 4, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the sole survivor of the 2021 Men's Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title on the September 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Shinsuke Nakamura"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bushwhacker Luke from the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Finn Bálor from his 2021 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who was forced to compete in a Handicap Match on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the victim of 2 RKOs and a Big Ending on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who Powerbombed Rey Mysterio through a table in the Main Event of the October 25, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Sycho Sid from his 1995 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Which Title did NOT change hands during the October 26, 2021 Halloween Havoc Episode of NXT?",
"Answer": "NXT Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged the Usos on the Crown Jewel 2021 pre-show?",
"Answer": "The Hurt Business"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for championships in two different matches at 1995's In Your House 4?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "How was Jim Duggan eliminated from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who was controversially pinned on the November 19, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bushwhacker Luke from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Rick Rude"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Undertaker from the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the WWE Title on 2019's SmackDown's 20th Anniversary show?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who answered Drew McIntyre's Open Challenge on the October 22, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who managed Sycho Sid for his match at 1995's In Your House 3?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who left the September 27, 2021 Raw as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Irwin R. Schyster from the 1994 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The 1-2-3 Kid from his Survivor Series 1994 Match?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Greg Valentine from the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "ho won a King of the Ring Quarterfinal Match on the October 8, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bushwhacker Luke from the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Earthquake"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ted DiBiase from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first Superstar to ever enter a Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Title on the October 26, 2021 Halloween Havoc Episode of NXT?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Queen's Crown Quarterfinal Match on the October 11, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Brutus Beefcake from his 1987 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "The Honky Tonk Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Shayna Baszler from her 2021 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Diesel from his 1993 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "How was Jim Duggan eliminated from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Tugboat from the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first man eliminated from the 2020 Men's Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Elias"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jeff Hardy from his 2021 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Champion vs. Champion Tag Team Match at Survivor Series 2021?",
"Answer": "RK-Bro"
},
{
"Question": "Where was Survivor Series 2021 held?",
"Answer": "Brooklyn"
},
{
"Question": "How did Bret Hart win his match at 1995's In Your House 3?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Natalya from her 2021 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "What WWE Hall of Famer was drafted by Raw in the SmackDown portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who interfered in the Diesel-British Bulldog WWE Title Match at 1995's In Your House 4?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a King of the Ring Quarterfinal Match on the October 8, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a King of the Ring Quarterfinal Match on the October 8, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated a fellow member of her SmackDown Women's Team on November 19, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Shayna Baszler on the November 19, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not move from SmackDown to Raw during the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Doink the Clown eliminate from the 1995 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 0
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title on the September 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in Evolution?",
"Answer": "Batista"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title twice on the September 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "How did Lex Luger win his WWE Title Match at SummerSlam 1993?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Tag Team Titles at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "How was Sasha Banks eliminated from her 2021 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not move from Raw to SmackDown during the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who left Crown Jewel 2021 as SmackDown Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Ladder Match at WrestleMania X?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who attacked Bret Hart after his WWE Title defense at SummerSlam 1994?",
"Answer": "Jim Neidhart"
},
{
"Question": "Who left Extreme Rules 2021 as Raw Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a King of the Ring Semifinal Match on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Rey Mysterio from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced WWE Champion Big E in a match on the November 8, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first first-round pick by SmackDown in the Raw portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Isaac Yankem from his 1995 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated King Woods from his 2021 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Bianca Belair on the October 1, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Dirty Dawgs/Street Profits match on the November 1, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "How was Shawn Michaels eliminated from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "pinfall"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Champion vs Universal Champion Match at Survivor Series 2021?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Tag Team Titles on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title on the November 1, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Irwin R. Schyster from the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Earthquake"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Fatal 4-Way Match for a spot on Team SmackDown on the November 19, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Happy Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on a team that faced The Viking Raiders on the November 5, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Happy Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who made a statement on her return to Raw, winning a match on the October 25, 2021 episode?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Universal Title at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Lex Luger eliminate from his 1994 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": 2
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Falls Count Anywhere Match at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Goldberg"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Women's Tag Titles on the October 4, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "Alexa Bliss"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost his spot on the Raw Men's Survivor Series team as a result of a match on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the WWE Title at SummerSlam 2014?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Dirty Dawgs/Street Profits match on the November 1, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Montez Ford"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bret Hart from the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Dusty Rhodes"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Handicap Match at 1995's In Your House I?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Undertaker eliminate from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": 2
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Papa Shango from the 1993 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Jim Duggan"
},
{
"Question": "What was the first Championship Brock Lesnar won in his WWE career?",
"Answer": "WWE Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not involved in the Triple Threat Match for the United States Title at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 7 consecutive Superstars from the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a Hell in a Cell Match at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a Free Agent as a result of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Brock Lesnar from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Greg Valentine from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Jim Duggan"
},
{
"Question": "Who replaced Sami Zayn in the 2019 Men's Money in the Bank Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Queen's Crown Quarterfinal Match on the October 8, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "The holder of what NXT Title was drafted by SmackDown in the SmackDown portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "NXT North American Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who captured the WWE Title at 2003's WrestleMania XIX?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who left Extreme Rules 2021 as United States Champion?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "At what 2002 event did Brock Lesnar win his first World Title?",
"Answer": "Summerslam"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bushwhacker Butch from the 1995 Royal Rumble",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not Survive the first-ever Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Jim Duggan"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Shawn Michaels from the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the second first-round pick by SmackDown in the SmackDown portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 2002 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jim Duggan from the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar's home did Seth Rollins shockingly invade during the October 1, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Street Profits/Alpha Academy Match on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Montez Ford"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not counted out of his match at Survivor Series 1994?",
"Answer": "Razor Ramon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Rhea Ripley from her 2021 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a Falls Count Anywhere Match at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the first-ever Women's Royal Rumble Match?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Women's Title on the October 18, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Raw Tag Title Match on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Tag Team Champion at SummerSlam 1999?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Tag Team Champion at SummerSlam 1999?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Intergender Tag Team Match for the Intercontinental Title at SummerSlam 2000?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Main Event Tag Title Match at 1998's Fully Loaded: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Hardcore Title at Insurrextion 2000?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Fatal Five-Way WWE Title Match at 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who was named Roman Reigns' Royal Rumble opponent on the January 7, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Riddle from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Kane in a Steel Cage Match at Armageddon 1999?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big Boss Man from the 1999 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the United States Title on the November 22, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the Six-Man Tag Match for the WWE Title at King of the Ring 2000?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "At what 2000 event did the first Tables, Ladders, and Chairs Match take place?",
"Answer": "Summerslam 2000"
},
{
"Question": "What did WALTER announce he was changing his name to on the January 18, 2022 NXT?",
"Answer": "Gunther"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Riddle defeat on the December 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Stone Cold Steve Austin from the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Mr. McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Naomi defeat on the December 17, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Chyna from the 2000 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a WWE Women's Tag Team Champion on the November 22, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Riddle at 2019's NXT TakeOver: WarGames?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Jake Roberts not beat to make the finals of the 1996 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Ultimate Warrior"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Raw Women's Title Match at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the WWE Title at 1999's St. Valentine's Massacre: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "What pairing held a Graduation Ceremony on the the January 17, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Alpha Academy"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Buried Alive Match at 1998's in Your House: Rock Bottom?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin during the Raw Tag Title Match at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "Who left SummerSlam 2000 as Intercontinental Champion?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the 6-Man Hell in a Cell Match at Armageddon 2000?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who spent the most time in the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bam Bam Bigelow"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Stone Cold Steve Austin defend the WWE Title at Fully Loaded 1999?",
"Answer": "First Blood Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Tag Team Titles at 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "RK-Bro"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Handicap Match on the November 22, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title in a Anything Goes Match at No Mercy 1999?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Last Man Standing Match at Fully Loaded 2000?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Randy Orton face on the December 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ricochet from the 12 Days of Christmas Gauntlet Match on the December 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Hardcore Title at SummerSlam 2000?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bushwhacker Butch from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in two first-round matches in the Deadly Games Tournament at Survivor Series 1998?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who pinned a Women's Tag Team Champion in a match on the December 20, 2021 Raw",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Fatal 4-Way Match for the WWE Title at Unforgiven 2000?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Roman Reigns nail with a Superman Punch to open the January 7, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who got hit with pie in the face on the December 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated King Corbin from his Survivor Series 2020 Match?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "Who survived his Survivor Series 1999 Match?",
"Answer": "Godfather"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big Boss Man from the 2000 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on a team that defended the Raw Tag Titles at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Intercontinental Title at SummerSlam 1997?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "How did Big E win his match on the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "escaped the cage"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Stone Cold Steve Austin from the Deadly Games Tournament at Survivor Series 1998?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "How did Charlotte Flair win her match on the January 7, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "pinfall"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jake Roberts from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Vader"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors did Stone Cold Steve Austin eliminate from the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 8
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the 6-Man Tag Match on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Angelo Dawkins"
},
{
"Question": "Who disbanded the Hurt Business on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in an \"RK-Bro-Nament\" Match on the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Tag Team Titles at 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Who was challenged to an Alpha Academy Academic Challenge on the January 17, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "RK-Bro"
},
{
"Question": "Who threw 2 pies in the face of a rival on the November 26, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Rikishi face in a No Holds Barred Match at No Mercy 2000?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who spent the most time in the 1988 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced United States Champion Damian Priest on the December 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Riddle from his Survivor Series 2019 Match?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kane from the 2000 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The 1-2-3 Kid from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who go the pin in the Triple Threat Tag Team Match on the December 10,2021 Smackdown?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "How many of the Top 10 moments of the year on the December 31, 221 SmackDown were from Wrestlemania 37?",
"Answer": 3
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete for the WWE Title at Unforgiven 1999?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete for the WWE Title at Unforgiven 1999?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who gave Baron Corbin some needed money on the July 23 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Fully Loaded Strap Match to become #1 Contender for the WWE Title at Fully Loaded 1999?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What team did not compete in the \"RK-Bro-Nament\" on the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Yokozuna from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Lumberjack Match at 1995's In Your House 2?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "Who seconded Bret Hart for his WWE Title Match at Survivor Series 1994?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who earned the pin in the opening 8-Man Tag Match on the November 8, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who goes by the nickname \"Big Time\"?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first first-round pick by Raw in the Smackdown portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bret Hart from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at Survivor Series 2000?",
"Answer": "Kurt Angle"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Main Event Tag TItle Match at 1998's Fully Loaded: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on the team that faced Becky Lynch in a 10-Woman Tag Team Match on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "What team won the Triple Threat Tag Team Match on the December 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "The New Day"
},
{
"Question": "Who fought the WWE Champion in a Steel Cage Match on the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Women's Tag Match on the November 26, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "From what country does Nikki A.S.H. hail?",
"Answer": "Scotland"
},
{
"Question": "What team won the WWE Tag Team Titles at Fully Loaded 1999?",
"Answer": "The Acolytes"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Fatal 4-Way Ladder Match on the October 25, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Boiler Room Brawl at Backlash 1999?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Greg Valentine from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee in the WWE Title Match at Backlash 1999?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Bobby Lashley face Seth Rollins on the December 13, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "No Disqualification Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the guest on the KO Show that aired on the January 17, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who returned from a suspension on the December 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "What woman won the 2021 Money in the Bank Ladder Match?",
"Answer": "Nikki A.S.H"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Steel Cage Match at SummerSlam 1997?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the guest on the Miz TV episode on the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kane from the 1999 Corporation vs. DX \"Corporate Rumble\"?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Mr. Perfect eliminate from the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 3
},
{
"Question": "Who got the pin in the Miracle on 34th Street Fight on the December 24 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Survivor Series 2000?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "How did Stone Cold Steve Austin beat Bret Hart at 1997's In Your House: Revenge of the Taker?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who left the November 1, 2021 Raw as Raw Women's Champion?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the United States Title on the January 3, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who pinned AJ Styles on the January 3, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Omos"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at Armageddon 1999?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Stone Cold Steve Austin defend the WWE Title at Backlash 1999?",
"Answer": "No Holds Barred Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a \"Mask vs. Mask\" Match at 1998's Over The Edge: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Vader"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Mr. McMahon compete at 1999's St. Valentine's Day Massacre: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Steel Cage Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Raw Tag Team Titles at 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Sheamus from the 12 Days of Christmas Gauntlet Match on the December 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Raw Tag Team Title Match on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "What Championship was defended twice on the October 12, 2021 episode of NXT?",
"Answer": "North American Title"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NXT North American Championship on the November 23, 2021 NXT?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Godfather from the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Boot Camp Match at 1997's D-Generation X: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "What did Sami Zayn name his new Stunt Show on January 14, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "inZayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Sasha Banks on the December 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the NXT Title at NXT's New Year's Evil 2022?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the WWE Title Triple Threat Match at 1998's Fully Loaded: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "How did AJ Styles win his match on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Fairy Tale Ending as a signature move?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not accompany Triple H to the ring for his Iron Man Match at Judgment Day 2000?",
"Answer": "All of these"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Falls Count Anywhere Match at Judgment Day 2000?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars competed in the first-ever Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 20
},
{
"Question": "Who did Raw select with its first pick in the second round of the Raw portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the New Day vs. Hurt Business Match on the October 4, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team was not in the Triple Threat Match that ended the December 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Randy Orton defeat on the December 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Otis"
},
{
"Question": "Who interfered in the SmackDown Women's Title Match at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Hardcore Title at Fully Loaded 1999?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Cesaro from the 12 Days of Christmas Gauntlet Match on the December 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the United States Title at Fastlane 2021?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the United States Title on the December 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the RK-Bro/Alpha Academy Match on the January 3, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "Who teams with Randy Orton in the RK-Bro pairing?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was the WWE Title defended at the Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Street Fight"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a Tag Team Champion at Armageddon 2000?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Mixed Tag Team Match on the January 3, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Akira Tozawa"
},
{
"Question": "How much was Brock Lesnar fined on the October 29, 2021 SmackDown for his actions the previous week?",
"Answer": "$1 million"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at 1997's In Your House: Canadian Stampede?",
"Answer": "Vader"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a 1-on-4 Survivor Series Elimination Match at Survivor Series 1999?",
"Answer": "Big Show"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Rey Mysterio from the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Omos"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Mr. Perfect from the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the 8-Man Tag Match on the January 17, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Montez Ford"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Strap Match at Unforgiven 2000?",
"Answer": "Jerry Lawler"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at King of the Ring 1999?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "How was Lex Luger eliminated from the 1994 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not get involved in the WWE Title Match that opened the September 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced SmackDown Women's Champion Charlotte Flair in a match on the January 7, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the New Day/Usos Match on the December 17, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Jimmy Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Outside Enforcer for the WWE Title Match at King of the Ring 1996?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not on the team that challenged the Radicalz at Survivor Series 2000?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title on the December 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Stone Cold Steve Austin eliminate from the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 7
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did the Usos defend the SmackDown Tag Titles on the January 7, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Street Fight"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Triple H from the 1998 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Riddle on the December 13, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Otis"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first WWE Championship at Survivor Series 1996?",
"Answer": "Sycho Sid"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kama from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "Who slammed Becky Lynch and Sasha Banks through a table on the October 8, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who spent the most time in the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "What Raw Superstar won a match on the January 11, 2022 NXT?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost the fastest match in WWE history on the January 14, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Women's Tag Match on the November 26, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Natalya"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Honky Tonk Man from the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Vader"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the last person eliminated from the 1999 Corporation vs. DX \"Corporate Rumble\"?",
"Answer": "Mr. McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bradshaw from the 2000 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Kurt Angle"
},
{
"Question": "Who hosted the talk show \"Happy Talk\" on the September 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Baron Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big E from the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Omos"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the piin during the Raw Tag Team Title Match on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Otis"
},
{
"Question": "Who go the pin in the Triple Threat Tag Team Match on the December 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Steel Cage Match at Fully Loaded 2000?",
"Answer": "Rikishi"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Roman Reigns 1-on-1 on the September 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Montez Ford"
},
{
"Question": "Who, in January 2022, set a record for the longest Universal Title reign in WWE history?",
"Answer": "Roman Reigns"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Ricochet in a Tag Team Match on 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who turned on her partner Rhea Ripley on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Nikki A.S.H"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Fatal Five-Way WWE Title Match at 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced the Viking Raiders in a Tag Team Match on the December 17, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Jinder Mahal"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the European Title at Armageddon 1999?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the #1 Contender Fatal 4-Way Match on the January 3, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "How did Chyna lose the Intercontinental Title at Armageddon 1999?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Main Event Tag Match on the December 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who fought in a Greenwich Street Fight at SummerSlam 1999?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a #1 Contenders Match for the Raw Women's Title on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the Flag Match at 1997's In Your House: Badd Blood?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "How did WWE Champion Undertaker defeat Bret Hart at the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Hair vs. Hair Match at SummerSlam 1998?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Chyna win the Intercontinental Title at No Mercy 1999?",
"Answer": "Good Housekeeping Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Vader from his Survivor Series 1997 Match?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kama Mustafa from the 1998 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Black Friday Battle Royal on the November 26, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "How many of the Top 10 moments of the year on the December 31, 2021 SmackDown were from SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": 5
},
{
"Question": "How did Dolph Ziggler win his match on the December 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bret Hart from the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who put his career on the line for a WWE Title shot at No Way Out 2000?",
"Answer": "Cactus Jack"
},
{
"Question": "Who was Seth Rollins supposed to face on the November 22, 2021 Raw until Rollins attacked him before the match?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States Title on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Nikki A.S.H"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Falls Count Anywhere Match at 1998's Fully Loaded: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Bradshaw"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Tag Team Championship on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Otis"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Mixed Tag Team Match on the December 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "R-Truth"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jerry Lawler from the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big Boss Man from his 1991 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Irwin R. Schyster"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Undertaker from the Deadly Games Tournament at Survivor Series 1998?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not get an F-5 from Brock Lesner on on the December 17, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Happy Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Crowbar on a Pole Match on the January 11, 2022 NXT?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sheamus defeat on the January 14, 2022 SmackDOwn?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not challenge for the WWE Title at Rebellion 2000?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the NWA North American Title at 1998's No Way Out of Texas?",
"Answer": "Bradshaw"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors did Ultimate Warrior eliminate from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": 2
},
{
"Question": "Who spent the most time in the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "How did Dolph Ziggler win his match on the December 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Isaac Yankem from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "Becky Lynch"
},
{
"Question": "What Raw Superstar competed in 6-Man Tag Match at NXT's New Year's Evil 2022?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Last Man Standing Match at Armageddon 2000?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who earned a WWE Title Opportunity at WWE Day 1 on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced the Viking Raiders in a Tag Team Match on the January 7, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Happy Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Triple H in a No Holds Barred Match at Armageddon 1999?",
"Answer": "Mr. McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for the WWE Title Match at Backlash 2000?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "How did Kane win his match at WrestleMania XV?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who got the pin in the New Day/Usos Match on the December 17, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "How did X-Pac lose his second round match in the 2000 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Kama Mustafa from the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the WWE Title Triple Threat Match at SummerSlam 2000?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Road Dogg from the 1999 Corporation vs. DX \"Corporate Rumble\"?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Lion's Den Weapons Match at SummerSlam 1999?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "How did Kane win his match at Survivor Series 1999?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the 12 Days of Christmas Gauntlet Match on the December 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Riddle face on the November 22, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who spent the most time in the 1991 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Greg Valentine"
},
{
"Question": "From what Superstar did Drew McIntyre recover his sword Angela on the December 17, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Happy Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Godfather from the 2000 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "What is Riddle's hometown?",
"Answer": "Las Vegas"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Casket Match at the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the United States Title on the September 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Rock from his Survivor Series 1997 Match?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Triple H from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Diesel"
},
{
"Question": "How did Bianca Belair win her match on the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Seth Rollins in a match that opened the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the only King of the Ring 1999 semifinalist that wasn't a former D-Generation X Member?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "Who beat Triple H in the first round of the 1996 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Jake Roberts"
},
{
"Question": "Who hasn't won a Tag Team Title with Undertaker as his partner?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete for the WWE Title at SummerSlam 1999?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Falls Count Anywhere Match at WrestleMania X?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who's return at SummerSlam 2021 was chosen the #1 WWE Moment of the Year on the December 31, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Raw Women's Title at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who used a fire extinguisher during a tag-team match on the November 22, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced the WWE Champion on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the first person eliminated from the 1999 Corporation vs. DX \"Corporate Rumble\"?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the Universal Title at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "The Demon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ivar from the 12 Days of Christmas Gauntlet Match on the December 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "What Raw Superstar appeared on the December 21, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "How did Carmella lose her match on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "pinfall"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the SmackDown Women's Title at Extreme Rules 2021?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Triple H from the 1999 Corporation vs. DX \"Corporate Rumble\"?",
"Answer": "Mr. McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ken Shamrock from the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Tag Team Championship at WrestleMania 37?",
"Answer": "Omos"
},
{
"Question": "How was Jerry Lawler eliminated from the 1997 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who fought in a FInal Chapter Match on the December 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bianca Belair"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated X-Pac from the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Vader from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the European Title at the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big Boss Man from the 1999 Corporation vs. DX \"Corporate Rumble\"?",
"Answer": "Mr. McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Rock from the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at No Way Out 2000?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who got the pin in the Main Event Tag Match on the December 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Randy Orton from his Survivor Series 2019 Match?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "What recently returned Superstar challenged Roman Reigns at the beginning of the July 23 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "John Cena"
},
{
"Question": "The first WWE No Way Out event was actually titled \"No Way Out of....\"?",
"Answer": "Texas"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match did Ken Shamrock compete at Fully Loaded 1999?",
"Answer": "Iron Circle match"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Damian Priest in a Championship Contender's Match on the January 17, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with The New Day for a Miracle on 34th Street Fight on the December 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Handicap Tables Dumpster Match at King of the Ring 2000?",
"Answer": "D-Generation X"
},
{
"Question": "What city is Nikki A.S.H.'s hometown?",
"Answer": "Glasgow"
},
{
"Question": "Who was part of the Corporation team that challenged for the Tag Titles at 1998's In Your House: Rock Bottom?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Black Friday Battle Royal on the November 26, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who was the Special Guest Referee for the WWE Title Match at SummerSlam 1997?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Mixed Tag Team Match at SummerSlam 1998?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who initially won the Intercontinental Title at WrestleMania XIV only to have the decision reversed?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who interrupted Edge's return on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Women's Tag Team Title Match on the January 3, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Nikki A.S.H"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Alexa Bliss to win the Women's Tag Team Titles at WrestleMania 36?",
"Answer": "Nikki Cross"
},
{
"Question": "Who interrupted the Wedding Vow Renewal Ceremony on the December 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Edge"
},
{
"Question": "Who left 2022's Day 1 as WWE Champion?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who became an NXT Tag Team Champion at 2020's NXT TakeOver: Portland?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar wore a protective covering on her face for her match on the October 1, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Sheamus defeat on the December 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Cesaro"
},
{
"Question": "Who was forced to defend the WWE Tag Titles by himself at SummerSlam 1998?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Triple H from the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Rock from the 1998 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who had a bye in the quarterfinals of the Deadly Games Tournament at Survivor Series 1998?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a No Holds Barred Match at No Way Out 2000?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who goes by the nickname \"The Glowing Superstar\"?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Big E/McIntyre vs. Roode & Ziggler Match on the October 18, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Shawn Michaels eliminate from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 8
},
{
"Question": "Who won the first-ever Boiler Room Brawl at SummerSlam 1996?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who spent the most time in the 1989 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Mr. Perfect"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at WrestleMania 35?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who answered Damian Priest's Open Challenge on the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Robert Roode"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the 6-Man Hell in a Cell Match at Armageddon 2000?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who threatened several lawsuits at the beginning of the December 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Lex Luger eliminate from the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 6
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the European Title at Backlash 2000?",
"Answer": "Eddie Guerrero"
},
{
"Question": "Who accompanied Kurt Angle to the ring for his WWE Title challenge at No Mercy 2000?",
"Answer": "Stephanie McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who was attacked by his own tag team partner on the December 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "AJ Styles"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with the SmackDown Tag Team Champs in a match on the November 15, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jinder Mahal from the 12 Days of Christmas Gauntlet Match on the December 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "In what UK city did 1997's One Night Only event take place?",
"Answer": "Birmingham"
},
{
"Question": "Who uses the Bromission as a Signature Move?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "Who became a WWE Tag Champion at 1996's In Your House: Mind Games?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Triple Threat Match for the WWE Title at Insurrextion 2000?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Riddle from the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the WWE Title at 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who didn't Bobby Lashley have to beat on the December 13, 2021 Raw to earn a WWE Title opportunity?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first United States Title at Elimination Chamber 2021?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jerry Lawler from the 1997 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Lion's Den Match at SummerSlam 1998?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The British Bulldog from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Seth Rollins in the Main Event of the January 21, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Kevin Owens"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Nikki Cross from the 2021 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Stone Cold Steve Austin eliminate from the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 10
},
{
"Question": "Who was forced to compete solo in a Tag Team Match after his partner was injured on 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title at Backlash 1999?",
"Answer": "Godfather"
},
{
"Question": "Who interrupted \"Happy Talk\" on the December 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Drew McIntyre"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Seth Rollins face on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Big E"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the Handicap Ladder Match at King of the Ring 1999?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big Boss Man from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Dusty Rhodes"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Sasha Banks in a 6-Woman Tag Match on the November 12, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Diesel from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Big Boss Man from the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Kane to face D-Generation X at WrestleMania 2000?",
"Answer": "Rikishi"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Triple Threat Tag Team Match on the December 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Jey Uso"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Drew McIntyre face on the December 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Mankind from the Deadly Games Tournament at Survivor Series 1998?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Mankind from the 1997 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Blackjack Bradshaw from the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Dude Love"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jerry Lawler from the 1996 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these Superstars won the most matches in the Days of Christmas Gauntlet Match on the December 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sheamus"
},
{
"Question": "Whose challenge did Roman Reigns accept at the end of the July 23 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "Who renewed his wedding vows on the December 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "The Miz"
},
{
"Question": "On what WWE Champion did Seth Rollins cash in his Money in the Bank at WrestleMania 31?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bam Bam Bigelow from the 1994 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Lex Luger"
},
{
"Question": "Who captained a team of three different colored Knights in a 1993 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Shawn Michaels"
},
{
"Question": "Who had won 2 King of the Ring tournaments through 2021?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jake Roberts from the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Riddle defeat at Payback 2020?",
"Answer": "King Corbin"
},
{
"Question": "Who was coronated King of the Ring on the October 22, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the Intercontinental Title at the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Rock from the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Mankind"
},
{
"Question": "How did King Woods win his match on the December 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Natalya in a 6-Woman Tag Match on the November 12, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Shayna Baszler"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Vader from the 1998 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Shane McMahon from the 2000 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Rikishi"
},
{
"Question": "Who helped The Rock in the WWE Title Match at Backlash 2000?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "What faction was Shawn Michaels a member of?",
"Answer": "D-Generation X"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bushwhacker Luke from his 1990 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Sgt. Slaughter"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Big E McIntyre vs. Roode & Ziggler Match on the October 4, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "What was the name of Tommaso Ciampa's NXT Tag Team?",
"Answer": "DIY"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Triple Threat Tag Team Match on the October 25, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Angelo Dawkins"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Colonel Mustafa from the 1992 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not compete in the Fatal 4-Way Match for a Tag Title Opportunity on the January 14, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Ricochet"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Tag Team Titles at 2022's Day 1?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "How did Bobby Lashley win his match on the January 17, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in a Dungeon Match at 1998's Fully Loaded: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Ken Shamrock"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Bobby Lashley in a match on the January 17, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Seth Rollins"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Bret Hart from his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Randy Savage"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in the 1996 Royal Rumble as The Ringmaster?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Brock Lesnar attack at the beginning of the December 10, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sami Zayn"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated a fellow DX member from the 1999 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated X-Pac from the 1999 Corporation vs. DX \"Corporate Rumble\"?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who faced Goldberg at Crown Jewel 2021?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "What Superstar was forced out of the ring by WWE Officials on the September 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Naomi"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the SmackDown Tag Team Titles on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "The Usos"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Becky Lynch in a 10-Woman Tag Team Match on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "Who was on the tag team that won the rights to D-Generation X at Fully Loaded 1999?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who competed in two different Quarterfinal Matches in the 1997 King of the Ring tournament?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "How did Chyna lose her Intercontinental Title challenge at Unforgiven 1999?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Big E from the 2020 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "How did Kevin Owens win his match on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the 8-Man Tag Match on the October 1, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who spent the most time in the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Ted DiBiase"
},
{
"Question": "What item was used on Sami Zayn on the January 21, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "cattle prod"
},
{
"Question": "Who defeated Becky Lynch on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Sasha Banks"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated 2 men from the 2021 Royal Rumble despite not being entered in the match?",
"Answer": "Omos"
},
{
"Question": "Who goaded Sami Zayn into challenging Roman Reigns on the December 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Brock Lesnar"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Ken Shamrock from the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who did not survive his 1989 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "Jim Neidhart"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Edge from the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Road Dogg"
},
{
"Question": "How did Ken Shamrock win his WWE Title Match at 1997's D-Generation X: In Your House?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Mr. McMahon from the 1999 Corporation vs. DX \"Corporate Rumble\"?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated The Sultan from the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The British Bulldog"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the RK-Bro/Alpha Academy Match on the January 3, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Otis"
},
{
"Question": "What team won the Fatal 4-Way Match on the January 14, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the European Title at WrestleMania XV?",
"Answer": "Shane McMahon"
},
{
"Question": "Who was in DIY?",
"Answer": "Tommaso Ciampa"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not in the Triple Threat Steel Cage Match at 1998's Fully Loaded: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Kane"
},
{
"Question": "How was Earthquake eliminated from his 1991 Survivor Series Match?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Which of these is a signature move of John Cena",
"Answer": "Attitude Adjustment"
},
{
"Question": "Who was pinned in the Street Profits/Alpha Academy Match on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Chad Gable"
},
{
"Question": "Who won a Steel Cage Match at 1999's St. Valentine's Day Massacre: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a Hell in a Cell Match at WrestleMania XV?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who spent the most time in the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who pinned a Women's Tag Team Champion in a match on the December 20, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Rhea Ripley"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a Queen's Crown Semifinal Match on the October 15, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Carmella"
},
{
"Question": "What was Riddle's first singles title in his WWE career?",
"Answer": "United States Title"
},
{
"Question": "What year did Riddle win the Dusty Rhodes Tag Team Classic?",
"Answer": 2020
},
{
"Question": "How did Roman Reigns win his match on the December 3, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the New Day vs. Usos Match on the October 29, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Xavier Woods"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Chyna from the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the WWE Title at WrestleMania XV?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "What tag team moved from Raw to SmackDown during the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "The Viking Raiders"
},
{
"Question": "Who on SmackDown in 2021 used the nickname of \"The Hand of the King\"?",
"Answer": "Kofi Kingston"
},
{
"Question": "How did the Street Profits win their \"RK-Bro-Nament\" Match on the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "countout"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Mankind from the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the 6-Man Tag Match on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Dolph Ziggler"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not involved in the Tag Team Title Match at WrestleMania 13?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the European Title at WrestleMania XIV?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "Who did Damian Priest team with in Tag Team competition on the December 13, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "In what type of match was the Women's Title defended at the 1999 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Strap Match"
},
{
"Question": "Who won his first Raw Tag Title at SummerSlam 2021?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "With what Superstar did Riddle team to win the NXT Tag Team Titles?",
"Answer": "Pete Dunne"
},
{
"Question": "Who lost a Steel Cage Match at No Mercy 2000?",
"Answer": "X-Pac"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Kane at 1999's St. Valentine's Day Massacre: In Your House?",
"Answer": "Chyna"
},
{
"Question": "How many competitors did Rikishi eliminate from the 2000 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 7
},
{
"Question": "Who defended the United States Title at WrestleMani 37?",
"Answer": "Riddle"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Finals of the RK-Bro-nament on the December 27, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "The Street Profits"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an \"RK-Bro-Nament\" Match on the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Rey Mysterio"
},
{
"Question": "Who earned a WWE Title opportunity in the Fatal 4-Way Match on the January 3, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Bobby Lashley"
},
{
"Question": "Who got the pin in the Raw Tag Title Match on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Randy Orton"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Randy Savage from the 1990 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Dusty Rhodes"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Undertaker from the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "What returning Superstar challenged Roman Reigns at the end of the July 23 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Finn Balor"
},
{
"Question": "What champion was selected by Raw in the second round of the Raw portion of the 2021 WWE Draft?",
"Answer": "United States Champion"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Faarooq from the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "The Rock"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Faarooq from the 2000 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "How did Bret Hart win his WWE Title defense at 1997's In Your House: Ground Zero?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who challenged for the WWE Title at 1995's In Your House I?",
"Answer": "Sycho Sid"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with Dolph Ziggler & Robert Roode on the October 1, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Alpha Academy"
},
{
"Question": "How did Mankind defeat The Rock at 1998's In Your House: Rock Bottom?",
"Answer": "technical submission"
},
{
"Question": "How did Naomi controversially lose her match against Charlotte Flair on the January 21, 2022 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "How did Stone Cold Steve Austin win his first round 1996 King of the Ring Match?",
"Answer": "submission"
},
{
"Question": "Who was not a member of Doink's Clowns R' Us team at Survivor Series 1994?",
"Answer": "Stink"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Chyna from the 2000 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Big Boss Man"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jerry Lawler from the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Bret Hart"
},
{
"Question": "Who won the Intercontinental Title at Survivor Series 1997?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who recorded the pin in the Street Profits/Alpha Academy Match on the November 29, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Montez Ford"
},
{
"Question": "What type of match opened the December 6, 2021 Raw?",
"Answer": "Steel Cage Match"
},
{
"Question": "How did The Rock win his Intercontinental Title Match at the 1998 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who won an Armageddon Match at 1996's In Your House: It's Time?",
"Answer": "Undertaker"
},
{
"Question": "Who successfully defended the SmackDown Women's Title on the December 24, 2021 SmackDown?",
"Answer": "Charlotte Flair"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated X-Pac from the 1998 King of the Ring Tournament?",
"Answer": "Triple H"
},
{
"Question": "How did Stone Cold Steve Austin win his first round Deadly Games Tournament Match at Survivor Series 1998?",
"Answer": "disqualification"
},
{
"Question": "Who teamed with the Street Profits in a 6-Man Tag Match on the January 10, 2022 Raw?",
"Answer": "Damian Priest"
},
{
"Question": "How many Superstars did Yokozuna eliminate from the 1993 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": 7
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Vader from the 1997 Royal Rumble?",
"Answer": "Stone Cold Steve Austin"
},
{
"Question": "Who eliminated Jim Neidhart from his Survivor Series 1997 Match?",
"Answer": "Vader"
}
]
}